1
00:02:02,540 --> 00:02:04,590
YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
更多原创字幕翻译 请登陆www.YYeTs.com

2
00:02:04,590 --> 00:02:07,190
         时间轴： godwuwen  孤帆  字幕总监： YY

3
00:02:07,190 --> 00:02:09,690
翻译： 糊笑笑  非燕  猫中之王 孤帆  字幕总监： YY

4
00:02:09,690 --> 00:02:11,690
校对： 赛不愿让你一个人  呷赛猫 孤帆  字幕总监： YY

5
00:02:11,690 --> 00:02:14,690
老爸老妈浪漫史
第七季  第二十二集

6
00:00:00,470 --> 00:00:02,990
<i>2012年5月  马修和莉莉</i>
<i>In May of 2012, Marshall and Lily</i>

7
00:00:02,990 --> 00:00:05,190
<i>在家举办新生儿送礼会</i>
<i>hosted a baby shower in the apartment.</i>

8
00:00:05,190 --> 00:00:06,850
<i>他们所有朋友都来了</i>
<i>All their friends were there.</i>

9
00:00:06,870 --> 00:00:09,620
<i>我也确保自己准时在...</i>
<i>So of course I made sure to show up exactly...</i>

10
00:00:10,380 --> 00:00:11,760
<i>3小时之后出现</i>
<i>...three hours late.</i>

11
00:00:11,770 --> 00:00:14,680
-我来晚了吗  -有点
- Oh, no! Am I late? - Little bit.

12
00:00:14,680 --> 00:00:17,270
对不起  我是想早点到的
Ah, I'm sorry, I would've gotten here earlier;

13
00:00:17,270 --> 00:00:19,180
-只是...  -你不想碰见罗宾
- it's just, um... - You didn't want to see Robin.

14
00:00:19,180 --> 00:00:20,480
我不想碰见罗宾
I didn't want to see Robin.

15
00:00:20,490 --> 00:00:22,630
我知道这样很幼稚
I know, it's childish.

16
00:00:22,630 --> 00:00:24,130
她现在不在吧
She's not here, is she?

17
00:00:24,130 --> 00:00:25,470
其实...
Actually...

18
00:00:27,570 --> 00:00:30,650
我来早了吗
Oh, no! Am I early?

19
00:00:30,650 --> 00:00:32,160
有点
Little bit.

20
00:00:34,160 --> 00:00:36,940
她送的是红色婴儿车
Whoa, she got you the red stroller?

21
00:00:36,940 --> 00:00:40,670
看来我的车青出于"蓝"胜于"蓝"啊
Looks like I just blew her out of the water.

22
00:00:41,060 --> 00:00:43,770
反正她在派对开始前就走了
Anyway, she left before the party started.

23
00:00:43,900 --> 00:00:46,000
真是不好意思
Ah, I'm really sorry, I...

24
00:00:46,000 --> 00:00:47,520
我只是觉得我和罗宾
I just think it's best if Robin and I

25
00:00:47,520 --> 00:00:48,950
这阵子最好先不要见面
don't see each other for a while.

26
00:00:48,950 --> 00:00:49,820
泰德  我无所谓
Ted, it's fine;

27
00:00:49,820 --> 00:00:51,620
我在离异家庭中长大
I'm a child of divorce.

28
00:00:51,620 --> 00:00:53,700
你们爱怎么吵就怎么吵
You guys keep fighting all you want,

29
00:00:53,710 --> 00:00:56,200
只要贵重礼物不间断就好
as long as the expensive gifts keep coming.

30
00:00:56,320 --> 00:00:57,940
送礼会怎么样
Uh, so how was the shower?

31
00:00:57,940 --> 00:00:58,900
挺好的
It was good,

32
00:00:58,900 --> 00:01:00,660
虽然巴尼的脱衣舞娘女友
although there was one weird moment

33
00:01:00,660 --> 00:01:03,080
有一度害气氛变得很尴尬
with Barney's new stripper girlfriend.

34
00:01:03,230 --> 00:01:05,130
一天50个
50 laps a day?

35
00:01:05,230 --> 00:01:07,740
天啊  小姑娘  那可真是太多了
Oh, my goodness, young lady. That is a lot.

36
00:01:07,740 --> 00:01:08,980
是吗
Oh, is it?

37
00:01:09,250 --> 00:01:12,160
有很多吗  路易丝奶奶
Is it a lot, Grandma Lois?

38
00:01:12,240 --> 00:01:15,300
没错  我女朋友靠脱衣服
Yes, my girlfriend gets naked

39
00:01:15,300 --> 00:01:17,080
坐在男人腿上跳舞挣钱
and sits on guys' laps for money.

40
00:01:17,080 --> 00:01:20,520
没错  有时候一天她能坐50个大腿
And, yes, sometimes it's as many as 50 laps in one day.

41
00:01:20,520 --> 00:01:24,000
也许社会会觉得她的工作
And maybe society considers what she does

42
00:01:24,000 --> 00:01:25,820
很"恶心"
to be "disgusting,"

43
00:01:25,820 --> 00:01:27,370
很"淫荡"
or "sutty,"

44
00:01:27,500 --> 00:01:30,390
跟"做鸡"没区别
or verging on "prostitution,"

45
00:01:30,670 --> 00:01:33,350
或就是"做鸡"
or actual "prostitution."

46
00:01:33,510 --> 00:01:35,880
但我接受她
But you know what, I accept her.

47
00:01:35,880 --> 00:01:38,320
如果你不能接受她
And if you can't do the same,

48
00:01:38,740 --> 00:01:41,220
那我真为你感到羞耻
well, then shame on you.

49
00:01:42,360 --> 00:01:43,790
为你
Shame...

50
00:01:44,300 --> 00:01:45,630
感到
on...

51
00:01:45,690 --> 00:01:47,520
羞耻
you.

52
00:01:49,110 --> 00:01:52,670
我们其实在说游泳
We were, um, talking about swimming.

53
00:01:52,790 --> 00:01:56,130
说我一天能游50个来回
How I sometimes swim 50 laps a day.

54
00:01:58,420 --> 00:01:59,720
挺好的有氧运动啊
Well, it's great cardio.

55
00:01:59,720 --> 00:02:01,870
奶奶  我帮您加点香槟吧
Lois, can I top off your champagne?

56
00:02:15,790 --> 00:02:17,020
说来也好笑
You know, it's funny,

57
00:02:17,020 --> 00:02:19,390
你告诉普通男人  你和脱衣舞女约会
you tell the average guy you're dating a stripper,

58
00:02:19,390 --> 00:02:20,750
他会觉得超级棒
he thinks it's awesome.

59
00:02:20,750 --> 00:02:23,200
你告诉妈妈  她会兴奋地跟你击掌
Heck, you tell your mom, she high-fives you so fast,

60
00:02:23,200 --> 00:02:25,040
甚至连烤箱手套都来不及摘
she doesn't even take off her oven mitts.

61
00:02:25,240 --> 00:02:28,730
个中滋味若有人懂
But if they had any idea how difficult it is:

62
00:02:28,730 --> 00:02:32,000
醋海里翻波  不安里浮沉
the jealousy, the insecurity,

63
00:02:32,090 --> 00:02:36,830
连击掌都变成慰问击掌
those high-fives would be high-fives of condolence.

64
00:02:36,830 --> 00:02:40,650
巴尼  根本没有所谓的慰问击掌
Barney, condolence high-fives are not a thing.

65
00:02:40,650 --> 00:02:41,900
当然有
They're a thing.

66
00:02:41,860 --> 00:02:44,030
{\an8}当天早些时候...

67
00:02:42,420 --> 00:02:44,390
不好意思  我们不得不辞退你
I'm afraid we're gonna have to let you go.

68
00:02:45,730 --> 00:02:47,090
来  击掌
Up top.

69
00:02:48,190 --> 00:02:51,950
别光听我说我这些无聊的情侣问题了
Ah, listen to me and my boring couples' problems.

70
00:02:52,050 --> 00:02:53,210
你怎么样
How are you?

71
00:02:53,210 --> 00:02:54,550
单身生活过得好吗
How's the single life?

72
00:02:54,550 --> 00:02:56,790
没什么感觉  自从罗宾这事后
I wouldn't know. After this whole Robin thing,

73
00:02:56,790 --> 00:02:58,880
目前的我  比较低调
for the time being, I'm laying low.

74
00:02:58,880 --> 00:03:00,070
你是说...
Laying low as in

75
00:03:00,070 --> 00:03:02,310
标准低到跟很矮的妞上床吗
sleeping with a really short chick?

76
00:03:02,310 --> 00:03:04,040
你们有玩39式吗
You guys doing 39?

77
00:03:04,170 --> 00:03:06,130
我是说我没出去约会
I mean, I'm not seeing anyone.

78
00:03:06,130 --> 00:03:08,580
我要努力忘记罗宾
I'm just, you know, trying to get Robin out of my head.

79
00:03:08,580 --> 00:03:10,750
你该"换换口味"
You need a palate cleanser.

80
00:03:10,750 --> 00:03:13,040
巴尼  求你了  千万别撮合
Barney, please, don't try to set me up

81
00:03:13,040 --> 00:03:14,200
我和昆茵的脱衣舞女同事
with Quinn's stripper friends.

82
00:03:14,200 --> 00:03:15,150
我才不会呢
Oh, I wouldn't dream of it.

83
00:03:15,150 --> 00:03:17,540
为什么不  我暗示得还不够多吗
Why not, how many hints do I have to drop?!

84
00:03:17,840 --> 00:03:20,520
不是  我想的是比较传统的方式
No, I'm thinking of something much more traditional.

85
00:03:20,520 --> 00:03:23,180
-如网络交友  -不用了  谢谢
- Online dating. - Yeah, no thanks.

86
00:03:23,180 --> 00:03:25,460
拜托  泰德  都2012了
Come on, Ted! It's 2012.

87
00:03:25,460 --> 00:03:28,240
你还指望在书店看报纸的时候
What do you expect, to meet some cute travel agent

88
00:03:28,250 --> 00:03:30,880
邂逅漂亮的旅游中介吗
when you're reading a newspaper at a bookstore?

89
00:03:30,880 --> 00:03:32,920
现在没这种事了
None of those things exist anymore.

90
00:03:32,930 --> 00:03:37,040
巴尼  我是绝对不可能
Barney, I will never, ever, ever,

91
00:03:37,040 --> 00:03:38,620
去尝试网络交友的
try online dating.

92
00:03:38,620 --> 00:03:40,570
<i>那天晚上我试了网络交友</i>
<i>That night I tried online dating.</i>

93
00:03:40,570 --> 00:03:43,960
<i>孩子们  我遇到的第一个女孩就很棒</i>
<i>And kids, the first girl I found was amazing:</i>

94
00:03:43,960 --> 00:03:46,060
<i>她漂亮聪明  风趣幽默</i>
<i>beautiful, smart, funny,</i>

95
00:03:46,060 --> 00:03:47,940
<i>热爱战前建筑</i>
<i>huge fan of prewar architecture,</i>

96
00:03:47,940 --> 00:03:49,060
<i>最喜欢的诗人是聂鲁达</i>
<i>favorite poet Neruda,</i>

97
00:03:47,940 --> 00:03:49,060
{\an8}聂鲁达  智利当代著名诗人

98
00:03:49,060 --> 00:03:50,990
<i>最喜欢的电影是《捉鬼敢死队》</i>
<i>favorite movie Ghostbusters,</i>

99
00:03:50,990 --> 00:03:52,840
<i>而且不讨厌克利夫兰</i>
<i>and she didn't hate Cleveland.</i>

100
00:03:52,840 --> 00:03:54,910
<i>她简直太完美了</i>
<i>She's perfect.</i>

101
00:03:55,150 --> 00:03:56,590
<i>于是我给她发了封邮件</i>
<i>So I sent her an email,</i>

102
00:03:56,590 --> 00:03:59,910
<i>邀请她去打迷你高尔夫</i>
<i>inviting her to mini golf.</i>

103
00:04:05,070 --> 00:04:06,870
-喂  -迷你高尔夫
- Hello. - Mini golf?

104
00:04:06,870 --> 00:04:08,990
谁第一次约会去打迷你高尔夫啊
Who takes a first date to mini golf?

105
00:04:08,990 --> 00:04:10,580
我现在过去
I'm coming over!

106
00:04:10,980 --> 00:04:13,620
泰德  泰德  泰迪小德德
Oh, Ted-Ted-Ted- Teddy-Ted-Ted.

107
00:04:13,620 --> 00:04:14,420
谁让你进来的
Who buzzed you in?

108
00:04:14,420 --> 00:04:16,300
你真以为你玩网络交友时
Did you really think you could start dating online,

109
00:04:16,310 --> 00:04:17,690
我会不知道吗
and I wouldn't find out?

110
00:04:17,690 --> 00:04:20,590
可这个女孩  她是...
But with thi-this girl, sh-she was...

111
00:04:20,590 --> 00:04:22,850
我  她就是我  泰德
Me. She was me, Ted.

112
00:04:22,850 --> 00:04:25,570
照片就是随便找了个你没见过的
The photo was just of some girl I knew you'd never seen before,

113
00:04:25,570 --> 00:04:28,440
娱乐体育电视网的知名体育主播
a very famous sports anchor on ESPN.

114
00:04:29,030 --> 00:04:31,960
巴尼  我不用你在网上帮我找女人
Barney, I don't need you to help me find a girl online.

115
00:04:31,960 --> 00:04:34,430
当然  因为我已经找完了
Exactly because I've already done it!

116
00:04:34,440 --> 00:04:35,830
而且是3个
Three girls in fact.

117
00:04:35,830 --> 00:04:37,690
我地毯式搜索了所有交友网站
I scoured the dating sites

118
00:04:37,690 --> 00:04:40,200
用了自己写的对数函数
using my own personal logarithms,

119
00:04:40,200 --> 00:04:42,500
考虑了各种变量因素
factoring in a broad spectrum of variables,

120
00:04:42,500 --> 00:04:45,150
过滤掉不合标准的高风险对象
filtering out undesirable high-risk negatives,

121
00:04:45,150 --> 00:04:47,570
同时保证83%的成功率...
guaranteeing a success rate of 83...

122
00:04:47,570 --> 00:04:50,020
谁的胸部露得最多  你就选谁
You picked the girls that showed the most boob.

123
00:04:50,020 --> 00:04:52,620
我的方法可是百试百灵
My methods get results.

124
00:04:52,760 --> 00:04:54,540
你跟这3个妞出去约会
Go out with these three girls,

125
00:04:54,540 --> 00:04:56,670
我保证你的口味焕然一新
and your palate is going to be so cleansed,

126
00:04:56,670 --> 00:04:58,570
崭新锃亮到能看见自己的倒影
you will see your reflection in it.

127
00:04:58,570 --> 00:04:59,690
到时候
And when you do,

128
00:04:59,690 --> 00:05:00,800
好好打理下你的头发
you can fix the hair,

129
00:05:00,800 --> 00:05:02,950
因为...你最近有照过镜子吗
because... Have you seen yourself?

130
00:05:03,380 --> 00:05:04,820
没有  不过我最近倒是见过
No, but you know what I have seen,

131
00:05:04,820 --> 00:05:06,810
你脱衣舞女女友的咪咪哟
your stripper girlfriend's cans.

132
00:05:08,840 --> 00:05:11,010
这玩笑开得有点过了  对吧
That was going way too far, wasn't it?

133
00:05:11,290 --> 00:05:12,510
对不起
I'm sorry.

134
00:05:12,520 --> 00:05:13,970
来个慰问击掌吧
My condolences.

135
00:05:18,550 --> 00:05:22,200
靠  马修因为宝宝的到来神经紧张
Man, Marshall's really stressing out about this baby.

136
00:05:22,210 --> 00:05:23,700
他读各种孕妇书
He's reading every book,

137
00:05:23,700 --> 00:05:26,400
看哺乳记录片
watching breast-feeding documentaries.

138
00:05:26,400 --> 00:05:29,620
某天早上我醒来  他把我裹的像个婴儿
I woke up the other day, he had swaddled me.

139
00:05:29,960 --> 00:05:32,560
虽然那确实是几个月来  我睡的最香的一觉
Sure, it was the best night's sleep I had had in months,

140
00:05:32,560 --> 00:05:33,670
但还是...
but still...

141
00:05:33,870 --> 00:05:35,950
你知道他现在又搞什么吗
You know what his latest thing is?

142
00:05:38,860 --> 00:05:40,830
什么鬼东西在响
What the hell is that?

143
00:05:46,970 --> 00:05:48,600
马修  你搞什么啊
Marshall, what is that?

144
00:05:48,600 --> 00:05:51,550
我定了闹铃  每3小时响一次
I rigged this alarm to go off every three hours.

145
00:05:51,560 --> 00:05:53,250
我要把生物钟调整到
I'm training myself for the

146
00:05:53,260 --> 00:05:55,840
新生儿父母的不规则睡觉模式
sporadic sleep patterns of early parenthood.

147
00:05:55,840 --> 00:05:57,060
你不介意的话
Now, if you'll excuse me,

148
00:05:57,070 --> 00:05:59,990
我要哄我的演练宝宝睡觉了
I have a practice-baby to soothe.

149
00:06:03,390 --> 00:06:04,530
你得跟他谈谈
You got to talk to him.

150
00:06:04,530 --> 00:06:06,910
好吧  我晚上跟他说
Yeah, I'll talk to him tonight.

151
00:06:07,160 --> 00:06:08,470
还是明早再说吧
Maybe tomorrow morning.

152
00:06:08,470 --> 00:06:10,400
-还想再被裹一晚吗  -真的睡得好香
- One last swaddle? - It's just so cozy.

153
00:06:10,400 --> 00:06:12,640
感觉像睡在热乎乎的墨西哥卷饼里
It's like sleeping in a warm burrito.

154
00:06:13,380 --> 00:06:15,190
<i>与此同时  巴尼准备面对</i>
<i>Meanwhile, Barney was about to have</i>

155
00:06:15,190 --> 00:06:17,480
<i>脱衣舞女男友的最糟的噩梦</i>
<i>a stripper's boyfriend's worst nightmare.</i>

156
00:06:17,480 --> 00:06:18,540
卡玛
Karma?

157
00:06:18,540 --> 00:06:19,890
天啊  你的腿没绕到脖子后面
Oh, my gosh, I didn't recognize you

158
00:06:19,900 --> 00:06:21,350
我都没认出来是你
without your legs behind your head.

159
00:06:21,680 --> 00:06:23,650
达瑞尔  你没穿那件难看的风衣
Darryl, I didn't recognize you

160
00:06:23,650 --> 00:06:25,160
我也没认出来是你
without your creepy trench coat.

161
00:06:25,160 --> 00:06:25,950
你怎么样
How are you?

162
00:06:25,950 --> 00:06:28,170
-挺好的  你明天上班吗  -你知道的
- Great, you working tomorrow? - You know it.

163
00:06:28,170 --> 00:06:29,830
那就好  明天我一定穿戴好装备去
Great. I'll be there with bells on.

164
00:06:29,830 --> 00:06:32,310
装备就是超薄运动裤
And by bells, I mean super thin sweatpants.

165
00:06:33,500 --> 00:06:34,800
真恶心
Gross.

166
00:06:35,130 --> 00:06:37,260
他这个人其实挺好的
He's actually a nice guy.

167
00:06:37,260 --> 00:06:38,780
虽然当副市长很忙
he's so busy as deputy mayor,

168
00:06:38,780 --> 00:06:40,750
但总记得在我生日送卡片
but I always get a card on my birthday.

169
00:06:41,290 --> 00:06:44,330
昆茵  我爱你是个脱衣舞女
Quinn, I love the fact that you're a stripper,

170
00:06:44,330 --> 00:06:46,780
但同时  我又很你是个脱衣舞女
but I hate the fact that you're a stripper.

171
00:06:46,940 --> 00:06:49,540
巴尼  我喜欢我的工作
Barney, I like my job.

172
00:06:49,540 --> 00:06:51,670
我不需要被谁拯救
And I do not need to be rescued.

173
00:06:51,670 --> 00:06:54,470
所以  别当我的英雄
So, don't be that guy.

174
00:06:54,470 --> 00:06:55,910
你说得对  你说得对
You're right, you're right.

175
00:06:55,910 --> 00:06:58,540
我明白  当我没说过
I got it. Forget I said anything.

176
00:06:59,390 --> 00:07:00,640
晚上去捧你的场  卡玛
I'll see you tonight, Karma.

177
00:07:00,640 --> 00:07:01,960
没问题  淫贱拉里
You got it, Dirty Larry.

178
00:07:01,960 --> 00:07:03,630
你必须辞了这个工作
You have to quit your job!

179
00:07:04,880 --> 00:07:08,090
<i>那晚  我和巴尼挑的第一个女孩约会</i>
<i>That night, I went out with the first girl Barnrn picked for me.</i>

180
00:07:08,090 --> 00:07:09,670
<i>只是有个问题</i>
<i>There was just one problem.</i>

181
00:07:09,670 --> 00:07:11,400
你叫罗宾
Your name is Robin?

182
00:07:11,400 --> 00:07:13,570
对  后鼻音
Yeah, with a Y.

183
00:07:14,010 --> 00:07:16,040
是朗宾啊
Oh, Yobin.

184
00:07:16,040 --> 00:07:18,020
不  是罗冰
No, Robyn.

185
00:07:18,020 --> 00:07:20,770
我的网上资料写着"威士忌与枪支"
I go by scotch and gun lover in my online profile,

186
00:07:20,770 --> 00:07:22,740
那是因为我最喜欢这两样东西
'cause those are my two favorite things.

187
00:07:22,740 --> 00:07:26,140
还有就是加拿大  我的家乡和祖国
Well, next to Canada, my home and native land.

188
00:07:26,720 --> 00:07:29,210
加拿大
Oh. Canada.

189
00:07:29,210 --> 00:07:30,790
<i>就这样</i>
<i>And just like that,</i>

190
00:07:30,890 --> 00:07:33,410
<i>罗冰成了罗宾</i>
<i>Robyn became Robin.</i>

191
00:07:33,410 --> 00:07:34,990
近来好吗  泰德
How's it going, Ted?

192
00:07:39,460 --> 00:07:40,650
太好了
Oh, good.

193
00:07:40,650 --> 00:07:43,200
瞧  你老妈舍得从酒吧回来了
Hey, look, mommy's back from the bar!

194
00:07:43,390 --> 00:07:45,680
老爸终于可以去洗澡了
Now I can finally take a shower.

195
00:07:48,160 --> 00:07:49,510
这尿布真臭
This diaper smells.

196
00:07:49,510 --> 00:07:51,120
别告诉我怎么弄的
I don't want to know.

197
00:07:51,520 --> 00:07:52,780
好了  马修
Okay, Marshall,

198
00:07:52,780 --> 00:07:54,980
快坐下  我们得谈谈
sit down; we need to talk.

199
00:07:57,560 --> 00:07:59,440
听着  我知道你也是一片好心
Look, I know you mean well,

200
00:07:59,440 --> 00:08:01,980
可我们离预产期还有五周
but we have five weeks till the due date.

201
00:08:01,980 --> 00:08:04,880
我们不能利用这段时间放松下吗
Can't we use this time to just relax?

202
00:08:04,880 --> 00:08:06,810
等宝宝出生后
We'll figure out how all this stuff

203
00:08:06,810 --> 00:08:08,740
这些事情自然就懂了嘛
works after the baby comes.

204
00:08:08,740 --> 00:08:10,180
等宝宝出生后
After the baby comes?

205
00:08:10,180 --> 00:08:12,000
对  我们可以边做边学
Yeah, we'll learn on the job.

206
00:08:12,000 --> 00:08:14,570
边做边...真逗
Learn on the j... Huh.

207
00:08:14,880 --> 00:08:16,440
莉莉
Wow, you know, Lily,

208
00:08:16,450 --> 00:08:17,330
或许现在的燃眉之急
maybe the crisis here

209
00:08:17,330 --> 00:08:19,350
不是我没准备好当爹
isn't that I'm not ready to be a dad;

210
00:08:19,350 --> 00:08:21,500
而是你没准备好当妈
maybe it's that you're not ready to be a mom!

211
00:08:21,500 --> 00:08:22,550
-你说什么  -对
- Excuse me?! - Yeah.

212
00:08:22,550 --> 00:08:24,340
<i>就这样  他俩吵了起来</i>
<i>With that, an argument began,</i>

213
00:08:24,340 --> 00:08:27,220
<i>个中细节至今仍存在很大的争议</i>
<i>the details of which are still hotly debated to this day.</i>

214
00:08:27,220 --> 00:08:29,710
<i>比如说  马修叔叔发誓说绝没说过这句</i>
<i>For instance, Uncle Marshall swears he never said:</i>

215
00:08:29,710 --> 00:08:32,840
-我是唯一为这孩子做出牺牲的人  -什么
- I'm the only one making sacrifices for this baby! - What?!

216
00:08:32,840 --> 00:08:34,920
<i>同时他也声称自己所说  句句属实</i>
<i>And he claims he never actually altered the words:</i>

217
00:08:34,920 --> 00:08:36,940
你就像连自己怀孕了都不知道一样
It's like you don't even know that you're pregnant!

218
00:08:36,940 --> 00:08:39,370
<i>同时  莉莉坚称这一段被夸大其词</i>
<i>While Lily insists this part was exaggerated:</i>

219
00:08:39,370 --> 00:08:40,450
宝宝很好弄
Baby's are easy;

220
00:08:40,460 --> 00:08:43,580
只要看着他们卖萌  然后喂意大利面就好了
you just watch them be cute and feed them spaghetti!

221
00:08:43,590 --> 00:08:46,210
<i>不过大家都对收场意见一致</i>
<i>But everyone agrees this is how the argument ended:</i>

222
00:08:46,210 --> 00:08:48,830
马修  我要的不过是一点点清静
Marshall, what I need now is some peace, some quiet,

223
00:08:48,830 --> 00:08:50,790
不过现在我要的是  吃点意大利面
and now that it's out there, some spaghetti.

224
00:08:50,790 --> 00:08:53,640
帮忙拉我起来  好让我夺门而出
Now, please help me off the couch so I can storm out.

225
00:09:00,840 --> 00:09:03,410
<i>第二天  我告诉巴尼我的约会经过</i>
<i>The next day, I filled Barney in on my date.</i>

226
00:09:03,410 --> 00:09:05,790
朗宾
Oh, Yobin.

227
00:09:05,820 --> 00:09:07,680
不  是罗冰
No, Robyn.

228
00:09:07,690 --> 00:09:09,070
而之后的整晚
And for the rest of the night,

229
00:09:09,070 --> 00:09:12,220
只要我一看她  就会想到罗宾
every time I looked at her, I just saw Robin's face.

230
00:09:12,220 --> 00:09:14,990
-那是应该的啊  -不  是我们的罗宾
- Well, I should hope so. - No, our Robin.

231
00:09:14,990 --> 00:09:16,130
有个I[眼睛]
Robin with an I.

232
00:09:14,990 --> 00:09:18,590
{\an8}I和eye[眼睛]同音

233
00:09:16,130 --> 00:09:18,590
我们的罗宾有两只眼睛  朋友
Uh, our Robin has two eyes, my friend.

234
00:09:18,590 --> 00:09:20,540
不过也不错  你已经开始忘记她的长相了
But that's good. You're forgetting what she looks like.

235
00:09:21,430 --> 00:09:23,940
我理解  这过程一定很艰难
I'm sorry, that must have been tough.

236
00:09:23,940 --> 00:09:26,330
如果有人能感同身受  那一定是我
If anyone knows what that feels like, it's me.

237
00:09:26,590 --> 00:09:28,240
请接受我的慰问
My condolence.

238
00:09:31,910 --> 00:09:33,650
好了  向前看吧
Okay. Moving on.

239
00:09:33,650 --> 00:09:36,500
下一个女孩  味道大不同
The next girl: perfect palate cleanser.

240
00:09:36,510 --> 00:09:38,020
和罗宾完全不同
Nothing like Robin.

241
00:09:38,020 --> 00:09:39,300
怎么个不同
How nothing?

242
00:09:39,310 --> 00:09:41,870
我放眼望向世界
I gaze out into the world and all I see

243
00:09:41,880 --> 00:09:45,440
只看到葬送梦想的冰冷之地
is an icy place where dreams die.

244
00:09:47,380 --> 00:09:49,570
哇  千层面
Ooh, lasagna.

245
00:09:49,920 --> 00:09:51,240
近来好吗  泰德
How's it going, Ted?

246
00:09:51,690 --> 00:09:53,870
什么  不  怎么会这样
What? No. What? Wh-Why?

247
00:09:53,870 --> 00:09:55,800
记得吗  我有次做了千层面
Remember, I made lasagna that one time.

248
00:09:55,800 --> 00:09:57,090
这样你就来啦
That's all it takes?

249
00:09:57,100 --> 00:09:59,780
那都算不上千层面  你是往做坏的犹太面上
It wasn't even lasagna; you took your botched kugle

250
00:09:59,780 --> 00:10:01,310
倒了番茄酱
and poured tomato sauce on it.

251
00:10:01,310 --> 00:10:03,490
我可没说那千层面做得好
I didn't say it was good lasagna.

252
00:10:03,940 --> 00:10:06,470
对了  你没事干嘛勾搭这种女的呢
By the way, what are you doing with this girl?

253
00:10:06,470 --> 00:10:09,450
手臂上满是纹身  而且...
With tattoos all up and down her arms and...

254
00:10:09,450 --> 00:10:10,740
其他地方也不放过
everywhere else.

255
00:10:10,740 --> 00:10:13,340
瞧啊  我的妈呀
Hello... good gravy.

256
00:10:13,340 --> 00:10:15,540
那条龙尾巴是不是一直延伸到她的...
Does that dragons tail go all the way down to her...

257
00:10:15,540 --> 00:10:17,880
没错  我猜对了
Ohh, yes, it does.

258
00:10:18,370 --> 00:10:20,110
你还想我怎么样  罗宾
Well, what do you want me to do, Robin?

259
00:10:20,110 --> 00:10:21,800
我总得设法忘掉你
I have to get over you somehow,

260
00:10:21,800 --> 00:10:23,730
而且如果非得这样...
and if this is what it takes...

261
00:10:23,950 --> 00:10:25,590
你没事吧
Are you okay?

262
00:10:26,660 --> 00:10:28,150
没事  怎么了
Yeah. Why?

263
00:10:28,410 --> 00:10:30,590
你有点魂不守舍
You kind of spaced out there.

264
00:10:31,740 --> 00:10:33,090
怪胎
Weirdo.

265
00:10:34,120 --> 00:10:35,510
"所以  总的来说
"So, in summation,

266
00:10:35,510 --> 00:10:37,260
我非常非常抱歉"
I'm very, very sorry."

267
00:10:37,260 --> 00:10:39,460
"我猜我只是太想独占你
"I guess I just wanted you all to myself,

268
00:10:39,460 --> 00:10:41,740
而我想到这些怪人打量你的..."
and then I thought of all the creepy guys groping at your..."

269
00:10:41,740 --> 00:10:43,220
"好吧  我又要生气了
"Okay, I'm getting mad again,

270
00:10:43,220 --> 00:10:44,550
所以我在此搁笔了"
so I'm going to stop writing now."

271
00:10:44,550 --> 00:10:48,290
"请享用这些巧克力  可能含花生[鸡鸡]哟"
"Please enjoy these chocolates, may contain peanuts."

272
00:10:44,550 --> 00:10:48,290
{\an8}peanuts与penis谐音

273
00:10:48,400 --> 00:10:49,640
亲一个就和好吧
Kiss and make up?

274
00:10:52,610 --> 00:10:54,680
在窗前打一炮就和好吧
Have sex up against the window and make up?

275
00:10:55,380 --> 00:10:57,430
你这里风景还真不错
You do have a great view.

276
00:10:57,890 --> 00:10:59,660
你这么说还真有意思
Well, funny you should mention that.

277
00:10:59,760 --> 00:11:01,100
因为这是你的风景
It's your view.

278
00:11:01,510 --> 00:11:02,800
兄台  再说一次
Come again for Big Fudge?

279
00:11:02,800 --> 00:11:05,150
恭喜你  你被录用了
Congratulations. You're hired.

280
00:11:05,150 --> 00:11:06,980
你是巨人国家银行
You are Goliath National Bank's

281
00:11:06,980 --> 00:11:09,990
新任执行战略协调员
newest executive strategy coordinator.

282
00:11:10,230 --> 00:11:12,860
执行战略协调员是什么啊
What is an executive strategy coordinator?

283
00:11:12,860 --> 00:11:14,820
是几个感觉跟企业有关的词
It's three corporate-sounding words

284
00:11:14,820 --> 00:11:17,210
合起来造就的一个假职位
which, when added together, equal a fake job

285
00:11:17,210 --> 00:11:19,510
但你可以得到一份实打实的薪水
for which you get a real paycheck

286
00:11:19,510 --> 00:11:21,930
和你做脱衣舞娘赚的钱一样多呢
in the amount of exactly what you'd make stripping.

287
00:11:21,930 --> 00:11:23,980
还有牙科保险  不客气
Plus dental. You're welcs.

288
00:11:24,130 --> 00:11:26,350
现在该靠窗打炮了...
Now, about that up-against-the-window sex...

289
00:11:26,350 --> 00:11:28,150
兄台  我不想在银行工作
Dude, I don't want to work for a bank.

290
00:11:28,150 --> 00:11:28,900
为什么
Why not?

291
00:11:28,900 --> 00:11:30,830
因为我不是无下限的
Because I have standards.

292
00:11:30,830 --> 00:11:32,440
你们这些人就是妓女
You people are whores.

293
00:11:32,450 --> 00:11:34,400
为了钱  任人摆布
The things you're willing to do just for some money,

294
00:11:34,410 --> 00:11:35,940
不知廉耻
it's shameful.

295
00:11:35,940 --> 00:11:38,290
你可是在脱衣舞厅工作呢
You work in a strip club.

296
00:11:38,290 --> 00:11:40,490
对  我喜欢我的工作
Yeah, and I like it.

297
00:11:40,490 --> 00:11:41,970
而且我是行内高手
And I'm good at it.

298
00:11:41,970 --> 00:11:42,790
巴尼
Barney,

299
00:11:42,790 --> 00:11:45,690
如果我接受这份工作  那我就成了你的人
if I took this job, you would own me.

300
00:11:45,690 --> 00:11:47,670
我将得乖乖步入牢笼
I would be willingly stepping into a cage,

301
00:11:47,670 --> 00:11:49,480
这不是我想要的生活
which is something I don't do.

302
00:11:49,480 --> 00:11:50,390
除了周四
Except on Thursdays,

303
00:11:50,390 --> 00:11:51,950
"情欲小野猫"的牢笼夜
when it's cage night at the Lusty Leopard,

304
00:11:51,950 --> 00:11:53,140
可那是个纸板箱牢笼
but that's a cardboard cage,

305
00:11:53,140 --> 00:11:55,260
我随时都可以出笼
and I can get out of it any time I want.

306
00:11:55,260 --> 00:11:56,610
是吗
You can?

307
00:11:56,630 --> 00:11:58,810
牢笼夜的惊险都被你拆穿了
Wow, thanks for ruining cage night.

308
00:11:59,140 --> 00:12:00,450
-别这样  昆茵  -不
- Come on, Quinn. - No.

309
00:12:00,450 --> 00:12:01,440
-我不会...  -不
- I wouldn't... - Nope.

310
00:12:01,440 --> 00:12:02,890
别说了
Don't.

311
00:12:03,580 --> 00:12:05,910
我想要回去好好想想
I think I have some thinking to do.

312
00:12:07,060 --> 00:12:08,300
我...
I...

313
00:12:08,800 --> 00:12:09,870
斯丁森先生
Mr. Stinson?

314
00:12:09,870 --> 00:12:11,930
现在我是不是不用离职了
Does this mean I get to keep my job?

315
00:12:12,090 --> 00:12:13,980
对  赫姆  你可以留下
Yeah, Herm, you can stay.

316
00:12:15,160 --> 00:12:16,240
宝贝  听着
Hey, baby, listen.

317
00:12:16,240 --> 00:12:18,030
我很抱歉  我刚才太激动了
I'm-I'm sorry I flipped out.

318
00:12:18,030 --> 00:12:19,330
没关系
Oh, that's okay.

319
00:12:19,770 --> 00:12:22,320
说实在的  或许错在我
To be fair, maybe I'm at fault

320
00:12:22,330 --> 00:12:23,650
太爱我们的孩子了
for loving our child too much,

321
00:12:23,660 --> 00:12:25,850
尽管这就是为人父母的定义  所以...
although that is the definition of parenting, so...

322
00:12:25,850 --> 00:12:27,350
好吧  算和好了吧
All right, good make up.

323
00:12:27,360 --> 00:12:28,890
听着  我刚才上网
Hey, listen, I went online,

324
00:12:28,890 --> 00:12:31,020
发现了一个"宝宝训练营"
and I found this Baby Boot Camp thing

325
00:12:31,020 --> 00:12:33,630
这周末会在帕拉默斯的一家酒店举办培训
that they're doing at a hotel in Paramus this weekend.

326
00:12:33,630 --> 00:12:35,100
"宝宝训练营"
Baby Boot Camp?

327
00:12:35,100 --> 00:12:36,100
听起来不错
That sounds great.

328
00:12:36,110 --> 00:12:37,170
是啊  这是个两天的项目
Yeah, it's a two-day event...

329
00:12:37,170 --> 00:12:37,980
我们要去
We're going.

330
00:12:37,980 --> 00:12:40,360
...还有很多研讨会和课程
...and there's lots of seminars and classes.

331
00:12:40,370 --> 00:12:41,630
咱们一定要参加
You've already made the sale.

332
00:12:41,630 --> 00:12:42,880
我已经给我们俩报了名
Anyway, I signed us up.

333
00:12:42,880 --> 00:12:45,010
完全听不进去  我的心已经开始打包行李了
Not even listening anymore; mentally packing.

334
00:12:45,010 --> 00:12:46,770
我在想绕过收费口去帕拉默斯的
I'm trying to figure out the best way to get to Paramus

335
00:12:46,770 --> 00:12:47,900
最佳路线
without hitting any tolls.

336
00:12:47,900 --> 00:12:49,580
这训练营一定很棒
This is gonna be great.

337
00:12:50,920 --> 00:12:52,470
那就是我最后一次
And that was the last time

338
00:12:52,470 --> 00:12:55,340
和留胡子的人约会
I'll ever go out with a guy with a mustache.

339
00:12:56,870 --> 00:12:57,730
这次不错
This is good.

340
00:12:57,730 --> 00:13:00,200
不错  我没在想那个谁
This is nice, not thinking about you-know-who.

341
00:13:00,200 --> 00:13:01,960
只陶醉其中
Just having a good time

342
00:13:02,030 --> 00:13:04,630
感谢上帝  我没留胡子
and thanking God I didn't grow that mustache.

343
00:13:04,640 --> 00:13:05,800
而你
And you,

344
00:13:05,800 --> 00:13:07,820
你真有礼貌
you're so polite.

345
00:13:07,820 --> 00:13:11,740
我的前未婚夫  韦恩  他一点礼貌都没
My ex-fiancé, Wayne, he had no manners.

346
00:13:11,750 --> 00:13:13,370
韦恩没礼貌
Wayne had no manners.

347
00:13:13,370 --> 00:13:15,280
韦恩...礼貌...
Wayne... manners...

348
00:13:15,280 --> 00:13:18,390
韦恩庄园  布鲁斯·韦恩的家
Wayne Manor, home of Bruce Wayne,

349
00:13:18,390 --> 00:13:20,120
他以饰演蜘蛛侠而闻名
better known as Batman,

350
00:13:20,120 --> 00:13:22,760
迪克·格雷森的导师  韦恩的养子迪克
mentor to Dick Grayson, his orphan ward

351
00:13:22,760 --> 00:13:24,810
在夜晚会在穿上"神奇小子"彩色制服
who at night would don the colorful vestments

352
00:13:24,810 --> 00:13:27,210
人们又叫他为
of the Boy Wonder, aka...

353
00:13:27,680 --> 00:13:28,820
"罗宾"
Robin.

354
00:13:28,820 --> 00:13:31,810
你喝一口饮料能编这么多啊  泰德
Holy long walk for a short drink of water, Ted.

355
00:13:31,810 --> 00:13:32,580
闭嘴
Stop this.

356
00:13:32,580 --> 00:13:34,990
我要你离开我的世界
I need you out of my life for real.

357
00:13:34,990 --> 00:13:36,260
-你才不要呢  -我就要
- You don't mean that. - Yes, I do.

358
00:13:36,260 --> 00:13:37,450
不  你不要
No, you don't.

359
00:13:37,450 --> 00:13:39,340
泰德  今非昔比啊
Look how much is changing right now.

360
00:13:39,340 --> 00:13:41,810
马修和莉莉快生孩子了
Marshall and Lily are having a baby.

361
00:13:41,810 --> 00:13:43,510
巴尼和一个女人同居了
Barney's shacking up with a girl.

362
00:13:43,510 --> 00:13:45,830
你的整个世界  发生了翻天覆地的变化
With your whole world turning upside down,

363
00:13:45,830 --> 00:13:47,180
你难道不想死死守住
isn't a friendship like this one

364
00:13:47,180 --> 00:13:50,910
我们这样的一段友谊吗
something you want to hold on to as tightly as possible?

365
00:13:52,870 --> 00:13:55,580
每看你一眼  我的心就多痛一分
And every time I look at you, it hurts.

366
00:13:55,950 --> 00:13:59,500
这就是我唯一一次的当拉拉的经历
...and that's the story of my only lesbian experience.

367
00:13:59,800 --> 00:14:02,540
抱歉  细节部分说太多了
I'm sorry for going into so much detail.

368
00:14:02,550 --> 00:14:04,680
我以后再也不讲这事了
I'll never tell that story again.

369
00:14:04,850 --> 00:14:06,600
对了  饭菜还合胃口吗
Anyway, how's your meal?

370
00:14:06,660 --> 00:14:08,660
霍莉  听我说  或许我该坦白
Holly, listen, I should probably tell you,

371
00:14:08,660 --> 00:14:12,530
其实  我对某人仍余情未了
um, I'm kind of getting over someone right now.

372
00:14:13,070 --> 00:14:15,370
很高兴听到你这么说
I am so glad you said that.

373
00:14:15,580 --> 00:14:17,820
我对韦恩也还念念不忘
I guess I'm still getting over Wayne.

374
00:14:17,900 --> 00:14:19,900
要走出一段感情实在太难
It's been really hard.

375
00:14:20,530 --> 00:14:22,180
两位要来份果汁冰糕吗
Can I interest you in some sorbet?

376
00:14:22,180 --> 00:14:24,960
你俩看起来都该"换换口味"了
You two look like you could both use a palate cleanser.

377
00:14:30,630 --> 00:14:32,590
我这顿饭菜合你胃口吗  泰德
How's your palate, Ted?

378
00:14:32,910 --> 00:14:34,500
焕然一新
Pretty cleansed.

379
00:14:38,210 --> 00:14:39,360
在研讨会上
You know, at this seminar,

380
00:14:39,360 --> 00:14:42,820
将会有某位自许"育儿专家"的人
there's gonna be the one guy who's, like, Mr. Parenting Expert,

381
00:14:42,820 --> 00:14:46,180
时不时用自己的"重要观点"  打断讲师的话
keeps interrupting the speakers with his own "important facts."

382
00:14:46,180 --> 00:14:48,260
而那个人  就坐在你旁边
And you're gonna be sitting right next to him,

383
00:14:48,270 --> 00:14:50,410
准备大开眼界吧
so get ready for that.

384
00:14:50,570 --> 00:14:53,520
亲爱的  你最近有点睡眠不足
Baby, you've been a little sleep deprived lately.

385
00:14:53,520 --> 00:14:54,890
不如让我开车吧
Why don't you let me drive?

386
00:14:54,900 --> 00:14:58,180
这个主意倒是不坏
You know what, that's not such a bad idea.

387
00:14:58,190 --> 00:15:00,870
可我们都不希望看到
I mean, the last thing we want is

388
00:15:00,870 --> 00:15:04,150
我一坐上驾驶座就...
for me to get behind the wheel and just...

389
00:15:13,070 --> 00:15:15,800
亲爱的  你可真香
Oh, baby, you smell good.

390
00:15:16,620 --> 00:15:18,100
等我们到了酒店
When we get to that hotel,

391
00:15:18,100 --> 00:15:21,400
我要与你颠鸾倒凤  缠绵不休
I'm gonna wear your pregnant belly like a hat.

392
00:15:21,650 --> 00:15:24,010
那你可得先把我灌醉哟
You'll have to buy me a couple of cocktails first.

393
00:15:24,010 --> 00:15:25,500
巴  巴尼
Bar-Barney!

394
00:15:25,510 --> 00:15:26,660
我们这是在哪儿
Where are we?

395
00:15:26,660 --> 00:15:29,800
大西洋城啊  宝贝
Atlantic City, baby!

396
00:15:30,070 --> 00:15:31,860
其实还有14英里才到
Well, in 14 miles.

397
00:15:36,520 --> 00:15:38,480
这到底是怎么回事
What the hell is going on?

398
00:15:38,480 --> 00:15:39,900
莉莉人呢
And where is Lily?

399
00:15:39,900 --> 00:15:42,720
你对我的"演练宝宝"做了什么
And what did you do to the practice baby?

400
00:15:43,050 --> 00:15:44,920
宝宝还有剩吗
And is there any left?

401
00:15:46,090 --> 00:15:47,330
莉莉很担心你
Lily was worried about you.

402
00:15:47,330 --> 00:15:49,930
她认为你该放松一下  所以...
She thought you needed to unwind, so...

403
00:15:50,150 --> 00:15:52,910
我们都不希望看到
I mean, the last thing we want is for me to

404
00:15:52,910 --> 00:15:56,040
我一坐上驾驶座就...
get behind the wheel and just...

405
00:16:00,040 --> 00:16:01,870
她在棕榈泉订了两间豪华套房
She made reservations for two deluxe rooms,

406
00:16:01,870 --> 00:16:03,430
按摩  还有晚餐
massages, and dinner at the Palm,

407
00:16:03,440 --> 00:16:06,230
作为交换  我烤了饼干给她
and in return, I made her cookies.

408
00:16:09,120 --> 00:16:12,250
所以华尔道夫酒店的宝宝预热营是假的咯
So, there's no Baby Boot Camp at the Paramus Waldorf?

409
00:16:13,520 --> 00:16:15,810
话说帕拉默斯有华尔道夫酒店吗
Is there even a Paramus Waldorf?

410
00:16:16,010 --> 00:16:17,180
老弟
Bro...

411
00:16:17,180 --> 00:16:19,260
莉莉这是要气死我呀
I am so mad at Lily right now.

412
00:16:19,260 --> 00:16:20,240
她早料到你会这样
She knew you would be;

413
00:16:20,240 --> 00:16:23,030
所以她准备了这个
that's why she packed this.

414
00:16:26,120 --> 00:16:28,070
我的"气死莉莉"T恤
My Mad-at-Lily shirt.

415
00:16:28,720 --> 00:16:30,170
这是我为我的
I had this made for me

416
00:16:30,170 --> 00:16:32,430
高中女友史戴芙专门订做的衣服
and my high school girlfriend, Steph.

417
00:16:32,430 --> 00:16:34,710
实际上  "马修和史戴芙  天长地久"
In reality, "Marshall and Steph 4-eva"

418
00:16:34,710 --> 00:16:35,800
结果却成了
turned out to be

419
00:16:35,800 --> 00:16:37,430
"马修和史戴芙  两天分手
"Marshall and Steph for two days

420
00:16:37,430 --> 00:16:40,780
因为史戴芙的男友提前一周出了少管所"
until Steph's boyfriend got out of juvie a week early."

421
00:16:41,320 --> 00:16:43,680
每次穿这个  莉莉都气得要死
Drives Lily crazy when I wear it.

422
00:16:44,210 --> 00:16:46,810
希望没了我  她孤苦凄惨
I hope she's miserable without me.

423
00:16:51,670 --> 00:16:53,460
泰德  最近如何啊
Hey, Ted, how's tricks?

424
00:16:53,460 --> 00:16:55,070
相当不错  卢
Tricks are pretty good, Lou.

425
00:16:55,070 --> 00:16:57,990
前几天遇到了点感情上的麻烦  不过
Had some girl trouble earlier in the week, but, uh,

426
00:16:57,990 --> 00:17:00,430
我感觉从今往后  事情会越来越...
I got a feeling from here on out, things are gonna be A...

427
00:17:00,430 --> 00:17:02,850
靠  你有完没完啊
O-Oh, you son of a bitch.

428
00:17:02,850 --> 00:17:04,080
你好呀
Hello.

429
00:17:07,270 --> 00:17:08,080
莉莉说得对
Lily's right.

430
00:17:08,080 --> 00:17:09,610
我最近太不正常了
I've been acting crazy.

431
00:17:09,610 --> 00:17:10,850
没关系  老弟
No, it's okay, bro.

432
00:17:10,850 --> 00:17:13,360
我是说  你最近是有点不正常
I mean, yeah, you've been a little crazy,

433
00:17:13,360 --> 00:17:14,800
可那都是因为爱
but it comes from love.

434
00:17:14,800 --> 00:17:17,070
这种不正常  就和某男愿意
It's the same kind of crazy that makes a man

435
00:17:17,070 --> 00:17:20,190
从政府援助金里拿出50万大洋
offer his stripper girlfriend over half a million dollars

436
00:17:20,190 --> 00:17:21,540
付给他的脱衣舞娘女友
of government bailout money,

437
00:17:21,540 --> 00:17:23,400
只要她别在男人的老二上蹭来蹭去一样
not to rub up on other guys' junk.

438
00:17:23,400 --> 00:17:25,040
我们都是出于善意
It's good crazy.

439
00:17:30,100 --> 00:17:31,280
希望莉莉没事
I hope Lily's okay.

440
00:17:31,280 --> 00:17:32,810
够了  老弟
Okay, you know, that's it, bro.

441
00:17:32,810 --> 00:17:34,770
我们俩都关掉手机一小时
We're both turning off our phones for one hour.

442
00:17:34,770 --> 00:17:36,140
动议被否决
Motion denied.

443
00:17:36,180 --> 00:17:38,860
好吧  你让我别无选择
Okay, you leave me no choice.

444
00:17:39,410 --> 00:17:42,780
我提议  我们关机1小时享受兄弟时间
Proposal: you give me one hour of phone-free bro time,

445
00:17:42,780 --> 00:17:45,500
在此期间我们  也就是你自己
during which we, and by we I mean you,

446
00:17:45,500 --> 00:17:48,470
来个前无古人  后无来者的酩酊大醉
get magnificently, mythologically drunk.

447
00:17:48,470 --> 00:17:52,040
我是指"醉得说话都得带字幕"的那种
I'm talking needing-subtitles- when-you-speak drunk.

448
00:17:52,040 --> 00:17:53,790
如果你能做到
If you can give me that,

449
00:17:54,290 --> 00:17:57,030
我就系上这个
I will wear this.

450
00:17:57,790 --> 00:17:58,970
小鸭领带
The ducky tie?

451
00:17:58,970 --> 00:18:00,650
我以为你早把它扔了呢
I thought you threw that thing away.

452
00:18:00,650 --> 00:18:02,000
我是扔了
I did.

453
00:18:02,190 --> 00:18:03,670
它自己回来了
It came back.

454
00:18:04,220 --> 00:18:05,630
好吧  巴尼
All right, Barney,

455
00:18:05,840 --> 00:18:07,400
你成功打动我了
you got yourself a deal.

456
00:18:10,590 --> 00:18:12,920
不好意思  小姐
Um, excuse me, miss.

457
00:18:13,030 --> 00:18:14,490
你有空的话
Um, when you get a chance,

458
00:18:14,490 --> 00:18:18,500
能请你端来100杯龙舌兰酒吗
could you bring over a hundred shots of tequila, please?

459
00:18:18,880 --> 00:18:20,390
也给我来一份
I'll have the same.

460
00:18:24,600 --> 00:18:25,800
你为什么就不能放过我呢
Why are you still here?

461
00:18:25,800 --> 00:18:27,690
你觉得呢
Why do you think I'm still here?

462
00:18:27,790 --> 00:18:30,880
我猜是因为我还爱着你吧
I guess because I'm in love with you.

463
00:18:31,040 --> 00:18:33,690
不然怎么会走到哪里  都能看到你的脸
Why else would I be seeing your face everywhere I look?

464
00:18:33,690 --> 00:18:35,470
那是因为你心里难过
Because you feel bad.

465
00:18:35,710 --> 00:18:37,760
我当然难过
Of course I feel bad.

466
00:18:37,760 --> 00:18:39,210
我告诉你  我爱你
I told you I love you,

467
00:18:39,210 --> 00:18:40,700
而显然
which is apparently

468
00:18:40,700 --> 00:18:42,710
这是最不应该说出口的一句话
the worst thing you can say to someone.

469
00:18:42,710 --> 00:18:44,610
这不是你难过的原因
That's not why you feel bad.

470
00:18:44,760 --> 00:18:46,890
你难过是因为  你说了这句话
You feel bad because after you said it,

471
00:18:46,890 --> 00:18:48,800
却还是放手让我走掉
you let me go away.

472
00:18:49,360 --> 00:18:50,780
我明白我们的关系
I know our relationship

473
00:18:50,780 --> 00:18:53,500
和你期望的不太一样
isn't exactly what you want it to be,

474
00:18:53,580 --> 00:18:56,330
我也知道  或许我不如你爱我那般深
and I know I may not love you the way you love me,

475
00:18:56,330 --> 00:18:59,660
但  我是爱你的
but I do love you.

476
00:19:00,470 --> 00:19:03,110
这难道不值得死死守住吗
Isn't that worth hanging on to?

477
00:19:09,350 --> 00:19:10,430
我好想你
I miss you.

478
00:19:10,430 --> 00:19:12,600
{\an8}金温尿牌啤酒[马修前下属生产的啤酒  参见S6E07]

479
00:19:10,820 --> 00:19:12,610
还不快去把我找回来
So go get me back.

480
00:19:20,470 --> 00:19:21,520
罗宾
Robin?

481
00:19:21,520 --> 00:19:22,450
泰德
Ted.

482
00:19:22,450 --> 00:19:23,620
能见到你真人太好了
It's good to really see you.

483
00:19:23,620 --> 00:19:25,390
我是说  能见到你真太好了
I mean, it's really good to see you.

484
00:19:25,390 --> 00:19:26,740
我们应该好好谈谈
Look, I think we need to talk.

485
00:19:26,740 --> 00:19:28,980
我也这么想  可现在不是时候
Uh, me, too, but now's not a good time.

486
00:19:28,980 --> 00:19:30,160
为什么
Why not?

487
00:19:30,330 --> 00:19:32,040
为你骄傲  老弟
I am proud of you, bro.

488
00:19:32,050 --> 00:19:34,310
你不但关机1小时
You turned off your phone for one hour,

489
00:19:34,310 --> 00:19:35,640
还喝得酩酊大醉
and you got so drunk...

490
00:19:35,640 --> 00:19:40,320
现在我说话都得挂上字幕

491
00:19:40,670 --> 00:19:42,160
要的就是这效果
Exactly.

492
00:19:42,980 --> 00:19:44,140
我说  巴尼

493
00:19:44,680 --> 00:19:45,990
干嘛  马修
Yes, Marshall?

494
00:19:46,080 --> 00:19:48,070
咱现在能把手机打开了不

495
00:19:48,700 --> 00:19:50,240
当然可以
Well, I don't see why not.

496
00:19:52,320 --> 00:19:55,600
哎哟  我有17条语音留言呢
Whoa! I've got 17 new voicemails.

497
00:19:55,870 --> 00:19:57,190
巴尼  我是莉莉
Barney, it's Lily.

498
00:19:57,190 --> 00:19:59,380
你俩最好赶紧滚回纽约
You guys need to get back to New York right away.

499
00:19:59,380 --> 00:20:00,910
我快生了
I'm in labor.

500
00:20:02,100 --> 00:20:05,480
向啤酒猛男里斯致敬
All hail Beercules!

501
00:20:02,100 --> 00:20:05,480
{\an8}马修喝醉后给自己取的外号  参见S7E2

502
00:20:05,520 --> 00:20:06,880
万岁
Yeah!

503
00:20:16,050 --> 00:20:19,420
好吧  巴尼  你成功打动我了
All right, Barney, you got yourself a deal.

504
00:20:24,230 --> 00:20:25,870
这是马修的语音信箱
Hey, you've reached Marshall.

505
00:20:25,870 --> 00:20:27,680
请留言
Please leave a message.

506
00:20:27,760 --> 00:20:29,500
亲爱的  是我
Hey, baby, it's me.

507
00:20:29,510 --> 00:20:31,300
我可能快生了
I think I'm labor.

508
00:20:32,560 --> 00:20:34,940
我们应该每周来一次
We should do this every weekend.

509
00:20:35,270 --> 00:20:36,830
这次是真的
Okay, this is real.

510
00:20:36,830 --> 00:20:38,050
不是在玩狼来了
It's not a false alarm.

511
00:20:38,050 --> 00:20:39,370
我真的要生了
This is real; I'm in labor.

512
00:20:39,370 --> 00:20:41,740
我要你赶快回我电话
I kind of need you to call me back now.

513
00:20:41,750 --> 00:20:43,880
你说你如此娇小
How does somebody so little

514
00:20:43,880 --> 00:20:46,280
手指怎么会如此有力呢
have such strong fingers?

515
00:20:46,760 --> 00:20:47,580
你在哪里
Where are you?

516
00:20:47,580 --> 00:20:48,810
回我电话
Call me!

517
00:20:48,810 --> 00:20:51,890
这位兄弟是帕拉默斯的华尔道夫酒店经理
He is the manager of the Paramus Waldorf.

518
00:20:51,890 --> 00:20:55,380
你要是来帕拉默斯玩  我们罩着你
You come to Paramus, we will hook you up.

519
00:20:55,600 --> 00:20:57,440
如果你是想要借机报复我
If you're trying to get back at me,

520
00:20:57,440 --> 00:21:01,970
那你这招可真是他妈的大错特错了
you have chosen a wildly inappropriate way of doing so!

521
00:21:02,130 --> 00:21:05,800
爽哉  美哉
Oh, yeah... Oh, yeah.

