1
00:00:01,570 --> 00:00:03,540
<i>孩子们  爱因斯坦说得对</i>
<i>kids, Einstein was right.</i>

2
00:00:03,640 --> 00:00:05,550
<i>时间的快慢是相对参考系而定</i>
<i>Time moves at different speeds.</i>

3
00:00:05,550 --> 00:00:08,120
<i>对于巴尼而言  昨晚在激情中一晃而过</i>
<i>To Barney, the previous night raced by in a blur.</i>

4
00:00:10,310 --> 00:00:12,060
<i>而后  突然间</i>
<i>But then, all of a sudden,</i>

5
00:00:12,680 --> 00:00:14,360
<i>时间在清醒中停滞了</i>
<i>time stopped.</i>

6
00:00:14,570 --> 00:00:16,770
这恐怕是我做过最坏的一次了
This might be the worst thing I've ever done.

7
00:00:16,770 --> 00:00:18,310
嘿  别这么说
Hey, now.

8
00:00:18,710 --> 00:00:20,520
虽说这不是你发挥最好的一次  但还是非常...
You weren't at the top of your game, but it was still pretty...

9
00:00:20,520 --> 00:00:22,060
我的天啊
Oh, my God!

10
00:00:22,210 --> 00:00:23,860
我居然出轨了
I just cheated on Kevin.

11
00:00:23,870 --> 00:00:27,430
凯文是史上最好的男友  我真是太差劲了
He is the nicest guy ever.I'm a terrible person.

12
00:00:27,430 --> 00:00:28,550
没关系
It's okay.

13
00:00:28,660 --> 00:00:30,080
我们都出轨了
We both cheated.

14
00:00:30,220 --> 00:00:33,120
有句俗语怎么说来着  负负得正嘛
What's that saying about two wrongs making a right?

15
00:00:33,120 --> 00:00:35,460
应该是"一失足成千古恨"吧
"Two wrongs don't make a right"?

16
00:00:35,840 --> 00:00:37,530
不  肯定不是这样的
No, that's not it.

17
00:00:37,840 --> 00:00:38,850
我的天啊
Oh, my God.

18
00:00:39,210 --> 00:00:40,500
我居然出轨了
I just cheated on Nora.

19
00:00:40,500 --> 00:00:42,520
我怎么能对诺拉做这种事呢  我们该怎么办
How could I do this to her? What are we gonna do?

20
00:00:42,520 --> 00:00:43,130
我不知道
I don't know.

21
00:00:44,550 --> 00:00:47,980
我能问你  今晚对你有意义吗
Can I ask you, did this mean anything?

22
00:00:47,980 --> 00:00:49,700
当然有啦
Of course it did.

23
00:00:49,800 --> 00:00:52,010
当然没啦
Of course it didn't.

24
00:00:52,010 --> 00:00:53,990
你到底想听哪种  两种趋势我看都行
Which one are you looking for? I could see it going either way.

25
00:00:53,990 --> 00:00:55,790
-今晚毫无意义  -毫无意义
- It meant nothing. - It meant nothing!

26
00:00:55,790 --> 00:00:57,180
你怎么能说它毫无意义呢
How could you say it meant nothing?!

27
00:00:57,190 --> 00:00:58,380
今晚当然意义重大
Of course it meant something!

28
00:00:58,380 --> 00:00:59,500
不  它没有
No, it didn't!

29
00:00:59,500 --> 00:01:01,400
它也不能  明白吗
It can't.Okay?

30
00:01:01,400 --> 00:01:04,600
你有诺拉了  我也有凯文了
You're with Nora, and I'm with Kevin and...

31
00:01:05,660 --> 00:01:06,710
我得走了
I have to go.

32
00:01:06,710 --> 00:01:08,210
慢着  我们该如何跟他们开口
Wait, what are we gonna tell them?

33
00:01:08,210 --> 00:01:09,340
绝口不提
Nothing.

34
00:01:09,340 --> 00:01:11,390
天啊  我们犯了个大错
God! We made a horrible mistake.

35
00:01:11,390 --> 00:01:12,960
但现在都结束了
But it-it is over now.

36
00:01:12,960 --> 00:01:15,330
再提这件事只会伤害他们
There's no reason to hurt more people by talking about it.

37
00:01:16,010 --> 00:01:18,300
你是叫我撒谎吗
You're asking me to lie?

38
00:01:18,730 --> 00:01:20,710
我是...无所谓啦
That's... fine.

39
00:01:20,970 --> 00:01:22,010
该死
Damn it.

40
00:01:22,010 --> 00:01:23,980
我和诺拉明晚有个公司的游轮聚会
Nora and I have that work cruise tomorrow night.

41
00:01:23,990 --> 00:01:25,580
我们都要携伴参加
We're all supposed to go together.

42
00:01:25,990 --> 00:01:29,110
好的  我知道这么想实在有点离谱
Okay, I know this is thinking way, way out of the box,

43
00:01:29,110 --> 00:01:31,060
但如果  先听我说完
but what if-- and hear me out--

44
00:01:32,150 --> 00:01:33,510
如果我们都不去呢
we don't go?

45
00:01:33,510 --> 00:01:34,640
不行
No.

46
00:01:34,810 --> 00:01:38,020
我只想让这个夜晚成为历史  所以
I just want this whole night to fade into history, so

47
00:01:38,020 --> 00:01:40,390
我们必须装得像什么都没发生一样
we have to act like it never happened.

48
00:01:40,390 --> 00:01:41,620
我们应该去
We should go.

49
00:01:41,690 --> 00:01:43,530
我是说  就在船上呆3个小时
I mean, it's a three-hour boat ride--

50
00:01:43,530 --> 00:01:45,020
这么短时间能发生什么呀
what could happen?

51
00:01:43,530 --> 00:01:45,020
{\an8}《盖里甘的岛》是CBS上世纪60年代的喜剧

52
00:01:45,020 --> 00:01:47,780
{\an8}讲述因为一个3小时的航海之旅让7个人流落荒岛的故事

53
00:01:45,810 --> 00:01:47,780
我打赌盖里甘会这么说
I'm sure that's what Gilligan said.

54
00:01:47,980 --> 00:01:50,030
YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
更多原创字幕翻译 请登陆www.YYeTs.com

55
00:01:50,030 --> 00:01:52,630
         时间轴： godwuwen 孤帆  字幕总监： YY

56
00:01:52,630 --> 00:01:55,130
翻译： 一块二  非燕  阿蘅阿蘅  猫中之王 孤帆  字幕总监： YY

57
00:01:55,130 --> 00:01:57,130
校对： YY    后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY

58
00:01:57,130 --> 00:02:00,130
老爸老妈浪漫史
第七季  第十集

59
00:02:05,690 --> 00:02:07,960
怀旧狂欢音乐会
Groovapalooza!

60
00:02:07,960 --> 00:02:12,080
囊括上世纪90年代所有自以为是的嬉皮士乐队
All the smug hippie bands from the '90s in one big concert.

61
00:02:12,080 --> 00:02:15,520
甚至门票都有一股丁香烟和庸才的味道
Ah, even the tickets smell like cloves and mediocrity.

62
00:02:13,310 --> 00:02:15,520
{\an8}嬉皮士常常与丁香烟联系在一起

63
00:02:15,520 --> 00:02:17,710
为了重回过去的美好时光
And to really take us back,

64
00:02:17,730 --> 00:02:20,630
我还特意弄来一袋  没错  就是大麻
I scored us a bag of, yes, mari...

65
00:02:20,630 --> 00:02:22,700
<i>孩子们  为了更好地感受音乐会的气氛</i>
<i>Kids, we used to do something before concerts</i>

66
00:02:22,700 --> 00:02:23,750
<i>我们会在开始前做件事</i>
<i>to enjoy them more.</i>

67
00:02:23,750 --> 00:02:27,140
<i>那就是  吃个三明治</i>
<i>And that thing was to... eat a sandwich.</i>

68
00:02:27,150 --> 00:02:29,220
加料牛肉三明治
...nated steak subs.

69
00:02:29,220 --> 00:02:30,040
哦也
Oh, yeah!

70
00:02:30,040 --> 00:02:34,540
我们快要为人父母了  三明治还是少吃为妙
Well, as future parents, we'll pass on the sandwiches.

71
00:02:34,640 --> 00:02:36,650
你怎么能提议这种事呢  泰德
How could you even suggest such a thing, Ted?!

72
00:02:36,650 --> 00:02:38,610
快把我60块还给我
I better get my 60 bucks back.

73
00:02:38,610 --> 00:02:39,800
不吃三明治吗
No sandwich?

74
00:02:39,800 --> 00:02:42,300
马修  这可是狂欢会呀
Marshall, it's a palooza.

75
00:02:42,310 --> 00:02:43,960
以前每一个狂欢会  我们都会吃三明治
We've eaten sandwiches at every palooza.

76
00:02:43,960 --> 00:02:45,960
摇滚狂欢会  爵士狂欢会
Lollapalooza, Funkapalooza...

77
00:02:45,960 --> 00:02:49,000
还有大学三年级  妇女能顶半天狂欢会
Gender-diversity-awareness- palooza, junior year.

78
00:02:49,000 --> 00:02:51,530
我记得  当时还有几个贱女人赶我呢
Yeah, there were some real bitches there.

79
00:02:52,650 --> 00:02:53,560
好了  快点
Okay, quick,

80
00:02:53,560 --> 00:02:55,780
趁莉莉没来  我们先吃掉它
before Lily gets here, let's fire this up.

81
00:02:55,780 --> 00:02:58,660
不行  我答应过莉莉要有责任心
No way. I promised Lily that I would be responsible.

82
00:02:58,660 --> 00:03:00,030
反正你的60块也要不回来了
You're not getting your 60 bucks back.

83
00:03:00,030 --> 00:03:01,020
那还是来一口吧
Give me that.

84
00:03:11,160 --> 00:03:12,390
你还好吧
Hey, how you holding up?

85
00:03:12,390 --> 00:03:14,500
我要跟你们三个困在这艘船上一整晚
Well, I'm about to be trapped on a boat all night

86
00:03:14,500 --> 00:03:16,640
我的戴绿帽的男友  我的出轨对象
with the guy I cheated on, the guy I cheated with

87
00:03:16,640 --> 00:03:19,140
我出轨对象的戴绿帽女友
and the girl that the guy I cheated with cheated on.

88
00:03:19,180 --> 00:03:21,110
所以  我一点都不好
So, not super.

89
00:03:21,110 --> 00:03:21,870
你好  桑迪
Hi, Sandy.

90
00:03:21,870 --> 00:03:23,480
不用谢
You're welcome.

91
00:03:23,660 --> 00:03:25,230
我可没跟你道谢呀
I did not say "Thank you."

92
00:03:25,240 --> 00:03:26,960
你太客气了
Oh, you're too kind.

93
00:03:26,960 --> 00:03:28,290
太客气了
Too kind.

94
00:03:28,700 --> 00:03:30,390
借过  我真该试过去
Excuse me, I should really try

95
00:03:30,390 --> 00:03:32,840
把那个新实习生搞上床
to have sex with that new intern.

96
00:03:32,840 --> 00:03:35,860
<i>罗宾的老板桑迪·里维斯  每年都要举办这个游轮会</i>
<i>Robin's boss Sandy Rivers hosted this cruise every year,</i>

97
00:03:35,860 --> 00:03:37,820
<i>主要是为了跟新员工搭讪</i>
<i>mostly to hit on the new employees.</i>

98
00:03:38,240 --> 00:03:41,170
<i>而且他还想到了一个分文不花的妙招</i>
<i>And he'd found a clever way to never spend a cent.</i>

99
00:03:41,180 --> 00:03:42,670
接下来  亚利桑那州
Up next, another four deaths

100
00:03:42,670 --> 00:03:45,430
又有4人因史上最强的热浪而致死
in Arizona's record-breaking heat wave.

101
00:03:45,810 --> 00:03:48,130
你想体验真正的史上最强热辣感吗
You want real record-breaking heat?

102
00:03:48,220 --> 00:03:52,230
来一杯克里托夫牌辣椒椰汁伏特加马丁尼酒
Try Kristoff's Jalapeno Coconut Vodka martini.

103
00:03:53,250 --> 00:03:55,570
热辣得不得了哦[西班牙语]
Muy caliente!

104
00:03:57,380 --> 00:03:59,920
好吧  诺拉和凯文随时会到
Okay, Nora and Kevin are gonna be here any minute.

105
00:04:00,280 --> 00:04:01,760
我原以为我能应付得来  但现在不行
I thought I could handle this, but I can't.

106
00:04:01,760 --> 00:04:03,460
好吧  那就按计划走吧
Okay, um, here's the plan.

107
00:04:03,470 --> 00:04:05,790
我们随便找个救生艇  逃回岸上
We'll grab one of the lifeboats, get back to shore,

108
00:04:05,790 --> 00:04:06,960
销毁我们滚床单的录像
destroy the tape of us doing it...

109
00:04:06,960 --> 00:04:08,290
你居然把过程录下来了
There's a tape of us doing it?

110
00:04:08,290 --> 00:04:10,040
然后我们开始一段新的人生
...and we'll start a new life together.

111
00:04:10,040 --> 00:04:13,170
去一个即简单又舒适的地方  比如佛蒙特州或者迪拜
Somewhere simple and homey, like Vermont or Dubai.

112
00:04:13,170 --> 00:04:15,230
等下  这是你想要的生活吗
Wait, is that what you want?

113
00:04:15,230 --> 00:04:18,000
你想跟我在一起
For us to be together?

114
00:04:18,000 --> 00:04:18,890
罗宾
Hey, Robin.

115
00:04:18,890 --> 00:04:20,390
天啊  我真的应付不来
Oh, God, I really can't do this.

116
00:04:20,390 --> 00:04:23,200
别担心  听我指挥  保持淡定
Don't worry. Just follow my lead and keep cool.

117
00:04:23,200 --> 00:04:24,420
伙计们
Hey, guys!

118
00:04:24,420 --> 00:04:25,970
他们知道了
They know!

119
00:04:27,020 --> 00:04:28,270
完了
Oh, no.

120
00:04:29,450 --> 00:04:33,910
我觉得那个三明治夹杂了其它东西
I think that sandwich was laced with other stuff.

121
00:04:34,140 --> 00:04:35,440
比如超强猛料
Like, hard meats.

122
00:04:35,440 --> 00:04:36,700
何出此言
What do you mean?

123
00:04:36,820 --> 00:04:41,040
我一般吃完三明治后会胡思乱想  可现在没有
Well, usually after a sandwich, I feel paranoid, but I'm not.

124
00:04:42,080 --> 00:04:43,120
为什么我没有胡思乱想
Why am I not feeling paranoid?!

125
00:04:43,120 --> 00:04:45,530
别激动  兄弟
Calm down, dude!

126
00:04:45,730 --> 00:04:47,590
没事的
We'll be fine.

127
00:04:47,880 --> 00:04:49,280
莉莉会知道的
Lily's gonna know.

128
00:04:49,660 --> 00:04:50,940
听我说
Listen to me.

129
00:04:51,700 --> 00:04:53,860
虽然我不记得刚才我们在说什么
Whatever we were just talking about...

130
00:04:55,450 --> 00:04:57,420
反正没事的
we'll be fine.

131
00:04:57,420 --> 00:04:59,160
你说得对  她不会发现的
You're right, she won't find out.

132
00:04:59,250 --> 00:05:00,020
伙计们
Hey, guys.

133
00:05:00,020 --> 00:05:01,820
她知道了
She knows!

134
00:05:02,700 --> 00:05:04,190
晚上好
Good evening.

135
00:05:04,200 --> 00:05:06,480
接下来要特别欢迎我们的4位新实习生  分别是
A special welcome to our four new interns:

136
00:05:06,480 --> 00:05:09,160
艾丽卡...和其他人
Erika... and so on.

137
00:05:09,160 --> 00:05:12,260
安全小贴士  万一有人不幸落水
One safety matter: life preservers are on the side rails,

138
00:05:12,260 --> 00:05:14,770
救生用具就在甲板两侧
in case anyone falls overboard.

139
00:05:14,970 --> 00:05:16,640
我说完了  祝各位有个愉快的夜晚
That's it. Have a good night.

140
00:05:16,640 --> 00:05:17,940
别喝太多哦
Don't drink too much.

141
00:05:18,370 --> 00:05:19,600
喝多也无妨
Or do.

142
00:05:22,100 --> 00:05:23,500
今晚真开心  是吧  同志们
Beautiful night, huh, gang?

143
00:05:23,500 --> 00:05:25,920
对  我和罗宾刚在偷偷...
Yeah, Robin and I were just cheating--

144
00:05:25,920 --> 00:05:28,260
讨论今天有多热
chatting about how warm it is.

145
00:05:28,410 --> 00:05:31,080
我真是不忠...不中用
I'm breaking a trust-- sweat

146
00:05:31,330 --> 00:05:32,730
大汗淋漓呀
in here.

147
00:05:33,620 --> 00:05:36,320
我觉得我们热到要被抓去浸猪笼了
And I thought we'd be cuckold.

148
00:05:36,650 --> 00:05:38,610
我知道你为什么那么紧张  巴尼
I know why you're so nervous, Barney.

149
00:05:38,800 --> 00:05:40,000
你真知道
You do?

150
00:05:40,470 --> 00:05:42,390
明晚你要跟诺拉的父母见面  对吧
You're meeting Nora's parents tomorrow night, right?

151
00:05:43,410 --> 00:05:44,960
对对  没错
That's it! That's it!

152
00:05:44,960 --> 00:05:45,720
咱们去跳舞吧
Let's dance!

153
00:05:51,110 --> 00:05:53,950
莉莉不知道我嗨了
Lily has no idea I'm high.

154
00:05:54,150 --> 00:05:55,560
你嗨了
You're high?

155
00:05:55,960 --> 00:05:57,360
抱歉
I'm sorry.

156
00:06:00,300 --> 00:06:02,740
莉莉不知道我嗨了
Lily has no idea I'm high.

157
00:06:03,480 --> 00:06:05,460
好吧  如果你怀孕的妻子
Okay, well, if your pregnant wife

158
00:06:05,460 --> 00:06:07,420
不得不清醒地坐在这儿一整晚
has to sit here sober all night,

159
00:06:07,420 --> 00:06:10,460
那你至少得给她来点玉米片吧
she's gonna need some of them nachos.

160
00:06:10,660 --> 00:06:11,730
如你所愿
You got it.

161
00:06:11,980 --> 00:06:14,860
-伙计  把你玉米片交出来  -不要他吃过的
- Hey, dude, fork over some of them nach... - No, not his.

162
00:06:14,860 --> 00:06:16,200
我要独享一人份
My own.

163
00:06:16,310 --> 00:06:18,380
聪明
Ah. Smart.

164
00:06:19,050 --> 00:06:20,150
快走  泰德
Come on, Ted.

165
00:06:20,150 --> 00:06:21,160
怎么了
What?

166
00:06:25,290 --> 00:06:29,040
<i>于是我们踏上了人生最悲惨的旅程</i>
<i>And thus began the most harrowing journey of our lives.</i>

167
00:06:30,940 --> 00:06:32,880
<i>迄今为止  罗宾和巴尼都发誓</i>
<i>To this day, Robin and Barney swear</i>

168
00:06:32,880 --> 00:06:35,280
<i>当时他们跳舞就是放的这首歌</i>
<i>this is the song they danced to that night.</i>

169
00:06:35,540 --> 00:06:38,990
* 一株绿草出了墙 *
* You fooled around on your baby *

170
00:06:39,950 --> 00:06:42,940
* 坦白总比隐瞒强 *
* Now the least you could do is to tell her the truth *

171
00:06:42,940 --> 00:06:44,340
* 回头是岸西装男 *
* Yes, you in the suit *

172
00:06:44,340 --> 00:06:47,580
* 秘密吞噬你灵魂 *
* Or that secret will eat up your soul *

173
00:06:47,580 --> 00:06:51,100
* 女孩内疚到发狂 *
* Girl, the guilt's gonna drive you crazy *

174
00:06:51,100 --> 00:06:52,170
* 到发狂 *
* Crazy *

175
00:06:52,170 --> 00:06:55,100
* 别瞒凯文这儿郎 *
* You can't live with this lie, Kevin's such a nice guy *

176
00:06:55,100 --> 00:06:56,980
* 刻不容缓就今晚 *
* Gotta tell him tonight *

177
00:06:56,980 --> 00:06:59,490
* 就在此船道真相  *
* Tell them right here on this boat *

178
00:06:59,490 --> 00:07:03,420
* 你如污垢般肮脏 *
* You're like scum round the edge of a toilet bowl *

179
00:07:03,420 --> 00:07:04,710
* 冲光光 *
* Flush *

180
00:07:05,990 --> 00:07:09,540
* 不守妇道难见光 *
* What the hell is in the place where you should have a soul? *

181
00:07:09,540 --> 00:07:10,310
* 爱偷欢 *
* Slut *

182
00:07:10,310 --> 00:07:11,870
* 你俩已铸成大错 *
* You did these too wrong *

183
00:07:11,870 --> 00:07:13,330
* 快下决定别傍徨 *
* Don't wait too long *

184
00:07:13,330 --> 00:07:14,940
* 其实何不就这样 *
* In fact, you know what? *

185
00:07:15,210 --> 00:07:17,470
* 在我歌中来坦白 *
* Tell them right during this song *

186
00:07:17,470 --> 00:07:20,230
* 坦白  坦白  坦白 *
* Tell 'em, tell 'em, tell 'em, tell 'em, tell 'em *

187
00:07:21,900 --> 00:07:22,830
我等着
I'll wait.

188
00:07:22,830 --> 00:07:25,520
* 摊牌  摊牌  摊牌 *
* Tell 'em, tell 'em, tell 'em, tell 'em, tell 'em *

189
00:07:25,520 --> 00:07:27,810
拜托  你们真的不打算摊牌吗
Oh, come on, seriously, you're not gonna tell them?

190
00:07:28,720 --> 00:07:30,840
我们得坦白  现在就说
We have to tell them. Right now.

191
00:07:30,890 --> 00:07:33,440
* 无耻盗用我妙方 *
* Sure, act like it was your idea. *

192
00:07:33,440 --> 00:07:35,260
说真的  你俩真没用
Seriously, you guys suck.

193
00:07:40,370 --> 00:07:43,360
<i>我和马修还在排队给莉莉买玉米片</i>
<i>Marshall and I were still in line to get Lily's nachos.</i>

194
00:07:43,360 --> 00:07:45,780
伙计  我们都等了都快一辈子了
Dude, we've been waiting forever.

195
00:07:47,360 --> 00:07:50,590
更糟的是  这是等着上女厕的队伍
Even worse, this is the line for the ladies' room.

196
00:07:52,620 --> 00:07:55,640
真不敢相信  我们最后一次参加狂欢会
I can't believe that our last Groovapalooza was,

197
00:07:55,640 --> 00:07:57,470
是在12年前
what, 12 years ago?

198
00:07:57,470 --> 00:07:59,540
我是说  时间过得真快
I mean, time is going by so fast.

199
00:07:59,540 --> 00:08:01,210
我知道这很疯狂
I know, it's crazy.

200
00:08:01,340 --> 00:08:03,450
就好像一眨眼
In, like, an eye blink,

201
00:08:03,900 --> 00:08:08,400
这只手就会变成皱巴巴的老人手
this hand will be, like, an old man's hand.

202
00:08:08,400 --> 00:08:12,400
我知道接下来我说的都是些陈词滥调  可...
I recognize the clichéd nature of what I'm about to say, but...

203
00:08:13,530 --> 00:08:15,440
-哇塞  -是吧
- Whoa! -Yeah.

204
00:08:17,350 --> 00:08:18,420
312
312?

205
00:08:18,420 --> 00:08:19,730
我们就从这儿出来的
That's our gate.

206
00:08:19,780 --> 00:08:22,970
伙计  我们刚把整个场地转了一圈
Dude, we just walked around the entire arena.

207
00:08:23,620 --> 00:08:24,980
我们走了大约一小时
We've been walking for, like, an hour

208
00:08:24,980 --> 00:08:27,020
还是没找到玉米片
and we still haven't found the nachos.

209
00:08:27,020 --> 00:08:28,850
我猜莉莉一定很失望
I bet Lily is so upset.

210
00:08:30,200 --> 00:08:32,530
喂  兄弟  我的玉米片分你一半
Yo, you want my nachos, bro?

211
00:08:33,120 --> 00:08:34,630
谢谢
Thank you.

212
00:08:34,790 --> 00:08:38,170
我丈夫出去买这玩意儿都一个小时了
My husband's been gone an hour looking for these.

213
00:08:38,280 --> 00:08:39,460
如果这点事都办不好
If he can't even do that,

214
00:08:39,460 --> 00:08:41,660
我怎能相信他会是个好父亲呢
how can I trust him as a father?

215
00:08:41,660 --> 00:08:44,290
不可信  兄弟  不可信呀
You can't, bro. You can't.

216
00:08:45,720 --> 00:08:47,460
我喜欢你长长的山羊胡
I like your long goatee.

217
00:08:47,690 --> 00:08:49,600
马修连一根胡子都长不出来
Marshall can't even grow a beard.

218
00:08:49,600 --> 00:08:51,060
真可怜
Oh, that's sad.

219
00:08:51,060 --> 00:08:54,340
因为如果一个人脸上连根毛都不长
'Cause one's ability to grow facial hair directly correlates

220
00:08:54,340 --> 00:08:57,280
那他还有毛能力做个好父亲呀
with one's ability to be a good father.

221
00:08:57,280 --> 00:09:00,820
我就知道  我就知道
I know it does. I know it does.

222
00:09:07,440 --> 00:09:08,650
先生  请问一下
Excuse me, sir.

223
00:09:08,650 --> 00:09:10,400
你知道哪里卖玉米片吗
Do you know where the nachos are?

224
00:09:14,230 --> 00:09:15,860
马修
Marshall!

225
00:09:15,920 --> 00:09:18,080
过来  我找到买玉米片的队伍了
Over here. I found the nacho line.

226
00:09:23,980 --> 00:09:25,470
凯文那边怎么样了
So, h-how'd it go with Kevin?

227
00:09:25,470 --> 00:09:27,960
我刚准备告诉他
Well, I was just about to tell him...

228
00:09:28,650 --> 00:09:29,520
听我说  凯文
Look, Kevin...

229
00:09:29,520 --> 00:09:32,370
艾丽卡  我整晚一直想跟你说话
Erika, I've been meaning to speak with you all night.

230
00:09:32,370 --> 00:09:33,760
是吗  想说什么
Really? What about?

231
00:09:33,760 --> 00:09:35,930
说我想有一副娇躯  俯身栏杆
About me bending your hard little body over the railing

232
00:09:35,930 --> 00:09:37,680
面朝纽约
of this boat and copulating furiously

233
00:09:37,680 --> 00:09:40,530
"春"暖"花"开
while I admire the New York City skyline.

234
00:09:41,030 --> 00:09:43,600
如果你想玩大点  我们就改朝新泽西
Or, if you're feeling dirty, we can always face Jersey.

235
00:09:44,400 --> 00:09:45,500
你意下如何
Thoughts?

236
00:09:47,380 --> 00:09:48,530
墨西哥辣椒
Jalapeno!

237
00:09:48,940 --> 00:09:50,890
还有少许椰汁
And just a hint of coconut.

238
00:09:53,880 --> 00:09:55,720
凯文撞到头了  可能是脑震荡
Kevin hit his head, he might have a concussion.

239
00:09:55,720 --> 00:09:58,420
显然  我不能告诉他
So obviously I couldn't tell him.

240
00:09:59,140 --> 00:09:59,910
那你呢
What about you?

241
00:09:59,910 --> 00:10:02,360
她的遭遇更惨绝人寰
Something even worse happened to her.

242
00:10:02,930 --> 00:10:05,430
我的袖子上有个小酒渍
I got a tiny spot of wine on my sleeve.

243
00:10:08,510 --> 00:10:10,250
我不能雪上加霜
I couldn't pile on.

244
00:10:10,250 --> 00:10:11,880
我又不是禽兽
I'm not a monster.

245
00:10:12,910 --> 00:10:13,950
到底哪里有得卖呀
Where are they?

246
00:10:13,950 --> 00:10:16,480
算了吧  别想着玉米片了
Come on, forget the nachos.

247
00:10:16,480 --> 00:10:18,700
这里的人都自得其乐
Everyone here is having fun.

248
00:10:18,730 --> 00:10:20,500
瞧  还包括这些人
Look, even these guys.

249
00:10:20,500 --> 00:10:21,930
看看
Check it out.

250
00:10:22,570 --> 00:10:26,500
音乐是连结人们的纽带
Wow, music really does bring people together.

251
00:10:26,560 --> 00:10:28,640
泰德  泰德
Ted? Ted!

252
00:10:28,640 --> 00:10:30,900
有个变态吉他手跟着我们
Creepy guitar guy is following us.

253
00:10:38,420 --> 00:10:40,260
我们又绕了整整一圈
We did a whole nother lap.

254
00:10:40,280 --> 00:10:42,220
天啊  我们差不多错过半场演唱会
Oh, man, we missed, like, half the concert now.

255
00:10:42,220 --> 00:10:44,670
-我们还是回去吧  -泰德  泰德
- Come on, let's just go back to our seats. - Ted, Ted, Ted.

256
00:10:44,740 --> 00:10:47,130
人们一直在这排队买玉米片呢
The nacho line was right here all along.

257
00:10:48,390 --> 00:10:50,520
咱俩真笨
So stupid.

258
00:10:51,580 --> 00:10:54,120
船一靠岸  我就送凯文去急诊室
As soon as we dock, I'm taking Kevin to the E.R.

259
00:10:54,390 --> 00:10:58,170
天啊  真希望昨晚什么都没发生
God, I wish last night never happened.

260
00:11:01,070 --> 00:11:02,290
我可不这么想
I don't.

261
00:11:03,770 --> 00:11:04,960
这话什么意思
What do you mean?

262
00:11:05,530 --> 00:11:07,290
如果这件事的主线
What if this whole thing,

263
00:11:07,440 --> 00:11:09,870
不是在于  我们犯下弥天大错
it isn't the story of how we both made a horrible mistake

264
00:11:09,880 --> 00:11:11,510
葬送了各自的感情
and ruined our relationships,

265
00:11:12,290 --> 00:11:16,670
而是在于我们重修旧好呢
what if it's actually the story of how we got back together?

266
00:11:17,820 --> 00:11:19,900
好吧  我最后再问你一次
Okay, I'm gonna ask you one last time.

267
00:11:19,910 --> 00:11:22,220
这是你想要的结果吗
Is this what you want?

268
00:11:22,220 --> 00:11:24,140
这是我们想要的结果
It's what we both want!

269
00:11:24,260 --> 00:11:26,620
不然我们干嘛这么着急地想告诉他们真相
Why else are we rushing to tell them what we did?

270
00:11:26,620 --> 00:11:29,180
还要在船上说  这主意太烂了
On a boat! That is a terrible idea!

271
00:11:29,180 --> 00:11:32,490
巴尼  我们努力过  但最终分手收场
Barney, we tried this and we failed.

272
00:11:32,490 --> 00:11:33,720
为什么还要执迷不悟呢
Why try again?

273
00:11:33,720 --> 00:11:35,680
因为我总是忍不住想起你
Because I haven't stopped thinking about you

274
00:11:35,680 --> 00:11:37,850
而你也没有彻底忘记我
and you haven't stopped thinking about me.

275
00:11:40,410 --> 00:11:41,920
我的生活一团糟
I'm such a mess.

276
00:11:42,570 --> 00:11:43,560
为什么
Why...

277
00:11:44,240 --> 00:11:45,750
你为什么会喜欢我
Why do you even like me?

278
00:11:49,180 --> 00:11:50,260
我想
I guess...

279
00:11:51,020 --> 00:11:54,490
因为你的生活跟我一样糟
'cause you're almost as messed up as I am.

280
00:11:58,140 --> 00:12:00,670
还有一个小问题
Well, there's the small issue

281
00:12:00,670 --> 00:12:03,040
就是目前我们各自都有男女朋友
that we're currently dating other people.

282
00:12:03,040 --> 00:12:04,290
这样如何
How about this?

283
00:12:05,430 --> 00:12:10,200
船一靠岸  我们就去...做该做的事
After we dock, let's each do what we have to do,

284
00:12:10,200 --> 00:12:14,060
午夜时分在麦凯伦酒吧碰面  然后
and then meet up at MacLaren's at midnight and...

285
00:12:15,420 --> 00:12:16,830
正式谈谈我们自己
talk about us.

286
00:12:19,680 --> 00:12:22,660
别忘了你们的神秘礼物包
Don't forget your mystery gift bags!

287
00:12:24,040 --> 00:12:25,270
里面全是套套哦
They're condoms.

288
00:12:27,690 --> 00:12:29,870
我们又绕了整整一圈
We just went all the way around again!

289
00:12:29,870 --> 00:12:31,720
玉米片到底在哪里啊
Where the hell are these nachos?!

290
00:12:31,720 --> 00:12:33,290
谁在乎玉米片啊
Who cares about nachos?

291
00:12:33,290 --> 00:12:33,840
我在乎
I do.

292
00:12:33,840 --> 00:12:34,830
我超爱玉米片的  伙计
Oh, I love nachos, man!

293
00:12:34,830 --> 00:12:36,190
你该放松一下  伙计
You gotta relax, man.

294
00:12:36,190 --> 00:12:39,350
你一直在为玉米片焦虑
You keep worrying about stuff like nachos,

295
00:12:39,360 --> 00:12:41,300
这样下去你该犯心脏病了
you're gonna give yourself a heart attack.

296
00:12:41,780 --> 00:12:43,800
-我要进去了  -好吧
- I'm going back in. - Fine!

297
00:12:45,080 --> 00:12:47,420
哈  被耍了吧
Ha! Joke's on you!

298
00:12:47,800 --> 00:12:50,240
人们一直在这排队买玉米片呢
The nacho line was right here all along!

299
00:12:56,120 --> 00:12:58,160
罗宾和巴尼终于下船了
Robin and Barney are finally off the boat.

300
00:12:56,440 --> 00:12:58,010
{\an8}急诊室

301
00:12:58,170 --> 00:13:00,270
于是他们觉得现在应该更容易
So they both assumed it was going to be a lot easier

302
00:13:00,270 --> 00:13:02,300
开口坦诚他们的所作所为
to admit what they had done.

303
00:13:02,300 --> 00:13:04,250
-凯文  -我先说
- Kevin... - Me first.

304
00:13:04,550 --> 00:13:06,500
我不想把第一次开口说"我爱你"
Look, I don't want to make too much out

305
00:13:06,500 --> 00:13:08,070
这件事弄得很夸张
of saying "I love you" for the first time...

306
00:13:08,070 --> 00:13:09,740
能让我插个队先说吗
Any way I can jump in with my thing?

307
00:13:09,740 --> 00:13:13,240
罗宾  我爱你
Robin... I love you.

308
00:13:14,320 --> 00:13:16,050
诺拉  听我说
Okay, Nora, look...

309
00:13:16,310 --> 00:13:17,770
妈  爸
Mom! Dad!

310
00:13:17,770 --> 00:13:20,240
诺拉  我们提前到了
Hi, Nora, we got in early!

311
00:13:22,020 --> 00:13:24,500
早知道就在船上做了断了
Should've done it on the boat.

312
00:13:35,070 --> 00:13:37,250
你的朋友呢
Hey, where's your friend?

313
00:13:37,680 --> 00:13:41,340
由于他罔顾我们的友情  非要去找玉米片
We missed almost the entire show because he put his stupid quest

314
00:13:41,340 --> 00:13:44,040
害我们几乎错过了整场演出  所以我不管他了
for nachos ahead of our friendship, so I bolted.

315
00:13:44,110 --> 00:13:46,780
我只是一个变态老吉他手
Well, I'm just a creepy old guitar player,

316
00:13:46,780 --> 00:13:49,750
但和朋友在一起的每分每秒  不应该觉得幸福吗
but isn't any time spent with a friend a blessing?

317
00:13:50,370 --> 00:13:52,300
如果你们一心要求玉米片
And if nachos is all you seek...

318
00:13:53,200 --> 00:13:54,860
我的给你吧  兄弟
take mine, brother.

319
00:13:57,330 --> 00:13:58,560
谢谢
Thank you.

320
00:13:58,730 --> 00:14:00,040
这是个标牌  兄弟
It's a sign, bro.

321
00:14:01,090 --> 00:14:02,140
没错
It is.

322
00:14:02,310 --> 00:14:04,560
标志着我应该去找马修
It's a sign I should go find Marshall!

323
00:14:05,940 --> 00:14:07,740
马修  马修
Marshall! Marshall!

324
00:14:11,120 --> 00:14:14,690
巴尼  诺拉跟我们说了很多你的事
So, Barney, Nora's told us so much about you,

325
00:14:15,200 --> 00:14:16,860
但我们想了解你的全部
but we want to know everything.

326
00:14:16,870 --> 00:14:19,020
让我想想  喜欢西服  喜欢真人CS
Ah, let's see, suits, laser tag,

327
00:14:19,020 --> 00:14:20,640
喜欢说"等一下"  自我介绍完毕
I say "Wait for it" A lot. That's about it.

328
00:14:20,640 --> 00:14:21,750
你俩肯定累坏了
You two must be exhausted.

329
00:14:21,750 --> 00:14:23,140
我去煮咖啡
I'll make coffee.

330
00:14:24,010 --> 00:14:27,300
看到你们这么幸福  我很开心
I'm so glad to see how happy you both are.

331
00:14:27,500 --> 00:14:29,370
当你遇见命中注定的那个人时
When you meet the right person,

332
00:14:29,370 --> 00:14:30,730
你自然会知道
you know it.

333
00:14:31,040 --> 00:14:33,180
你总会忍不住想起她
You can't stop thinking about them.

334
00:14:36,200 --> 00:14:37,910
她是你的莫逆之交
They're your best friend...

335
00:14:40,420 --> 00:14:42,110
也是你的灵魂伴侣
...and your soul mate.

336
00:14:43,090 --> 00:14:46,230
你迫不及待要和她共度余生
You can't wait to spend the rest of your life with them.

337
00:14:46,500 --> 00:14:50,060
她独一无二   无人能及
No one and nothing else can compare.

338
00:14:50,630 --> 00:14:53,560
咖啡怎么还没好
Now, where the hell is that coffee, eh?

339
00:14:57,400 --> 00:15:01,100
诺拉  我有话要对你说
Look, Nora, there's something I have to tell you.

340
00:15:07,950 --> 00:15:09,170
有人犯心脏病了
Heart attack.

341
00:15:09,710 --> 00:15:12,080
天啊   泰德说得对  我要放轻松
Oh, God, Ted was right. I have to relax!

342
00:15:12,110 --> 00:15:12,770
泰德
Ted!

343
00:15:12,770 --> 00:15:13,830
-马修  -泰德
- Marshall! - Ted?

344
00:15:13,830 --> 00:15:15,080
-泰德  -马修
- Ted! - Marshall!

345
00:15:15,080 --> 00:15:17,360
泰德啊泰德
Oh, Ted! Oh, Ted!

346
00:15:17,410 --> 00:15:19,210
我很抱歉  你说得对
I'm so sorry! You were right.

347
00:15:19,210 --> 00:15:21,920
不  马修  不过我是对的
No, Marshall, you... Yeah, I was right.

348
00:15:21,920 --> 00:15:23,510
瞧  玉米片
But look, nachos!

349
00:15:24,690 --> 00:15:26,170
走  我们进去吧
Come on. Let's go back inside.

350
00:15:28,590 --> 00:15:29,720
完了
That's it.

351
00:15:31,250 --> 00:15:32,400
音乐会结束了
It's over.

352
00:15:32,760 --> 00:15:34,400
我们错过了整场演出
We missed the whole show.

353
00:15:36,510 --> 00:15:38,230
所以
So...

354
00:15:38,800 --> 00:15:41,200
没错  我爱你
Yup, I love you.

355
00:15:41,780 --> 00:15:43,240
凯文
Look, Kevin...

356
00:15:45,210 --> 00:15:46,920
有件事我必须告诉你
There's something I have to tell you.

357
00:15:47,270 --> 00:15:48,570
我出轨了
I cheated on you.

358
00:15:51,420 --> 00:15:53,530
我不知道该作何反应
I don't even know how to react.

359
00:15:54,380 --> 00:15:55,950
我真的很抱歉
I am so sorry.

360
00:15:57,520 --> 00:16:00,330
我明白你不会原谅我的
I know I don't get any second chances,

361
00:16:00,330 --> 00:16:03,400
可你永远会是...
but you will always be...

362
00:16:03,400 --> 00:16:05,550
是一夜情吗
Was this a one-time thing?

363
00:16:08,910 --> 00:16:10,840
告诉我她对你来说毫无意义
Can you tell me it didn't mean anything?

364
00:16:13,460 --> 00:16:14,650
不是的
No.

365
00:16:25,000 --> 00:16:26,470
抱歉  泰德
I'm sorry, Ted.

366
00:16:27,120 --> 00:16:28,860
我也想跟你一起找乐子
I still want to have fun,

367
00:16:29,550 --> 00:16:32,550
可我也得做个好老公  当个好父亲
it's just, I have to be a good husband and father, too.

368
00:16:32,550 --> 00:16:34,140
能跟你一起纵情欢乐的时间不多了
There's just not enough time, you know?

369
00:16:34,140 --> 00:16:35,220
我知道
I know.

370
00:16:35,580 --> 00:16:37,870
岁月如飞刀
It's all going by so damn fast.

371
00:16:38,120 --> 00:16:39,490
刀刀催人老呀
We're getting old.

372
00:16:40,530 --> 00:16:41,620
莉莉
Lily!

373
00:16:42,240 --> 00:16:45,530
莉莉  抱歉
Hey! Oh, Lily, I'm so sorry

374
00:16:45,530 --> 00:16:47,490
我们把今晚给毁了
that we ruined our night.

375
00:16:47,540 --> 00:16:48,830
你们俩说什么呢
What are you guys talking about?

376
00:16:48,830 --> 00:16:51,080
你们才出来不到两分钟
You've been gone less than 2 minutes.

377
00:16:51,440 --> 00:16:53,030
<i>孩子们  她没说错</i>
<i>Kids, she was right.</i>

378
00:16:57,560 --> 00:16:58,520
老人手
My hand.

379
00:16:58,520 --> 00:16:59,480
哇塞
Whoa!

380
00:16:59,490 --> 00:17:01,320
音乐会
Ah! Concert!

381
00:17:01,320 --> 00:17:03,870
玉米片
Nachos! Ah!

382
00:17:06,180 --> 00:17:07,440
音乐真奇妙
Haha, music!

383
00:17:13,070 --> 00:17:14,740
-时光啊  -玉米片啊
- Time! - Nachos!

384
00:17:17,550 --> 00:17:18,800
多谢了
Thank you!

385
00:17:18,880 --> 00:17:20,070
这是个标牌  兄弟
It's a sign, bro.

386
00:17:23,330 --> 00:17:24,990
-有人犯心脏病了  -马修
- Heart attack! - Marshall!

387
00:17:25,130 --> 00:17:27,280
-马修  -泰德
- Marshall! Oh! - Ted! Ted!

388
00:17:29,990 --> 00:17:31,480
岁月啊
Time...

389
00:17:36,150 --> 00:17:37,330
-莉莉  -莉莉
- Lily! - Lily!

390
00:17:39,580 --> 00:17:41,610
马修  你发现了吗
Marshall, do you get what this means?

391
00:17:41,750 --> 00:17:43,120
生命还没有太匆匆
Life isn't moving too fast.

392
00:17:43,120 --> 00:17:44,780
我们还来得及做任何事
We-we still have time for everything!

393
00:17:44,780 --> 00:17:46,870
我们也没有错过音乐会
And we're not gonna miss the concert!

394
00:17:48,230 --> 00:17:50,960
{\an8}十分钟后

395
00:17:48,230 --> 00:17:49,170
我快嗨爆了
I'm freaking out.

396
00:17:48,230 --> 00:17:49,170
{\an8}freak out也指吸毒后产生幻觉的意思

397
00:17:49,170 --> 00:17:50,960
-我们得离开这儿  -没错
- We gotta get out of here. - Yeah

398
00:17:53,000 --> 00:17:55,120
你们知道女厕所在哪儿吗
Do you guys know where the ladies' room is?

399
00:17:55,200 --> 00:17:56,630
-不知道  -从没见过
- No idea. - Haven't seen it.

400
00:18:00,470 --> 00:18:01,960
约会怎么样
Hey! How's it going?

401
00:18:02,150 --> 00:18:04,950
不怎么样  我和诺拉分手了
Oh, not great. Nora and I broke up.

402
00:18:05,070 --> 00:18:06,750
我的天  出什么事了
Oh, my God, what happened?

403
00:18:06,750 --> 00:18:09,540
我暂时不想谈这个  不过
I don't really feel like getting into it, but...

404
00:18:10,020 --> 00:18:11,760
我想我已经看见胜利的曙光了
I think the worst part is over.

405
00:18:18,300 --> 00:18:19,440
-凯文  -你好  凯文
- Hey, Kev. - What's up, Kev?

406
00:18:19,450 --> 00:18:20,150
还好吗  老兄
How's it going, buddy?

407
00:18:20,150 --> 00:18:21,210
各位好呀
Hey, guys.

408
00:18:21,720 --> 00:18:23,360
有件事我必须告诉你
There's something I have to tell you.

409
00:18:23,860 --> 00:18:25,400
我不想听
Then don't.

410
00:18:25,400 --> 00:18:26,530
什么
What?

411
00:18:26,710 --> 00:18:29,020
作为一个心理医生  我至少学到一件事
If there's one thing I've learned as a therapist,

412
00:18:29,370 --> 00:18:32,590
那就是有些"必须得说"的话
it's that just because something needs to be told

413
00:18:32,990 --> 00:18:34,890
不一定就"必须得听"
doesn't always mean it needs to be heard.

414
00:18:35,910 --> 00:18:38,820
凯文  我做了一件坏事
Kevin, I did something bad.

415
00:18:39,580 --> 00:18:41,280
人非圣贤
We've all ne bad things.

416
00:18:41,280 --> 00:18:43,000
孰能无过
Doesn't mean we're bad people.

417
00:18:44,150 --> 00:18:47,340
我不在乎你过去的细枝末节
Look, I don't care about every detail from your past,

418
00:18:47,340 --> 00:18:49,450
也希望你别在乎我的
and I hope you don't care about mine either.

419
00:18:50,440 --> 00:18:52,190
我在乎的只是你
What I do care about is you,

420
00:18:52,800 --> 00:18:57,020
从今往后  希望你跟我一样在乎这份感情
and that from tonight forward, you're in this as much as I am.

421
00:18:58,540 --> 00:18:59,810
你觉得如何
What do you think?

422
00:19:01,430 --> 00:19:04,290
我的生活一团糟
I'm such a mess.

423
00:19:06,740 --> 00:19:08,590
你为什么会喜欢我
Why do you even like me?

424
00:19:08,620 --> 00:19:09,650
过来
Come here.

425
00:19:11,330 --> 00:19:15,140
你说的每一件事都让我惊喜
I am constantly amazed by the things you say,

426
00:19:15,730 --> 00:19:18,070
你做的每一件事都让我着迷
entranced by the things you do,

427
00:19:18,590 --> 00:19:22,860
不像某个牌子的辣椒椰汁伏特加马丁尼酒
and unlike a certain Jalapeno Coconut Vodka martini,

428
00:19:23,360 --> 00:19:25,040
不会辣到让我的眼睛流泪
you're easy on the eyes.

429
00:19:26,500 --> 00:19:28,110
如果我们相处再久一点
And if we're together long enough,

430
00:19:29,540 --> 00:19:32,610
希望有一天  你眼中的自己就像我眼中的你一样
I hope that one day you see yourself the way I see you.

431
00:19:36,680 --> 00:19:38,130
这个回答真不错
That's a pretty good answer.

432
00:19:39,420 --> 00:19:41,790
时间很奇妙  有时候如白驹过隙
Sometimes hours can feel like minutes

433
00:19:41,920 --> 00:19:44,830
有时候却似度日如年
and sometimes a single second can last a lifetime.

434
00:19:45,430 --> 00:19:49,600
对巴尼来说  最漫长难熬的一秒莫过于此时
For Barney, the second that would never end was this one.

435
00:20:08,810 --> 00:20:10,830
各位  我先走了
Well, um, I should go.

436
00:20:11,080 --> 00:20:12,240
今晚真难熬
Tough night.

437
00:20:12,950 --> 00:20:13,890
抱歉[对不起]
I'm so sorry.

438
00:20:13,890 --> 00:20:16,160
真不用  其实没什么
Don't be. It's nothing.

439
00:20:18,520 --> 00:20:20,300
恢复清醒的感觉真好
It feels good to be sober again.

440
00:20:20,900 --> 00:20:24,320
天啊  我们都快在这坐到地老天荒了
Man, how long have we been sitting here, right?

441
00:20:24,510 --> 00:20:26,760
你坐下也就12秒  还坐错了卡座
12 seconds and you're in the wrong booth.

442
00:20:33,900 --> 00:20:35,280
我还是滚上床睡觉吧
I should go to bed.

443
00:20:35,280 --> 00:20:37,680
{\an8}Crooked Fingers 《Heavy Hours》

444
00:20:37,680 --> 00:20:43,180
* 在你窗外  我翘首等待 *
* Outside your window I waited for you *

445
00:20:44,780 --> 00:20:49,880
* 痴痴苦等  你不见芳踪 *
* You didn't come, you never do *

446
00:20:52,880 --> 00:20:57,080
* 沉重的分秒 *
* Heavy hours *

447
00:20:57,080 --> 00:21:03,480
* 从我的皮肤上划过 *
* Passing by away *

