1
00:02:14,400 --> 00:02:16,450
YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
更多原创字幕翻译 请登陆www.YYeTs.com

2
00:02:16,450 --> 00:02:19,050
         时间轴：YY 孤帆字幕总监： YY

3
00:02:19,050 --> 00:02:21,550
翻译： 小赛喵  非燕  阿蘅  猫中之王 孤帆  字幕总监： YY

4
00:02:21,550 --> 00:02:23,550
校对： YY    后期：孤帆 字幕总监： YY

5
00:02:23,550 --> 00:02:26,550
老爸老妈浪漫史
第七季  第十九集

6
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:02,060
<i>孩子们  2012年的春天</i>
<i>Kids, in the spring of 2012,</i>

7
00:00:02,060 --> 00:00:04,580
<i>你们巴尼叔叔突然失联了好几周</i>
<i>your Uncle Barney went off the grid for a couple weeks.</i>

8
00:00:04,580 --> 00:00:06,290
<i>所以等他发短信让我去他家时</i>
<i>So I was relieved when I got a text</i>

9
00:00:06,360 --> 00:00:08,090
<i>我松了一口气</i>
<i>asking me to come over to his place.</i>

10
00:00:08,180 --> 00:00:09,730
很高兴收到你短信  兄弟
Glad to hear from you, buddy.

11
00:00:09,730 --> 00:00:12,930
我还挺担心你是不是遭遇...
I was worried something bad happened...

12
00:00:13,680 --> 00:00:14,700
不测了
...to you.

13
00:00:14,700 --> 00:00:16,340
欢迎你  我的兄弟
Welcome, brother.

14
00:00:16,690 --> 00:00:17,540
这是干嘛
What is this?

15
00:00:17,540 --> 00:00:20,200
泰德·艾弗琳·莫斯比
Ted Evelyn Mosby,

16
00:00:20,200 --> 00:00:22,730
你将宣誓替我守密
you are about to be sworn to secrecy

17
00:00:22,730 --> 00:00:25,710
要以神圣兄弟的誓言起誓
through the sacred vows of a Bro Oath,

18
00:00:25,710 --> 00:00:28,230
或简称"兄言"
or "Broath."

19
00:00:28,990 --> 00:00:31,830
请穿上你的"兄袍"
Please, put on your "Brobe."

20
00:00:31,830 --> 00:00:34,290
我才不要穿这破"兄袍"
Yeah, I'm not putting on the "Brobe."

21
00:00:34,290 --> 00:00:35,570
泰德  你就...
Ted, just...

22
00:00:35,570 --> 00:00:37,970
配合点  可以吗
just... Okay?

23
00:00:38,150 --> 00:00:41,290
* 兄...*
* Broooo... *

24
00:00:41,650 --> 00:00:44,960
等等  这格列高利圣咏是在吟唱"兄"字吗
Wait, are they chanting "Bro"?"?

25
00:00:41,650 --> 00:00:44,960
{\an8}格列高利圣咏  是罗马天主教做弥撒时所用的音乐

26
00:00:44,960 --> 00:00:45,530
* 兄... *
* Bro... *

27
00:00:45,530 --> 00:00:47,470
我找了些当地的僧人给我录的
I got some local monks to record this.

28
00:00:47,470 --> 00:00:49,500
没错  我佛教界也有人
Yeah! I got a monk guy.

29
00:00:49,500 --> 00:00:50,100
厉害吧
Cool, right?

30
00:00:50,170 --> 00:00:51,540
是蛮厉害的
It actually is, yeah.

31
00:00:51,540 --> 00:00:52,470
我刻张碟给你
I'll burn it for you.

32
00:00:52,540 --> 00:00:54,250
"兄言"仪式结束后提醒我就行
Just remind me after The Broath.

33
00:00:54,250 --> 00:00:57,460
言归正传  泰德·艾弗琳·莫斯比
Anyway, Ted Evelyn Mosby,

34
00:00:57,460 --> 00:01:02,740
宣誓仪式后  你就要永远为我保守秘密
this ritual forever binds you to keep a solemn secret...

35
00:01:02,950 --> 00:01:03,720
什么秘密
Which is?

36
00:01:03,720 --> 00:01:05,650
我真的好喜欢昆茵哦
I really like this Quinn girl!

37
00:01:05,860 --> 00:01:07,240
我们最近总是形影不离
We've been spending tons of time together,

38
00:01:07,240 --> 00:01:08,520
我好想带她见见大伙
and I want the gang to meet her.

39
00:01:08,520 --> 00:01:10,600
不过我又怕其他人会反对  原因...
but I'm afraid they're gonna disapprove because,

40
00:01:10,600 --> 00:01:12,140
你懂的
well, you know.

41
00:01:12,140 --> 00:01:13,970
<i>我确实懂</i>
<i>I did know. You see,</i>

42
00:01:14,580 --> 00:01:16,040
<i>昆茵是个脱衣舞娘</i>
<i>Quinn was a stripper...</i>

43
00:01:16,040 --> 00:01:18,670
<i>还坑过巴尼不少钱</i>
<i>who had swindled Barney out of quite a bit of cash.</i>

44
00:01:19,110 --> 00:01:20,740
我们打算请大伙来昆茵家吃饭
We're inviting everyone to dinner at Quinn's,

45
00:01:20,740 --> 00:01:22,310
我不想大家对她有成见
and I want them to keep an open mind,

46
00:01:22,310 --> 00:01:24,370
所以才需要你以"兄言"的名义起誓
which brings us to The Broath.

47
00:01:24,490 --> 00:01:26,840
把你的手放在《兄弟法典》上
Place your hand on The Bro Code.

48
00:01:27,020 --> 00:01:28,910
好  好  随便
Yeah, yeah, yeah...

49
00:01:29,140 --> 00:01:30,600
随我复诵
Repeat after me.

50
00:01:30,600 --> 00:01:34,940
我  泰德·"艾弗琳"·莫斯比
I, Ted Evelyn Mosby...

51
00:01:34,940 --> 00:01:38,940
我  泰德·"跟你说我中间名真蠢"·莫斯比
"I, Ted "Why Did I Ever Tell You My Middle Name" Mosby..."

52
00:01:39,210 --> 00:01:41,580
慎重地起誓  不会给大伙们泄露半句
...solemnly swear not to tell our friends

53
00:01:41,580 --> 00:01:42,990
昆茵是个脱衣舞娘的事
that Quinn is a stripper.

54
00:01:42,990 --> 00:01:44,780
慎重地起誓  不会给大伙们泄露半句
"...solemnly swear not to tell our friends

55
00:01:44,780 --> 00:01:47,830
昆茵是个脱衣舞娘  还坑了你不少钱的事
that Quinn is a stripper" Who duped you out of lots of money.

56
00:01:48,220 --> 00:01:49,620
你复诵我说的就行了
You're only supposed to repeat after me.

57
00:01:49,620 --> 00:01:51,110
你复诵我说的就行了
"You're only supposed to repeat after me."

58
00:01:51,110 --> 00:01:52,030
-别闹了  -别闹了
- Stop it. - Stop it.

59
00:01:52,030 --> 00:01:53,220
肃静
Silence!

60
00:01:54,520 --> 00:01:58,170
我知道我和昆茵一开始不是很顺遂
Look, I know that things started out sketchy with me and Quinn,

61
00:01:58,170 --> 00:01:59,900
但我真的很喜欢她  就行行好吧
but I really like her, so please.

62
00:02:00,270 --> 00:02:01,580
你
Do you,

63
00:02:01,580 --> 00:02:05,770
泰德·中名省略·莫斯比
Ted Middle-Name-Omitted Mosby,

64
00:02:05,770 --> 00:02:09,060
愿意发誓永远遵守"兄言"吗
swear to uphold this Broath?

65
00:02:09,650 --> 00:02:11,240
我愿意
I do.

66
00:02:11,240 --> 00:02:13,610
巴尼跟一个会把他钱骗光光的脱衣舞娘好上了
Barney's dating a stripper who's gonna steal all his money!

67
00:02:27,530 --> 00:02:29,560
好了  该昆茵家吃饭啦  记住
Okay, time to go to Quinn's. Now remember,

68
00:02:29,560 --> 00:02:30,960
我什么都没说过  知道吗
I told you nothing, okay?

69
00:02:30,960 --> 00:02:32,780
巴尼真的很希望我们都喜欢她
Barney really wants us all to like her.

70
00:02:32,780 --> 00:02:33,830
怎么可能呀
But how can we?

71
00:02:33,830 --> 00:02:36,850
巴尼被人玩弄于股掌之间  还浑然不觉
Quinn totally duped Barney, and he couldn't even see it.

72
00:02:36,850 --> 00:02:39,410
显然  昆茵的床技让巴尼忘却了一切
Well, apparently, the sex is mind-blowing.

73
00:02:39,410 --> 00:02:42,100
我也有过这种经历  没错
Ha, I've been there. Yeah.

74
00:02:42,100 --> 00:02:44,200
某个妞开门时
I was once with this chick who answered the door

75
00:02:44,200 --> 00:02:47,320
上身赤裸  涂满奶油  脖戴狗链
wearing nothing but, uh, whipped cream, a dog collar

76
00:02:47,320 --> 00:02:49,140
粉红丁字绕股沟
and a hot pink thong.

77
00:02:49,310 --> 00:02:52,360
马修  你不能用"某个妞"来说你的性事
Marshall, you can't tell sex stories about "This chick,"

78
00:02:52,360 --> 00:02:54,590
因为大家都知道那个妞是我
because everyone knows it's me.

79
00:02:54,590 --> 00:02:56,680
你这辈子只跟我一个女人爽过
I'm the only woman you've ever been with.

80
00:02:56,680 --> 00:02:59,130
这不公平  他们都能显摆跟妞的性事
It's not fair, the guys are always telling their sex stories

81
00:02:59,130 --> 00:03:00,790
我有更好的却不能说
and I can top every one of them.

82
00:03:00,790 --> 00:03:04,260
宝贝  二十个性感风骚妞才荟萃成一个风情万种的你
Baby, you're like 20 slutty chicks all rolled into one.

83
00:03:04,260 --> 00:03:06,820
说再多的甜言蜜语也没用
Sweet talk is not going to change my mind.

84
00:03:07,050 --> 00:03:08,440
别再岔题
Let's focus.

85
00:03:08,490 --> 00:03:10,150
今晚  我们得看清
Tonight, we want to make sure

86
00:03:10,150 --> 00:03:12,590
昆茵到底是不是在骗巴尼的钱
that Quinn is not out to scam Barney.

87
00:03:12,590 --> 00:03:15,650
所以  当三个小时后重回这里时
So, when we walk back through that door three hours from now,

88
00:03:15,650 --> 00:03:18,770
我们心中都得有个答案
we should all be able to answer one simple question:

89
00:03:19,390 --> 00:03:20,980
三小时后

90
00:03:20,980 --> 00:03:23,120
这女人我们信不信得过
Do we trust this girl?

91
00:03:23,120 --> 00:03:24,290
先提一点
Well, for one thing,

92
00:03:24,290 --> 00:03:26,120
她控制欲有点儿强
she seems kind of controlling.

93
00:03:27,320 --> 00:03:29,420
要端鹰嘴豆泥出来吗  兔兔宝贝
Is it okay if I put out the hummus, bunny face?

94
00:03:29,420 --> 00:03:30,760
不许  留着当甜点
No, save it for dessert.

95
00:03:30,830 --> 00:03:32,200
白痴
Idiot.

96
00:03:36,130 --> 00:03:38,200
再来点红酒吗  天鹅美妞
More red wine, beauty-swan?

97
00:03:38,650 --> 00:03:40,490
她酒量超好
She drinks a lot.

98
00:03:41,640 --> 00:03:43,750
-我可以去尿尿吗  甜心小绵羊  -不准
- Is it okay if I go pee, sugar lamb? - No!

99
00:03:44,440 --> 00:03:46,010
你不是三个小时前刚去尿过吗
You just went three hours ago.

100
00:03:46,200 --> 00:03:47,920
你说得对  熊宝宝
You're right, baby bear!

101
00:03:52,070 --> 00:03:53,320
那又如何  就算巴尼是妻管严
Yes, so Barney's whipped;

102
00:03:53,320 --> 00:03:55,870
也不代表昆茵就是个骗子啊
it doesn't mean that Quinn is a con artist.

103
00:03:55,870 --> 00:03:58,290
要不是因为某两个人一直在岔题
Well, maybe we could've gotten a better read on her

104
00:03:58,290 --> 00:04:01,150
或许我们会更多机会分析她了
if two people hadn't gone off topic.

105
00:04:01,690 --> 00:04:04,080
顺带一提  昆茵  你这公寓真不错
By the way, Quinn, your apartment is amazing.

106
00:04:04,080 --> 00:04:05,620
是啊  真漂亮
Oh, yeah, it's beautiful.

107
00:04:05,620 --> 00:04:07,810
其实我快要搬了
I'm actually moving out soon.

108
00:04:07,810 --> 00:04:09,460
你们有认识人想租房吗
If you know anyone looking for a sublet,

109
00:04:09,530 --> 00:04:10,800
这里有租金管制制度
this place is rent-controlled.

110
00:04:10,870 --> 00:04:12,470
价钱划算到让你们难以置信
You would not believe what I pay.

111
00:04:12,530 --> 00:04:13,760
<i>孩子们  那段时间</i>
<i>Kids, things have been tense</i>

112
00:04:13,760 --> 00:04:15,650
<i>我和罗宾的关系变得紧张</i>
<i>between Robin and I for weeks.</i>

113
00:04:15,650 --> 00:04:17,610
<i>她搬走后</i>
<i>Ever since she moved out,</i>

114
00:04:17,610 --> 00:04:19,930
<i>我把公寓让给了马修和莉莉</i>
<i>and I gave the apartment to Marshall and Lily,</i>

115
00:04:20,230 --> 00:04:22,400
<i>然后自己跑去住大学宿舍</i>
<i>I'd been crashing in university housing.</i>

116
00:04:22,400 --> 00:04:24,760
都晚上十点了  我靠
It's 10 o'clock, damn it.

117
00:04:24,760 --> 00:04:26,280
耐德  马丁和米莉
Ned, Martin and Millie,

118
00:04:26,350 --> 00:04:27,950
有人想好好睡觉呢
people are trying to sleep!

119
00:04:27,950 --> 00:04:30,890
你年轻时不也这样吗
Hey, you were young like us once, right?

120
00:04:30,890 --> 00:04:35,020
我年轻时  才不是你们这样
I was never like you guys.

121
00:04:35,020 --> 00:04:37,720
<i>罗宾则是去她同事帕拉里斯家住</i>
<i>And Robin was staying with her coworker, Patrice.</i>

122
00:04:37,720 --> 00:04:39,490
你今天心情好像不太好啊  罗宾
You seem so down today, Robin.

123
00:04:39,490 --> 00:04:40,920
我烤了点饼干哦
I made you cookies.

124
00:04:40,920 --> 00:04:43,690
我靠  帕拉里斯  你想烦死我呀
Damn it, Patrice, stop smothering me!

125
00:04:44,770 --> 00:04:47,440
<i>因此  当昆茵说出她的公寓待租的时候...</i>
<i>So, when Quinn said her apartment was available...</i>

126
00:04:48,970 --> 00:04:50,370
我的  我的  我的
It's mine! It's mine! It's mine!

127
00:04:50,440 --> 00:04:51,400
我先  我先  我先
Dibs! Dibs! Dibs!

128
00:04:51,770 --> 00:04:54,450
岔题的是我们吗  那马修算什么
We got off topic? What about Marshall?

129
00:04:54,450 --> 00:04:56,210
我只是附和那个
Hey, I was just going along with

130
00:04:56,210 --> 00:04:58,270
提议要玩游戏的人而已
whoever suggested we play that game.

131
00:04:58,270 --> 00:04:59,510
大伙们  来玩个游戏吧
Hey, let's play a game!

132
00:04:59,580 --> 00:05:02,620
来说说"公共场合最刺激的性爱经历"  我先说
Uh, craziest sex-in-public story; I'll start.

133
00:05:02,620 --> 00:05:04,070
曾经有某个妞
I was once with this chick

134
00:05:04,070 --> 00:05:06,730
她爱在电梯里"性"奋
who loved to get freaky in elevators.

135
00:05:06,730 --> 00:05:08,340
门一关上  她会突然间
Doors would close; suddenly,

136
00:05:08,340 --> 00:05:11,190
四脚着地喘粗气  像只发情的母狗
she's panting on all fours like a dog in heat.

137
00:05:14,020 --> 00:05:15,360
马修  别说了
Marshall, stop.

138
00:05:15,360 --> 00:05:17,180
我可没说过那人就是你
I never said that it was you.

139
00:05:17,180 --> 00:05:18,880
好吧  不管怎样  去年八月
Okay, so anyway, last August,

140
00:05:18,880 --> 00:05:21,040
我和这个小荡妇做爱时没戴套
I go bareback with this same slut.

141
00:05:21,040 --> 00:05:23,840
结果她怀孕了  此后这妞性欲更强了
She get's pregnant; bitch is even hornier.

142
00:05:25,070 --> 00:05:27,000
是吗  我也和某个男的交往过
Oh, yeah? I was once with this dude

143
00:05:27,000 --> 00:05:29,120
被我发现他在做爱时吃三明治
who I caught eating a sandwich during sex.

144
00:05:29,120 --> 00:05:32,800
大肉丸掉出来  砸过我背上
Big ol' meatball falls out, lands on my back,

145
00:05:32,800 --> 00:05:34,930
一直滚到电梯地板上
rolls on to the elevator floor.

146
00:05:34,930 --> 00:05:37,150
恶心吧
Hmm. Disgusting, right?

147
00:05:37,600 --> 00:05:39,340
怎么了  我可没说那人就是你
What, I never said it was you.

148
00:05:40,900 --> 00:05:43,760
是啊  抱歉我们没你们那么专注
Yeah, sorry we didn't stay as laser-focused as you guys.

149
00:05:43,760 --> 00:05:45,990
至少我发现了些证据
Hey, at least I got some evidence.

150
00:05:45,990 --> 00:05:48,710
瞧我在昆茵卧室里发现了什么
Look what I found in Quinn's bedroom.

151
00:05:48,710 --> 00:05:50,870
巴尼要带她去夏威夷
Barney's taking her to Hawaii.

152
00:05:50,930 --> 00:05:52,600
莉莉  你还偷翻她的东西了
Lily, you snooped through her stuff?

153
00:05:52,670 --> 00:05:54,820
才没有  我不过是用开信刀
No. It's like the first thing you see

154
00:05:54,820 --> 00:05:57,670
偷偷打开她的抽屉  一眼就看到了
when you Jimmy open her desk drawer with a letter opener

155
00:05:57,740 --> 00:06:00,290
她日记里面还说  这开信刀是她奶奶留给她的呢
her grandfather left her, according to her diary.

156
00:06:00,560 --> 00:06:01,570
一等舱机票
First-class tickets,

157
00:06:01,570 --> 00:06:03,920
四星级酒店  这得花巴尼不少钱呢
a four-star hotel-- this cost Barney a fortune.

158
00:06:03,920 --> 00:06:07,780
对  这证明昆茵只是把巴尼当金主
Yeah, this proves that Quinn is totally using him for his money.

159
00:06:07,780 --> 00:06:09,260
好了  莉莉  别闹了
You know what, Lily, enough.

160
00:06:09,260 --> 00:06:11,650
伙计们  即使你们说得没错  但这是巴尼的事
Guys, even if you're right about Quinn, this is Barney.

161
00:06:11,650 --> 00:06:12,920
他迟早会意识到的
He'll come to his senses.

162
00:06:12,920 --> 00:06:15,620
我们再等一周  最多两周
I give this whole thing a week, two weeks, tops.

163
00:06:15,620 --> 00:06:17,830
现在  我们有事要宣布
And now, we have an announcement.

164
00:06:17,890 --> 00:06:18,530
能让我来说吗
Can I tell them?

165
00:06:18,590 --> 00:06:19,710
不行
No.

166
00:06:20,050 --> 00:06:21,720
-我们要同居了  -我们...
- We're moving in together - We're m...

167
00:06:22,840 --> 00:06:25,620
-恭喜  太好了  -真替你们高兴
- Congrats! That's great. - So happy for you.

168
00:06:25,630 --> 00:06:26,730
我们得棒打鸳鸯了
We gotta end this.

169
00:06:26,800 --> 00:06:28,100
对
Yup.

170
00:06:31,640 --> 00:06:33,240
<i>孩子们  你们应该记得</i>
<i>Kids, as you'll recall,</i>

171
00:06:33,240 --> 00:06:35,960
<i>我们这伙人会通过隐晦的方式</i>
<i>our gang had a subtle way</i> <i>of letting someone know</i>

172
00:06:35,960 --> 00:06:37,620
<i>让朋友知道他们在犯错</i>
<i>they were making a mistake.</i>

173
00:06:37,620 --> 00:06:38,220
劝诫大会

174
00:06:39,480 --> 00:06:40,700
你去哪里了
Where have you been?

175
00:06:40,700 --> 00:06:42,870
没白跑  等等
Oh, worth it. Hang on.

176
00:06:45,260 --> 00:06:50,220
戒茵大会

177
00:06:51,420 --> 00:06:53,220
我们事后肯定会恨死自己的  对吧
You know we would've hated ourselves, right?

178
00:06:55,710 --> 00:06:56,450
所以
So,

179
00:06:56,450 --> 00:06:59,710
罗宾有说今天自己偷摸着干嘛了吗
did Robin tell you the incredibly devious thing she did today?

180
00:06:59,710 --> 00:07:00,820
怎么是我
Me?!

181
00:07:02,080 --> 00:07:04,150
我刚碰巧来这个小区
Hey, so I just happened to be in the neighborhood

182
00:07:04,150 --> 00:07:06,910
然后灵光一闪  "天啊  昆茵身材那么好"
and I thought, "Man, Quinn is in such great shape,

183
00:07:06,910 --> 00:07:08,900
"她一定喜欢吃水果"
she must love fruit."

184
00:07:09,840 --> 00:07:11,180
对了  随便问下
So, unrelated,

185
00:07:11,180 --> 00:07:13,530
你代租人找得怎么样了
how's the search for a sub-letter going?

186
00:07:13,530 --> 00:07:16,730
这也太巧了吧
This is such a weird coincidence!

187
00:07:16,730 --> 00:07:19,080
罗宾也"正好碰巧"来这个小区
Robin also "just happened" to be in the neighborhood

188
00:07:19,080 --> 00:07:22,360
还带了一瓶酒和她的信用评级
with a bottle of wine and her credit scores.

189
00:07:29,170 --> 00:07:30,640
你俩真是不可理喻
I can't believe you two.

190
00:07:30,640 --> 00:07:31,900
你们更在意什么
What do you care about more,

191
00:07:31,900 --> 00:07:33,510
是保护朋友不受伤害
protecting your friend from getting hurt

192
00:07:33,510 --> 00:07:35,660
还是抢占这个姑娘的公寓
or scoring this girl's apartment?

193
00:07:35,660 --> 00:07:37,410
那房子有个能用的壁炉
There's a working fireplace!

194
00:07:37,410 --> 00:07:39,860
帕拉里斯把我的裤子都给烫坏了
Patrice is ironing my pants all wrong!

195
00:07:40,320 --> 00:07:42,150
你们真该感到难为情
You guys should be ashamed.

196
00:07:42,150 --> 00:07:43,470
说到难为情
Speaking of shame,

197
00:07:43,470 --> 00:07:46,240
以前有某个妞  她喜欢在麦凯伦酒吧
I was once with this chick who liked to do hand stuff

198
00:07:46,240 --> 00:07:47,820
我们最喜欢的小隔间里
underneath a jacket while we were all

199
00:07:47,820 --> 00:07:49,890
盖着外套帮我打手枪
sitting around our favorite booth at MacLaren's.

200
00:07:49,890 --> 00:07:50,770
真恶心
Gross.

201
00:07:50,770 --> 00:07:52,510
我们前菜可是一起吃的
We share appetizers.

202
00:07:52,510 --> 00:07:55,330
好吧  我以前交往过的某个男的
Okay, well, I was once with a dude

203
00:07:55,330 --> 00:07:58,130
连意淫下三人行都不敢
who couldn't even fantasize about a three-way.

204
00:07:58,130 --> 00:08:00,400
他就只会说  "她可是你的闺蜜"
He was all, "Ew, she's your best friend."

205
00:08:00,400 --> 00:08:01,230
干嘛现在说
What now?

206
00:08:01,230 --> 00:08:02,740
我以前交往过的某个妞
I was once with a chick who wanted

207
00:08:02,740 --> 00:08:05,560
想在演学校话剧《彼得潘》的时候亲热
to get it on during a school production of <i>Peter</i> <i>Pan.</i>

208
00:08:05,560 --> 00:08:09,410
我...等等  你说的不是我
Well, I... Wait, that wasn't me.

209
00:08:09,410 --> 00:08:11,140
还是继续聊帕拉里斯和烫衣服的事吧
So, back to Patrice and this ironing issue...

210
00:08:11,140 --> 00:08:13,920
我以为你所有的第一次都是和我做的
I thought I was the first girl you ever did anything with.

211
00:08:13,920 --> 00:08:15,130
所有认真的第一次
Anything serious.

212
00:08:15,130 --> 00:08:17,120
别告诉我你嫉妒我在十年级时
Please don't tell me that you're jealous of me getting

213
00:08:17,120 --> 00:08:20,210
和珍娜·克里斯托莉进行到二垒[摸胸]
to second base in tenth grade with Jenna Cristalli.

214
00:08:20,210 --> 00:08:22,980
别当着我们宝宝的面提那个婊子的名字
Don't say that whore's name in front of our baby.

215
00:08:24,580 --> 00:08:25,720
什么事
What's going on?

216
00:08:26,840 --> 00:08:29,820
巴尼  这是场劝说大会
Barney, this in an intervention.

217
00:08:31,560 --> 00:08:33,330
是"戒茵大会"
A "Quinntervention."

218
00:08:33,790 --> 00:08:37,150
你和奎茵进展太快了  而我们不信任她
You and Quinn are moving really fast, and we don't trust her.

219
00:08:37,520 --> 00:08:39,690
我们只是让你留个心眼
We're just looking out for your best interests.

220
00:08:42,750 --> 00:08:44,810
"留心昆茵"
"Quinn-terests."

221
00:08:45,370 --> 00:08:47,160
我不明白
I don't understand. Wh...

222
00:08:47,630 --> 00:08:49,330
等等
Wait a sec.

223
00:08:49,400 --> 00:08:51,740
泰德·艾弗琳·莫斯比
Ted Evelyn Mosby...

224
00:08:51,800 --> 00:08:54,370
你违反了"兄言"
you broke The Broath.

225
00:08:54,440 --> 00:08:56,040
你可别血口喷人
How dare you?!

226
00:08:56,110 --> 00:08:58,760
"兄言"是兄弟间最神圣的...
A Broath is the most sacred bond between--

227
00:08:58,760 --> 00:09:00,030
是  我违反了
okay, yeah, I did.

228
00:09:00,270 --> 00:09:04,160
你知道违反"兄言"后果严重
Are you aware that breaking a Broath can have deadly,

229
00:09:04,160 --> 00:09:06,850
甚至可能招来杀生之祸吗
even fatal repercussions?

230
00:09:06,850 --> 00:09:09,580
-你有学过历史吗  泰德  -我古今皆通
- Have you studied history, Ted? - Extensively.

231
00:09:09,580 --> 00:09:11,670
可我对捏造的历史一窍不通  所以...
But I'm a little shaky on fake history, so...

232
00:09:11,670 --> 00:09:14,380
违反"兄言"的惨痛代价
The tragic cost of a broken Broath

233
00:09:14,380 --> 00:09:18,030
可以追溯到古"罗兄"时期
dates back to Ancient Bro-man times...

234
00:09:20,350 --> 00:09:22,360
兄鲁图
Hey, Bro-tus,

235
00:09:20,350 --> 00:09:24,560
{\an8}源自罗马政治家布鲁图[Brutus]
马尔库斯·尤尼乌斯·布鲁图是凯撒最宠爱的助手、挚友和养子

236
00:09:22,360 --> 00:09:24,560
要是有一群人合谋刺杀我
you'd tell me if, like, a bunch of dudes

237
00:09:24,560 --> 00:09:26,920
你会告诉我的  对吧
were conspiring to assassinate me, right?

238
00:09:26,920 --> 00:09:30,310
没错  凯撒
Um, totally, Caesar.

239
00:09:30,640 --> 00:09:32,170
被害妄想症又烦了吧
Paranoid much?

240
00:09:32,910 --> 00:09:34,420
我只是想确定
Just to be sure,

241
00:09:35,150 --> 00:09:37,430
你能对着"兄言"发誓吗
can you swear a Broath to me?

242
00:09:37,550 --> 00:09:39,960
好  我发誓
Sure. I swear.

243
00:09:41,110 --> 00:09:42,090
谢了
Thanks.

244
00:09:42,090 --> 00:09:44,220
就知道你一直都挺我
You've always got my back.

245
00:09:49,240 --> 00:09:54,990
[恺撒被一班反对君主制的罗马元老院成员一人一刀捅死
行刺者包括布鲁图]

246
00:10:04,840 --> 00:10:07,850
<i>你也有份吗  兄鲁图</i>
<i>Et tu, Bro-te?</i>

247
00:10:04,840 --> 00:10:10,640
{\an8}"Et tu, brute"出自英国文艺复兴时期
大文豪威廉·莎士比亚的作品《儒略·恺撒》

248
00:10:12,350 --> 00:10:14,830
然后他上了上百个妞
And then he banged, like, a hundred chicks

249
00:10:14,830 --> 00:10:16,270
还发明了凯撒沙拉
and invented a salad.

250
00:10:14,830 --> 00:10:18,130
{\an8}凯撒沙拉则是由一名墨西哥餐厅主厨
凯撒·卡迪尼在1924年发明

251
00:10:17,160 --> 00:10:18,130
真事哟
True story.

252
00:10:18,760 --> 00:10:21,470
昆茵骗了你  还把你玩弄于股掌之间
Well, Quinn lied to you, she manipulated you.

253
00:10:21,470 --> 00:10:23,040
如果她只是在利用你呢
What if she's just using you?

254
00:10:23,040 --> 00:10:24,250
她没有利用我
She's not just using me.

255
00:10:24,250 --> 00:10:26,420
夏威夷奢华之旅怎么说呢
What about the expensive trip to Hawaii?

256
00:10:26,420 --> 00:10:28,620
什么夏威夷奢华之旅
What expensive trip to Hawaii?

257
00:10:29,620 --> 00:10:31,320
那是我为你准备的
The one I got for you.

258
00:10:32,400 --> 00:10:34,720
那本来是给巴尼的惊喜
That was supposed to be a surprise for Barney.

259
00:10:34,720 --> 00:10:36,750
巴尼让我来这里找他
He asked me to meet him here.

260
00:10:36,750 --> 00:10:38,850
你们在做什么
What's going on, you guys?

261
00:10:39,880 --> 00:10:40,590
告诉她
Tell her.

262
00:10:42,870 --> 00:10:45,080
好  那我来告诉她[我来塞满她]
Fine, I'll fill her in.

263
00:10:45,080 --> 00:10:46,520
我现在一肚子火
And I am so angry,

264
00:10:46,520 --> 00:10:49,990
都没心情开黄色玩笑了
I'm not even gonna make a joke about "filling her in."

265
00:10:49,990 --> 00:10:52,270
虽然我昨晚塞了三次  自己鼓掌
Which I did three times last night, self-five.

266
00:10:52,940 --> 00:10:54,730
我朋友觉得你不适合我
My friends think you're wrong for me,

267
00:10:54,730 --> 00:10:56,700
所以他们在开劝诫大会
so they're having an intervention.

268
00:10:59,470 --> 00:11:01,470
是"戒茵大会"
A "Quinntervention."

269
00:11:01,930 --> 00:11:03,200
我不明白
I don't understand.

270
00:11:03,270 --> 00:11:05,590
你叫昆茵嘛  "戒"是指...
Well, see, your name is Quinn, and so...

271
00:11:05,590 --> 00:11:06,870
我来解释
I'll explain.

272
00:11:08,020 --> 00:11:11,190
我让泰德不要告诉他们你的职业
I made Ted promise not to tell them what you do,

273
00:11:11,190 --> 00:11:12,060
但是他还是说了
but he did,

274
00:11:12,060 --> 00:11:13,550
现在他们不信任你
and now they don't trust you.

275
00:11:14,270 --> 00:11:17,310
还真是伤人啊
Wow, that really hurts.

276
00:11:17,700 --> 00:11:19,320
但让我更伤心的是
But what's even worse is that

277
00:11:19,320 --> 00:11:21,810
你居然觉得有必要隐瞒我的职业
you felt the need to lie about me.

278
00:11:21,810 --> 00:11:23,900
巴尼  我不已自己为耻
I'm not ashamed of who I am, Barney,

279
00:11:23,900 --> 00:11:25,920
但你却觉得不光彩
but you clearly are.

280
00:11:25,920 --> 00:11:27,330
我没有觉得不光彩
I'm not ashamed of you.

281
00:11:27,390 --> 00:11:29,270
我只是不想让他们对你妄下评判
I just didn't want them to judge you without...

282
00:11:29,270 --> 00:11:31,120
也许我们是进展得太快了
Maybe we are moving too fast.

283
00:11:31,120 --> 00:11:33,410
什么  你这话什么意思
What? What is that supposed to mean?

284
00:11:33,410 --> 00:11:35,420
我没办法继续了
I don't think I can do this.

285
00:11:35,420 --> 00:11:38,680
你就这样和我分手吗
Wait, are you ending things just like that?

286
00:11:39,500 --> 00:11:42,050
如果你走出那扇门  就证明他们是对的
If you walk out that door, you prove them right.

287
00:11:42,050 --> 00:11:44,660
也证明了  你是个绝情寡义的脱衣舞娘
You prove that you're just some heartless stripper

288
00:11:44,660 --> 00:11:46,120
一心在乎的是我的钱而不是...
who never gave a damn about me in the...

289
00:11:48,510 --> 00:11:50,020
别找我了
Don't call me.

290
00:11:54,380 --> 00:11:57,060
真是紧张又激烈
Wow. That was intense.

291
00:12:02,330 --> 00:12:03,890
我们刚刚破坏了
We just destroyed what could have been

292
00:12:03,890 --> 00:12:06,610
一个千载难逢的幸福机会
a once-in-a-lifetime shot at happiness.

293
00:12:06,610 --> 00:12:08,800
我知道  我也很自责
I know. I feel guilty, too.

294
00:12:09,120 --> 00:12:11,650
壁炉  阳台
Fireplace, balcony,

295
00:12:11,720 --> 00:12:13,180
硬木地板
hardwood floors...

296
00:12:13,470 --> 00:12:15,060
够了  我就直说吧
Okay, I'll just say it:

297
00:12:15,390 --> 00:12:16,490
在我们发生那么多事后
After everything that happened between us,

298
00:12:16,490 --> 00:12:18,150
我真不敢相信你居然还不肯放手
I can't believe you wouldn't back down

299
00:12:18,150 --> 00:12:19,930
把昆茵的房子让给我
and let me have Quinn's place.

300
00:12:20,790 --> 00:12:22,880
泰德  我们能出去聊聊吗
Ted, can I talk to you out in the hall?

301
00:12:25,760 --> 00:12:27,220
你有没有想过
Has it ever occurred to you

302
00:12:27,220 --> 00:12:30,320
过去的几周  我也很难熬
that the last few weeks haven't been easy for me either?

303
00:12:30,320 --> 00:12:33,930
一天之内  我感情破裂
In the span of one day, my engagement fell apart,

304
00:12:33,930 --> 00:12:36,700
痛失挚友  无家可归
I lost my best friend, then I lost my apartment.

305
00:12:36,700 --> 00:12:39,190
而现在  我又即将变成无业游民
And-and now I'm about to lose my job.

306
00:12:39,190 --> 00:12:40,380
这话什么意思
What do you mean?

307
00:12:40,790 --> 00:12:44,170
我最近无法专心工作
I-I've been completely distracted at work.

308
00:12:44,170 --> 00:12:46,990
老板要我周五五点去见他
And now my boss wants to see me Friday at 5:00,

309
00:12:46,990 --> 00:12:50,610
全办公室的人都知道那是"炒鱿鱼专点"
which, around the office, is known as "fire o'clock."

310
00:12:50,960 --> 00:12:52,820
我不知道
I had no idea.

311
00:12:52,820 --> 00:12:53,860
你怎么可能知道
How could you?

312
00:12:53,860 --> 00:12:57,270
我唯一想与之倾诉的那个人
The one person I want to talk to most barely looks me

313
00:12:57,270 --> 00:12:59,890
现在不愿看我一眼  更别说回我电话了
in the eye anymore, much less returns my calls.

314
00:13:00,370 --> 00:13:03,150
泰德  我知道向我表白需要很大的勇气
Ted, I know it took guts to tell me you love me.

315
00:13:03,150 --> 00:13:07,240
我也知道我没有接受你有多伤心
And I-I know how much it hurt that I didn't say it back,

316
00:13:07,240 --> 00:13:08,190
但是...
but...

317
00:13:08,900 --> 00:13:12,160
该死的  我心里也不好受
Damn it, th-this sucks for me,  too.

318
00:13:13,580 --> 00:13:15,410
我想你
And I-I miss you.

319
00:13:17,050 --> 00:13:19,040
我们能不能...
Is there any way we can just...

320
00:13:20,050 --> 00:13:21,740
重新做回朋友
go back to normal?

321
00:13:24,250 --> 00:13:27,060
我们回不去了
I don't think I can do normal anymore.

322
00:13:31,000 --> 00:13:32,700
巴尼还是没回电话
Barney still isn't answering.

323
00:13:32,700 --> 00:13:35,120
我们得找到他  向他道歉
We gotta go find him and apologize.

324
00:13:39,930 --> 00:13:41,990
我还以为是昆茵呢
Oh. I thought you were Quinn.

325
00:13:42,490 --> 00:13:43,960
巴尼  真的很抱歉
Barney, we're so sorry.

326
00:13:43,960 --> 00:13:46,100
我们不该这么蛮横插手你的事
We never should've meddled like that.

327
00:13:46,100 --> 00:13:47,810
-你能原谅我们吗  -我不知道
- Can you forgive us? - I don't know.

328
00:13:47,880 --> 00:13:49,380
你们没有权利那么做
You had no right to do that.

329
00:13:49,380 --> 00:13:51,210
兄弟  那你想我们怎么补偿你
How can we make it up to you, buddy?

330
00:13:54,360 --> 00:13:57,250
我  巴尼的死党之一
I, one of Barney's best friends...

331
00:13:57,250 --> 00:14:00,080
我  巴尼的死党之一
"I, one of Barney's best friends..."

332
00:14:00,080 --> 00:14:04,020
发誓再也不会干涉他的私人生活
...promise never to interfere with his personal life again...

333
00:14:04,020 --> 00:14:07,880
发誓再也不会干涉他的私人生活
"...promise never to interfere with his personal life again..."

334
00:14:07,880 --> 00:14:11,700
除非涉及到身体健康  国家安全
...unless it's an issue of health, national security,

335
00:14:11,770 --> 00:14:13,830
或他准备上一个胖妞
or he's about to get up on a fattie.

336
00:14:13,830 --> 00:14:17,950
除非涉及到身体健康  国家安全
"...unless it's an issue of health, national security,

337
00:14:17,950 --> 00:14:20,960
或他准备上一个胖妞
or he's about to get up on a fattie."

338
00:14:20,960 --> 00:14:24,820
现在  两位女士请亲吻对方
And now, to seal this sacred vow,

339
00:14:25,490 --> 00:14:27,120
-以吻封住这庄严的誓言  -巴尼
- the two ladies will kiss. - Barney...

340
00:14:27,190 --> 00:14:29,680
两位女士请亲吻对方
The two ladies will kiss!

341
00:14:36,640 --> 00:14:37,370
莉莉
Lil...

342
00:14:37,830 --> 00:14:38,740
好了
Okay.

343
00:14:39,370 --> 00:14:40,690
现在该男士了
And now the gentlemen.

344
00:14:40,690 --> 00:14:41,540
老兄
Dude...

345
00:14:41,540 --> 00:14:43,960
现在该男士了
And now the gentlemen!

346
00:14:45,400 --> 00:14:48,240
-我们就...  -太乱来了
- Let's just... - This is silly.

347
00:14:50,680 --> 00:14:52,710
别  别碰我的脸
Don't-don't touch my face.

348
00:14:57,170 --> 00:14:57,770
我本来要说
I was going to say,

349
00:14:57,770 --> 00:14:59,590
"现在该男士碰拳封住誓言"
"And now the gentlemen bump fists."

350
00:14:59,650 --> 00:15:01,660
你们俩想亲对方多久了呀
How long you been holding back that one?

351
00:15:02,530 --> 00:15:04,410
太香艳了  老兄
Hot stuff, fellas.

352
00:15:04,410 --> 00:15:06,410
是有伸舌头吗
Did I see a little tongue in there?

353
00:15:07,690 --> 00:15:09,350
这是怎么回事
I don't understand.

354
00:15:09,350 --> 00:15:12,180
如果这两位不是那么如胶似漆的话
Well, if these two will keep their sweaty paws off each other

355
00:15:12,180 --> 00:15:13,740
我就解释给你们听
for half a second, I'll explain.

356
00:15:13,740 --> 00:15:15,570
这是因为几天前...
It all started a couple days ago...

357
00:15:15,770 --> 00:15:17,420
我想带你去见我的朋友
I want you to meet my friends.

358
00:15:17,420 --> 00:15:18,840
我应该紧张吗
Should I be nervous?

359
00:15:18,840 --> 00:15:20,810
就像你带我回家见家长一样
Is it like bringing me home to meet your parents?

360
00:15:20,870 --> 00:15:21,940
不  不  不
No, no, no.

361
00:15:22,010 --> 00:15:23,640
比见家长更有压力
Much more stressful than that.

362
00:15:23,710 --> 00:15:25,880
我的朋友们虽然很棒  但又自以为是
You see, my friends, while awesome, can be presumptuous,

363
00:15:25,950 --> 00:15:28,380
爱管闲事  搞砸事情功夫一流
meddlesome and downright destructive.

364
00:15:28,450 --> 00:15:30,720
当他们知道你的职业  知道我们如何邂逅
When they learn what you do and how we met,

365
00:15:30,780 --> 00:15:32,280
他们很可能会想办法拆散我们
they'll probably try to break us up.

366
00:15:33,030 --> 00:15:34,490
不如我们就将计就计
So let's have some fun with them.

367
00:15:34,490 --> 00:15:35,880
陪他们玩玩
Mess with their heads.

368
00:15:35,880 --> 00:15:38,890
你是说  整人计划吗
Are you saying... evil plan?

369
00:15:38,960 --> 00:15:40,750
正是此意
Hells to the yes.

370
00:15:40,750 --> 00:15:42,730
天啊  你真撩人
My God, you're hot.

371
00:15:42,800 --> 00:15:44,010
等等
Wait for it.

372
00:15:44,320 --> 00:15:45,600
我们的计划如下
Here's what we do.

373
00:15:45,900 --> 00:15:48,900
我会让泰德发誓不向任何人透露有关你的事
<i>I'll make Ted swear not to tell</i> <i>anyone what he knows about you,</i>

374
00:15:48,970 --> 00:15:50,500
他肯定会立马跑去泄密
<i>and he'll cave immediately.</i>

375
00:15:50,570 --> 00:15:52,600
巴尼跟一个会把他钱骗光光的脱衣舞娘好上了
Barney's dating a stripper who's gonna steal all his money!

376
00:15:52,670 --> 00:15:54,010
接着  我们邀请大伙来做客
<i>Next, we invite everyone over.</i>

377
00:15:54,010 --> 00:15:55,260
我会不断征求你的意见
<i>I'll keep saying stuff like:</i>

378
00:15:55,260 --> 00:15:57,440
要端鹰嘴豆泥出来吗  兔兔宝贝
Is it okay if I put out the hummus, bunny face?

379
00:15:57,510 --> 00:15:58,430
我则摆出悍妇的样子来回答
<i>And I'll be the bossy</i> <i>bitch who says:</i>

380
00:15:58,430 --> 00:16:01,490
不许  留着当甜点  白痴
No, save it for dessert, idiot.

381
00:16:01,490 --> 00:16:02,480
太棒了
<i>Nice.</i>

382
00:16:02,550 --> 00:16:03,820
最后  我们会宣布
<i>And, finally, we'll announce...</i>

383
00:16:03,880 --> 00:16:05,280
我们俩要同居了
We're moving in together!

384
00:16:05,350 --> 00:16:06,720
我有个主意
I've got an idea.

385
00:16:06,850 --> 00:16:08,250
让你的朋友泰德和罗宾
Let's get your friends Ted and Robin

386
00:16:08,250 --> 00:16:09,990
一起争夺我的公寓吧
fighting over my apartment.

387
00:16:09,990 --> 00:16:11,770
等等   这对于咱俩有啥好处吗
Wait, what does that have to do with you and me?

388
00:16:11,770 --> 00:16:13,490
没好处  我就爱损人不利己
Nothing. I just worship chaos.

389
00:16:13,490 --> 00:16:15,230
你真是让我欲火焚身
I can't handle how hot you are right now.

390
00:16:15,230 --> 00:16:17,580
-再等等  -接下来
- Wait for it. - Next,

391
00:16:17,580 --> 00:16:20,020
他们会劝我和你分手
<i>they'll try to talk me</i> <i>into dumping you.</i>

392
00:16:20,020 --> 00:16:21,260
我则正好撞见此事
<i>And I'll walk in on it.</i>

393
00:16:21,260 --> 00:16:22,670
然后我们假装分手
<i>Then we pretend to break up.</i>

394
00:16:22,670 --> 00:16:23,950
当他们回来
<i>And when they crawl back,</i>

395
00:16:23,950 --> 00:16:25,330
跪求我的原谅时
<i>begging for forgiveness...</i>

396
00:16:25,330 --> 00:16:27,750
我就装出大人有大量的样子  原谅他们
<i>I'll be the bigger man</i> <i>and let them off the hook.</i>

397
00:16:27,750 --> 00:16:29,880
又或者  将他们玩弄于股掌之间
<i>Or make the monkeys</i> <i>dance for you.</i>

398
00:16:29,880 --> 00:16:31,490
我的天啊  你太有才了
<i>God, you're smart!</i>

399
00:16:31,840 --> 00:16:34,450
这将会成为传
It's gonna be legen...

400
00:16:34,510 --> 00:16:36,940
我再也等不了了
I'm not waiting for it anymore.

401
00:16:37,120 --> 00:16:38,820
奇
...dary.

402
00:16:40,450 --> 00:16:42,890
我的天啊  你们俩真是
My God, you two are...

403
00:16:42,960 --> 00:16:44,450
天造地设的一对
Perfect together.

404
00:16:44,450 --> 00:16:46,260
所以你不打算搬进来了吗
So you're not really moving in?

405
00:16:46,260 --> 00:16:48,100
一开始我们只是开玩笑而已
Well, it started out as a joke,

406
00:16:48,100 --> 00:16:49,640
可当我们越深入地谈这事
but the more we talked about it...

407
00:16:49,640 --> 00:16:50,880
就越起劲
The more excited we got.

408
00:16:50,880 --> 00:16:53,440
所以没错  我们要同居了
So, yeah, we are.

409
00:16:53,830 --> 00:16:56,740
你们对此有何意见吗
You have anything to say about that?

410
00:16:57,640 --> 00:16:59,440
-为你们俩高兴  -恭喜了
- So happy for you. - Congratulations.

411
00:17:01,570 --> 00:17:02,610
谢谢你们
Thank you.

412
00:17:02,680 --> 00:17:03,780
谢了
Thank you.

413
00:17:05,040 --> 00:17:06,980
你俩明白这就意味着
You two realize this means

414
00:17:06,980 --> 00:17:09,180
我的公寓真的要出租了  对吧
my apartment really is up for grabs, right?

415
00:17:11,360 --> 00:17:12,860
我一定能找到其他住所的
I'm sure I'll find something else.

416
00:17:12,860 --> 00:17:14,660
我也是
Me, too.

417
00:17:14,660 --> 00:17:18,160
<i>这就是我们和昆茵相识的经过</i>
<i>And that's the story</i> <i>of how we met Quinn.</i>

418
00:17:18,160 --> 00:17:22,160
<i>周五  我和罗宾碰面详谈"炒鱿鱼专点"的事</i>
<i>That Friday, I met Robin to see</i> <i>how it went at "fire o'clock."</i>

419
00:17:22,230 --> 00:17:24,640
他们调我去主持直播达人秀
They promoted me to on-air talent.

420
00:17:24,640 --> 00:17:27,100
我将成为桑迪·里维斯的新主持搭档
I'm gonna be Sandy Rivers' new co-host.

421
00:17:27,100 --> 00:17:28,580
我的天
Oh, my God!

422
00:17:28,580 --> 00:17:29,590
怎么会这样
How'd that happen?

423
00:17:29,590 --> 00:17:30,950
还记得跨年夜吗
Remember New Year's Eve?

424
00:17:30,950 --> 00:17:33,150
我临时代替桑迪主持  结果
<i>When I filled in for Sandy,</i> <i>it turns out</i>

425
00:17:33,150 --> 00:17:35,510
环球新闻的执行总裁很喜欢我
the C.E.O. of <i>World Wide News</i> liked me.

426
00:17:35,510 --> 00:17:37,010
他说我挺"带种"的
He said I have "moxie."

427
00:17:37,010 --> 00:17:38,930
他是四十年代的黑帮分子吗
So he's a 1940s gangster?

428
00:17:38,930 --> 00:17:40,160
显然是的
Apparently.

429
00:17:40,890 --> 00:17:42,950
我的薪水涨了不少
And I got a big raise,

430
00:17:42,980 --> 00:17:46,420
所以我决定租下中央公园西区的公寓
so I'm taking this apartment on Central Park West,

431
00:17:46,420 --> 00:17:47,730
这就意味着
which means...

432
00:17:47,730 --> 00:17:48,980
昆茵的公寓
Quinn's apartment.

433
00:17:48,980 --> 00:17:50,330
我已经告诉她那房子归你了
I already told her you'd take it.

434
00:17:51,870 --> 00:17:53,930
多谢了
Wow. Thanks.

435
00:17:53,930 --> 00:17:54,720
没事
Yeah.

436
00:17:55,120 --> 00:17:56,280
也祝贺你
Hey, and congrats.

437
00:17:56,280 --> 00:17:57,950
你真的是名至实归
You deserve it all.

438
00:17:59,670 --> 00:18:02,250
我一直在考虑那件事
You know, I've been thinking about it, and...

439
00:18:03,800 --> 00:18:04,930
我可以跟你重新做回朋友
I can do normal.

440
00:18:06,050 --> 00:18:07,200
为重新做回朋友干杯
To back to normal.

441
00:18:07,200 --> 00:18:08,330
为重新做回朋友干杯
To back to normal.

442
00:18:17,710 --> 00:18:19,950
-我该走了  -行
- Uh... I-I should get going. - Yeah.

443
00:18:19,950 --> 00:18:21,470
-你还有好多事要办呢  -没错
- You've got a lot to do. - Totally.

444
00:18:21,470 --> 00:18:22,620
那就  回头见吧
So... Um, see you soon.

445
00:18:22,690 --> 00:18:23,510
回头见
See you soon.

446
00:18:23,510 --> 00:18:24,870
好
Yeah.

447
00:18:25,390 --> 00:18:27,230
<i>后来我们很长一段时间没有见面</i>
<i>We wouldn't see each other</i> <i>for a long time.</i>

448
00:18:28,030 --> 00:18:29,930
<i>不过这事以后再说</i>
<i>But I'll get to that.</i>

449
00:18:30,150 --> 00:18:31,510
听着
Listen, um...

450
00:18:32,230 --> 00:18:34,650
关于我在十年级时和珍娜·克里斯托莉
about me getting to second base in tenth grade

451
00:18:34,650 --> 00:18:36,400
进行到二垒的事
with Jenna Cristalli...

452
00:18:36,400 --> 00:18:37,770
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.

453
00:18:37,770 --> 00:18:40,270
我早就把那小贱货给忘了
I've already forgotten about that dumb hobag.

454
00:18:40,270 --> 00:18:44,350
那事不是在我俩看《彼得潘》时发生的
Yeah, um, it didn't happen while we were watching <i>Peter Pan.</i>

455
00:18:44,350 --> 00:18:48,370
而是在我扮演彼得潘时发生的
It happened while I was playing Peter Pan.

456
00:18:49,140 --> 00:18:51,030
这里有我演出时的照片
Here's a photo from the day I was cast.

457
00:18:51,320 --> 00:18:52,980
中间那娃就是我
That's me in the middle.

458
00:18:52,980 --> 00:18:56,050
当时我正值生长迅猛期
But then I had my growth spurt.

459
00:18:56,230 --> 00:18:59,010
演出当晚  我已经长到套不进悬空安全带了
By opening night, I was too big for the flying harness,

460
00:18:59,010 --> 00:19:00,550
于是乎
and, well...

461
00:19:03,720 --> 00:19:07,990
我摔在珍娜·克里斯托莉身上  双手先着胸
I fell hands-first right onto Jenna Cristalli.

462
00:19:07,990 --> 00:19:10,540
她在胸罩里塞的那堆纸巾让我免于双腕骨折
The tissues in her bra saved me two broken wrists.

463
00:19:10,540 --> 00:19:11,810
抱歉  我只是想要有件
I'm sorry. I just, I just wanted

464
00:19:11,810 --> 00:19:14,360
主角不是你的劲爆性事
to have one cool sex story that wasn't you.

465
00:19:14,640 --> 00:19:16,370
好吧  下次你就说
Okay. Next time you tell it,

466
00:19:16,370 --> 00:19:18,040
你偷开了你爸的车
you were in your dad's car,

467
00:19:18,040 --> 00:19:21,300
带她去看金属乐队的演唱会
which you stole to go to a Metallica concert,

468
00:19:21,300 --> 00:19:24,560
然后你和那浪货成功冲上三垒
and you got to third base with that slut.

469
00:19:21,300 --> 00:19:24,560
{\an8}三垒  指爱抚触摸私密部位

470
00:19:27,990 --> 00:19:29,690
我曾经和某个妞有过一腿
I was once with this chick...

471
00:19:31,150 --> 00:19:33,500
她是世上最棒的老婆
who is just the best wife ever.

472
00:19:37,310 --> 00:19:39,400
谢谢你不介意我的工作
Thank you for being so cool about what I do.

473
00:19:39,470 --> 00:19:41,450
好多男人对这事不是纠结就是嫉妒
A lot of guys would be weird or jealous.

474
00:19:41,450 --> 00:19:42,400
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?

475
00:19:42,470 --> 00:19:44,840
我有什么资格来说别人  我自己就坏透了
Who am I to judge anyone? I'm the devil!

476
00:19:49,750 --> 00:19:52,380
当然如果你不想跳了  我肯定举双手赞成
I mean, if you ever wanted to stop stripping, I'd support it.

477
00:19:52,450 --> 00:19:54,680
前提是你不想
If you wanted... to.

478
00:19:54,750 --> 00:19:56,820
所以你还是嫉妒咯
So, you are jealous?

479
00:19:56,880 --> 00:19:59,100
什么  才不是  真没有
What? No, no, not at all.

480
00:19:59,100 --> 00:20:01,950
我只是说  有天你不想宽衣解带了
I'm just saying, if you ever wanted to hang up the old G-string,

481
00:20:01,950 --> 00:20:03,630
我完全理解你的决定
I'd completely understand.

482
00:20:03,630 --> 00:20:06,670
不要  我喜欢为钱宽衣解带
Nah, I like taking my clothes off for money.

483
00:20:06,670 --> 00:20:07,980
很好
Great.

484
00:20:07,980 --> 00:20:09,480
听我  听我把话说完
Let me... let me finish.

485
00:20:10,130 --> 00:20:14,570
假设说  什么才能让你不跳呢
Hypothetically, what would make you stop?

486
00:20:14,630 --> 00:20:16,940
假如说...
Hypothetically...

487
00:20:17,000 --> 00:20:20,930
哪天我结婚了  我就不跳脱衣舞了
I would stop stripping if I ever got married.

488
00:20:22,750 --> 00:20:23,700
晚安
Good night.

489
00:20:30,210 --> 00:20:33,450
于是我们决定"重新做回朋友"
And then we agreed to "go back to normal."

490
00:20:34,110 --> 00:20:38,100
可我开始怀疑我们是否能够只做朋友
But I'm starting to wonder if we can ever really just be friends.

491
00:20:39,690 --> 00:20:44,530
总之  这就是我和罗宾从05年起纠结至今的故事
Anyway, that's the story of me and Robin, 2005 to the present.

492
00:20:44,910 --> 00:20:46,220
你们怎么看
What do you think?

493
00:20:46,220 --> 00:20:49,050
我觉得你这故事比一匹布还长
I think your stories are way too long.

494
00:20:49,050 --> 00:20:52,070
我真替他未来的小孩难过
I feel bad for his future kids, dude.

495
00:20:52,800 --> 00:20:57,040
我的孩子肯定爱听我的故事
Hey, my kids are gonna love my stories.

496
00:20:58,900 --> 00:21:01,700
他们肯定爱死这些故事了
They're gonna... yeah, they're gonna love my stories.

