1
00:00:00,211 --> 00:00:04,654
{\a6}中央公园 1994年

1
00:00:00,502 --> 00:00:04,859
1994年 罗宾的爸爸带她第一次来到纽约城
In 1994, Robin's dad took her to New York City for the first time...

2
00:00:03,509 --> 00:00:04,859


3
00:00:04,861 --> 00:00:07,361
这里棒极了 谢谢你 先生
This is amazing! Thank you, sir!

4
00:00:07,363 --> 00:00:09,947
是啊 这种增进情感的父子同游是没什么坏处
Wella little father-son bonding trip never hurt anyone.

5
00:00:09,949 --> 00:00:12,783
不过去年我们一起出来打狼那次
I-I did almost die from malnutrition

6
00:00:12,785 --> 00:00:14,518
我确实差点饿死
on that wolf hunt last year...

7
00:00:14,520 --> 00:00:16,520
我必须亲手将你推入将死之绝境
I had to almost kill you 

8
00:00:16,522 --> 00:00:17,738
你才能领悟杀戮之奥义
for you to learn how to kill.

9
00:00:17,740 --> 00:00:20,6 91
纽约城真是极好的诶
New York City's the best, eh?

10
00:00:20,693 --> 00:00:22,043
我倒不是挺喜欢 这里就像是埃德蒙顿
I despise it. It's like Edmonton,

11
00:00:20,693 --> 00:00:22,043
{\a6}埃德蒙顿 加拿大西南部城市

11
00:00:22,045 --> 00:00:23,911
还少了些艺术和文化
minus the arts and culture.

12
00:00:23,913 --> 00:00:25,162
快走吧 不然赶不上航班了
Come on, we'll miss our flight.

13
00:00:25,164 --> 00:00:26,747
我会跟上的
I'll catch up.

14
00:00:28,533 --> 00:00:31,201
将来某一天 我将搬来这里 
One day, I'm gonna move here,

15
00:00:31,203 --> 00:00:34,422
嫁给一个久经世故的大城市人
marry a sophisticated big-city man

16
00:00:34,424 --> 00:00:36,474
他脑后那帅到窒息的秀发
with a sick mullet--

16
00:00:34,424 --> 00:00:36,474
{\a6}mullet 一种前短后长的发型

17
00:00:36,476 --> 00:00:39,543
一直垂到他的垫肩上
like all the way down to his shoulder pads,

18
00:00:39,545 --> 00:00:40,561
到了晚上 
and at night,

19
00:00:40,563 --> 00:00:43,047
还会让我帮他梳理
he'll let me brush it...

20
00:00:43,049 --> 00:00:46,934
到时候我会来挖出这个吊坠小盒
and I'll dig up this locket

21
00:00:46,936 --> 00:00:51,388
作为我们婚礼上的"旧物"
so it can be my "Something old" At our wedding.

21
00:00:46,936 --> 00:00:51,398
{\a6}西方人婚礼上的习俗

22
00:00:52,190 --> 00:00:53,223
二罗
R.J.!

23
00:00:53,225 --> 00:00:54,658
来了 先生
Coming, sir!

24
00:00:56,394 --> 00:00:57,995
我会回来找你的
I'll be back for you.

24
00:01:00,000 --> 00:01:03,630
{\a6}2013年

25
00:01:00,582 --> 00:01:03,934
当年 我很不好意思把我做的这些事告诉你
Back then, I was embarrassed to tell you I've done that

26
00:01:03,936 --> 00:01:04,969
不过现在我们既然更亲近了
but we're closer now.

27
00:01:06,222 --> 00:01:08,189
我也不用再对你隐藏我阴柔的一面了
I feel like I don't have to hide my feminine side anymore

28
00:01:08,191 --> 00:01:09,473
只是因为你一直想要一个...
just because you've always wanted a...

29
00:01:09,475 --> 00:01:11,475
儿子 是巴尼
Son! It's Barney!

30
00:01:11,477 --> 00:01:13,060
太好了
Great!

31
00:01:13,062 --> 00:01:14,695
我15分钟后赶到 小巴狗 
I'll be there in 15, B-dawg.

32
00:01:14,697 --> 00:01:16,097
汪汪
Woof, woof!

33
00:01:18,568 --> 00:01:20,017
这是我俩的暗号
That's our thing.

34
00:01:20,019 --> 00:01:21,702
呃 15分钟后去哪儿  
Uh... be where in 15?

35
00:01:21,704 --> 00:01:22,787
真人激光枪
Laser tag.

36
00:01:22,789 --> 00:01:24,572
从来没玩过 小巴狗会教我的
Never been. B-dawg's gonna teach me.

37
00:01:24,574 --> 00:01:28,125
呃 我觉得这样很好 你和巴尼...
Look, I-I think that it's great that you and Barney are...

38
00:01:28,127 --> 00:01:28,959
是小巴狗
B-dawg.

39
00:01:28,961 --> 00:01:31,662
...和小巴狗建立了感情
...B-dawg are bonding,

40
00:01:31,664 --> 00:01:34,364
但是 呃 你答应过要来帮我的
but, um... you agreed to help me with this.

41
00:01:34,366 --> 00:01:35,800
好吧
Fine.

42
00:01:35,802 --> 00:01:37,718
你把卫生棉埋在哪儿了
Where did you bury this tampon?

43
00:01:37,720 --> 00:01:38,719
那是个吊坠小盒
It's a locket.

44
00:01:38,721 --> 00:01:39,737
抱歉 我老是把这些
I'm sorry, I get all these

45
00:01:39,739 --> 00:01:42,373
小女孩的东西搞混
girlie things confused.

46
00:01:42,375 --> 00:01:44,425
你到底需不需要我帮忙
Do you need my help or not?

47
00:01:45,811 --> 00:01:47,728
算了 蠢得要死
Nah, it's stupid.

48
00:01:49,515 --> 00:01:51,882
当罗宾在寻找她的"旧物"的时候
So while Robin searched for her something old,

49
00:01:51,884 --> 00:01:54,268
莉莉和马修在打包他们的新物了
Lily and Marshall packed for their something new:

50
00:01:54,270 --> 00:01:56,504
莉莉要去意大利做为期一年的艺术顾问
Lily's year-long art consultant gig in Italy.

51
00:01:56,506 --> 00:01:58,555
我还是不愿相信
I still can't believe

52
00:01:58,557 --> 00:02:00,524
我们还是得跟这地方告别了
we have to say goodbye to this place...

53
00:02:00,526 --> 00:02:02,443
哦 我知道 宝贝 
Oh. I know, baby.

54
00:02:02,445 --> 00:02:04,912
但这可以被当作我们简化自己生活的好理由
But look at it as an excuse to simplify our lives.

55
00:02:04,914 --> 00:02:06,580
你明白 我们没法带着所有东西去意大利
You know, we can't bring everything to Italy,

56
00:02:06,582 --> 00:02:08,082
肯定得丢掉一些垃圾
so we gotta throw out some junk.

57
00:02:08,084 --> 00:02:10,668
比如说 看这个
For example, look...

58
00:02:10,670 --> 00:02:12,036
我以前的大脚怪追踪记录 
my old Sasquatch binders

59
00:02:12,038 --> 00:02:14,121
这个我一辈子都不会扔掉的
that "I could never throw away"

60
00:02:14,123 --> 00:02:15,923
因为我将会成为
because "I was gonna be the guy

61
00:02:15,925 --> 00:02:17,675
证明大脚怪存在的人
who proved the existence of Bigfoot..."

62
00:02:17,677 --> 00:02:18,909
这些必须带去意大利
These are obviously coming to Italy.

63
00:02:18,911 --> 00:02:20,127
而这些手提包 
But these handbags?

64
00:02:20,129 --> 00:02:21,212
就拜拜咯 
Gonzo.

65
00:02:21,214 --> 00:02:22,513
没门
No way!

66
00:02:22,515 --> 00:02:25,582
这些寄托着我深深的感伤呢
These have sentimental meaning to me.

67
00:02:25,584 --> 00:02:27,384
这些不是你20多岁那会从商店顺出来的吗
Didn't you shop-lift these in your 20s?

68
00:02:27,386 --> 00:02:29,937
是啊 我好怀念那段时光的说
Yes, and I get very nostalgic for that time.

69
00:02:29,939 --> 00:02:33,257
等人老了 有娃了 只能金盆洗手了 多伤感啊
You get older, you have kids, you stop stealing, it's sad.

70
00:02:33,259 --> 00:02:34,275
莉莉
Lily...

71
00:02:34,277 --> 00:02:35,759
只是我们没那么多地方当这些了
we just don't have room for these.

72
00:02:35,761 --> 00:02:38,896
可不 你的大脚怪文件夹倒是可以留着吗
Oh, but you get to keep your Bigfoot binders?

73
00:02:38,898 --> 00:02:42,432
等等 为什么这本只到1999年12月
Wait, why is this one just December 1999?

74
00:02:42,434 --> 00:02:44,952
哦 当时千禧年要来了
Oh. Y2K was coming.

75
00:02:44,954 --> 00:02:47,988
很多人逃到树林里面去
Lot of people took to the woods.

76
00:02:47,990 --> 00:02:49,740
看到了真相
Saw the truth.

77
00:02:49,742 --> 00:02:53,043
好了 马修 我们没时间争论
Okay, Marshall, we don't have time to argue

78
00:02:53,045 --> 00:02:54,778
什么丢掉什么留了
over what stays and what goes.

79
00:02:54,780 --> 00:02:56,881
哦 你知道我们该叫谁来吗
Ooh, you know who we gotta bring in?

80
00:02:56,883 --> 00:02:59,834
好吧 我承认他在这方面是有两把刷子 
Okay, I agree he is good at this stuff,

81
00:02:59,836 --> 00:03:01,836
但他真心好臭屁啊
but he just gets so cocky.

82
00:03:01,838 --> 00:03:03,120
他才没有呢
No, he doesn't.

83
00:03:06,457 --> 00:03:08,943
听说你们遇到了一点... 
So I heard you guys have a bit of a...

84
00:03:08,945 --> 00:03:11,512
打包困难
packing situation.

85
00:03:11,514 --> 00:03:13,797
现在我同意这是个错误的决定
I acknowledge now this was a mistake.

86
00:03:13,799 --> 00:03:17,101
听着 我是过来嚼泡泡糖顺便帮你们打包的
Look, I came here to chew bubblegum and pack boxes.

87
00:03:17,103 --> 00:03:19,820
现在我没有泡泡...
And I'm all out of bubble...

88
00:03:19,822 --> 00:03:21,972
哦 我的天哪... 哦 天哪
Oh, my God.... Oh, my God.

89
00:03:21,974 --> 00:03:24,441
我给吞下去了
I swallowed it.

90
00:03:24,443 --> 00:03:25,976
这严重不
Is that bad?

91
00:03:25,878 --> 00:03:27,500
{\a6}12分钟后

91
00:03:25,978 --> 00:03:27,495
好的 谢谢了
Okay, thank you.

92
00:03:27,497 --> 00:03:29,246
好了 戈德史密斯医生说我应该没事
Well, Dr. Goldsmith says I should be fine.

93
00:03:29,248 --> 00:03:31,081
我只需要在如厕的时候注意找下了
I just have to look for it in my stool.

94
00:03:31,867 --> 00:03:34,451
所以正如我所说的
So as I was saying

95
00:03:34,453 --> 00:03:36,520
听说你们遇到了一点... 
I heard you guys have a bit of a...

96
00:03:36,522 --> 00:03:39,043
打包困难
packing situation.

1
00:03:40,411 --> 00:03:42,411
{\a1}{\fs17}　　　　 老爸\N　　　  　　 老妈\N　　 　　 浪漫史\N{\fs16}{\bord1}{\3c&H00DCE1&}　　  　　　　第八季  第二十三集\N
{\fnDaxlinePro-Regular}{\fs19}{\b0}{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\3c&H2F2F2F&}{\4c&H000000&}{\a1}　　　　　S08E23 Something Old

2
00:03:42,521 --> 00:03:45,521
{\fs16}翻译: @卟哒哒伽马 @小白是憎恶 @Big-Fudge @moonywen文妹\N{\3c&H00DCE1&}{\bord1}@KRengine达 @轩然AI简 @纷扬DLL @Mr_Gao703\N{\3c&H007EFF&}校对: @我叫肉鸭鸭 @晒小花

3
00:03:45,522 --> 00:03:48,522
{\fs17}{\3c&H00DCE1&}{\bord1}压制: @Big-Fudge\N{\3c&H007EFF&}统筹+后期: 怒TR不愿统筹肉小鸭 怒TR不愿后期晒小花

4
00:03:48,806 --> 00:03:51,206
HIMYM字幕组 倾情奉献

100
00:03:51,970 --> 00:03:53,804
你俩都知道
Now, as you know,

101
00:03:53,806 --> 00:03:57,041
提到打包领域 我也算是传奇人物
I'm a bit of a legend when it comes to packing.

102
00:03:57,043 --> 00:03:58,726
知道×2
-We know. -We know.

103
00:03:58,728 --> 00:04:00,444
至今仍流传着
Tales are still told

104
00:04:00,446 --> 00:04:03,030
我在西班牙旅行
of the time I traveled all through Spain...

105
00:04:04,515 --> 00:04:06,734
为期两周的神话
for two weeks.

106
00:04:07,852 --> 00:04:09,787
无论我需要什么
with everything I needed

107
00:04:09,789 --> 00:04:13,624
我那免提小书包 应有尽有
efficiently packed into a hands-free belt satchel.

108
00:04:13,626 --> 00:04:15,525
当地人惊呼我为
The locals called me...

1000
00:04:16,126 --> 00:04:18,925
拥有小书包的多啦A梦

109
00:04:22,133 --> 00:04:25,052
好吧 那才不是什么免提小书包
Yeah, it's not a "Hands-free belt satchel," Ted.

110
00:04:25,054 --> 00:04:26,053
是腰包
It's a fanny pack.

111
00:04:26,055 --> 00:04:27,838
才不是腰包
It's not a fanny pack.

112
00:04:27,840 --> 00:04:30,925
还有在西班牙语 那句话是
In Spanish, El Ganso con la Riñonera

113
00:04:30,927 --> 00:04:32,760
腰包呆子
means "Fanny Pack Dork."

114
00:04:32,762 --> 00:04:33,928
才不是
No, it doesn't.

115
00:04:33,930 --> 00:04:36,380
翻译过来是"整理巧手"
It means "Packer of Great Skill and Merit."

116
00:04:36,382 --> 00:04:37,598
我查了
I looked it up.

117
00:04:37,600 --> 00:04:39,767
意思的确是"腰包呆子"
It means"Fanny Pack Dork."

118
00:04:39,769 --> 00:04:42,719
作为整理巧手界的砖家
And as a Packer of Great Skill and Merit,

119
00:04:42,721 --> 00:04:46,240
我将想你们讲解 如何做到俄罗斯方块般的严丝合缝
I will tell you how to pack with Tetris-like precision.

120
00:04:46,242 --> 00:04:48,776
懂了 看到啥都塞你腰包里
We get it, you pack a lot in your fanny.

121
00:04:48,778 --> 00:04:50,444
言之有理
Obvious yet delightful.

122
00:04:50,446 --> 00:04:51,495
好的
Okay.

123
00:04:51,497 --> 00:04:52,980
下午三点 我有个重要面试
I got a big interview at 3:00

124
00:04:52,982 --> 00:04:54,415
关系到我有没有可能去设计另一幢大楼
about possibly designing another building.

125
00:04:54,417 --> 00:04:57,234
在那之前 如果你们遵从我的条令
Until then, if you abide by my rulings,

126
00:04:57,236 --> 00:04:59,403
我将为你们决定哪些带去意大利
I will tell you what goes to Italy

127
00:04:59,405 --> 00:05:02,923
哪些丢入大三角
and what goes in... The Triangle.

128
00:05:02,925 --> 00:05:08,545
{\a6}S05E03中有记载

128
00:05:02,925 --> 00:05:05,676
孩子们 你们都知道 百慕达大三角
Kids, as you know, "The Bermuda Triangle"

129
00:05:05,678 --> 00:05:08,545
是我们给公寓门前那块地取的名字
was the name we gave to the curb right outside our apartment,

131
00:05:08,547 --> 00:05:13,601
那里有着让一切化为乌有的魔力
which possessed the magical ability to make any item disappear.

133
00:05:13,603 --> 00:05:14,802
瞬间吞噬
Instantly.

134
00:05:14,804 --> 00:05:16,920
清理中最重要的一条法则便是
The biggest rule for de-cluttering is,

135
00:05:16,922 --> 00:05:19,974
这玩意儿你一年之内是否用过
"Have you used it in the last year?"

136
00:05:19,976 --> 00:05:22,643
没用过的话 大三角里呆着去
If not... Triangle.

137
00:05:23,612 --> 00:05:26,397
一年内你跳过绳么
Have you used this jump rope in the last year?

138
00:05:26,399 --> 00:05:27,399
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?

139
00:05:27,400 --> 00:05:29,283
我天天早上都跳绳 小子
I hop threads every morning, son!

140
00:05:29,285 --> 00:05:31,485
连跳三个 你就能留下它
Do three in a row and you can keep it.

141
00:05:34,339 --> 00:05:35,406
算你狠 莫斯比
Well-played, Mosby.

142
00:05:35,408 --> 00:05:37,791
下一个
Next!

143
00:05:39,327 --> 00:05:41,078
这玩意儿你一年之内是否用过
Have you used it in the last year?

144
00:05:41,080 --> 00:05:44,298
天 我忘了
Gee, I can't remember.

145
00:05:47,585 --> 00:05:49,003
你是在贿赂我吗
Are you trying to bribe me?

146
00:05:50,055 --> 00:05:51,505
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.

147
00:05:51,507 --> 00:05:52,606
拿着
Take it.

148
00:05:52,608 --> 00:05:53,691
大三角
Triangle!

149
00:05:54,793 --> 00:05:55,959
下一个
Next!

150
00:05:59,315 --> 00:06:02,149
哇 你可真是块材料啊 爸爸
Wow, you're a natural... Dad.

151
00:06:02,984 --> 00:06:04,485
你明白 我爱罗宾
You know, I love Robin.

152
00:06:04,487 --> 00:06:06,170
我也算是爱她妹妹
And her sister's okay, I guess.

153
00:06:06,172 --> 00:06:09,657
可这些都抵不上最终能拥有一个
But there's something nice about finally having...

154
00:06:09,659 --> 00:06:10,858
儿子
a son.

155
00:06:10,860 --> 00:06:12,660
一个儿...
A s...

156
00:06:13,478 --> 00:06:15,312
我...
I...

157
00:06:15,314 --> 00:06:16,514
克里斯托利双胞胎 九点钟方向
Cristalli twins, nine o'clock!

158
00:06:19,585 --> 00:06:21,651
现在做回你妈咪的卵子 滚走吧
Now make like your mommy's ovum and split!

159
00:06:22,655 --> 00:06:25,039
极好的生物笑话 小巴狗
Solid biology joke, B-dawg.

160
00:06:25,041 --> 00:06:26,373
汪 汪
Woof, woof!

161
00:06:27,460 --> 00:06:29,793
我承认 对于那种未经训练的新兵
Now, I'll admit, to the untrained eye,

163
00:06:29,795 --> 00:06:32,262
有几条打包条令看上去可能有点武断
a few of my packing rulings may have seemed arbitrary.

165
00:06:32,264 --> 00:06:35,015
《去意大利吧》 进大三角
Let's Go Italy? Triangle.

166
00:06:35,800 --> 00:06:37,000
大三角铁
Triangle...

167
00:06:37,002 --> 00:06:38,168
去意大利吧
let's go Italy.

168
00:06:39,471 --> 00:06:42,639
一套大猩猩服和一顶金色假发
A gorilla suit and a blonde wig.

169
00:06:42,641 --> 00:06:44,558
你们去年有用过这些吗
Have you used either of these in the last year?

170
00:06:48,898 --> 00:06:50,731
嫔妾求你了 金刚嬷嬷
Please, Queen Kong...

171
00:06:50,733 --> 00:06:52,349
若能温柔些便是极好的了
be gentle.

172
00:06:54,570 --> 00:06:55,953
没 从来没用过
Nope, haven't used those.

173
00:06:55,955 --> 00:06:57,435
我觉得这东西根本就不是我们的
I don't think those even belong to us.

174
00:06:58,573 --> 00:07:00,407
好了 这个容易决定
Okay, here's an easy one.

175
00:07:00,409 --> 00:07:03,961
一个用了十年的 还破了洞的豆袋椅
A leaky, ten-year-old beanbag chair

176
00:07:03,963 --> 00:07:06,130
上面满是啤酒和水烟渍
covered in beer, bong water

177
00:07:06,132 --> 00:07:09,583
还有早已风干的吃清凉牧场味多力多滋留下的手指印子
and fossilized Cool Ranch Doritos fingerprints.

178
00:07:09,585 --> 00:07:10,634
去意大利
Italy.

179
00:07:10,636 --> 00:07:13,003
再给大软糖说一遍\N　\N　
Vieni ancora per Fudge Grande?

180
00:07:13,005 --> 00:07:15,556
伙计们 这椅子都已经在这儿生根了
Guys, this chair has been here forever.

181
00:07:15,558 --> 00:07:16,840
你们一定得带着它
You gotta take it with you.

182
00:07:16,842 --> 00:07:18,425
-去意大利  -泰德
- Italy. - Ted...

183
00:07:18,427 --> 00:07:22,229
意大利不需要这样皱巴巴 红彤彤 漏洞百出
Italy doesn't need something that is wrinkled, red and leaky,

185
00:07:22,231 --> 00:07:24,598
还外加一股酒精加毒品味的东西
and smells like booze and narcotics.

186
00:07:24,600 --> 00:07:27,401
他们已经有前总理西尔维奥•贝卢斯科尼了
They've already got former Prime Minister Silvio Berlusconi.

187
00:07:28,687 --> 00:07:30,237
完全不知道那是谁
I don't know who that is.

188
00:07:30,239 --> 00:07:32,689
这些都是终审裁决
All rulings are final.

189
00:07:32,691 --> 00:07:35,993
好吧 为什么我们喜欢的东西都放到大三角
Okay, why are things that we like getting "Triangled"

190
00:07:35,995 --> 00:07:38,729
-你喜欢的垃圾却留下了  -比如什么
-and crap you like sneaks through? -Like what?

191
00:07:38,731 --> 00:07:40,998
比如那个重达50磅的老点唱机
That old 50-pound karaoke machine.

192
00:07:41,000 --> 00:07:42,082
得了吧
Come on!

193
00:07:42,084 --> 00:07:44,868
我们02年新年是唱着它度过的 还记得吗
We sang in the New Year in '02 on this thing, remember?

195
00:07:44,870 --> 00:07:46,787
我们就是天命真女啊
We were Destiny's Child!

196
00:07:49,257 --> 00:07:50,507
既然我是碧昂丝
And since I was Beyonce ,

197
00:07:50,509 --> 00:07:52,576
我十分确信最终裁定权归我 所以呢
I'm pretty sure I get final say here, so...

198
00:07:52,578 --> 00:07:54,711
我们可不是你的配唱 小贱人
Oh, we were not your backup singers, bitch,

199
00:07:54,713 --> 00:07:55,879
我们是个组合
we were a group.

200
00:07:55,881 --> 00:07:58,382
不好意思 是你们嫁给了Jay-Z
I'm sorry, are you guys married to Jay-Z,

201
00:07:58,384 --> 00:08:00,467
还是我嫁给了Jay-Z
or am I married to Jay-Z?

202
00:08:01,136 --> 00:08:02,386
带去意大利
Italy.

203
00:08:04,723 --> 00:08:06,723
哇
Wow.

204
00:08:06,725 --> 00:08:08,809
你把那个犯哮喘病的孩子
The way you used that kid having an asthma attack

205
00:08:08,811 --> 00:08:09,810
当做人盾这方法
as a human shield?

206
00:08:09,812 --> 00:08:11,478
真是犀利到让我也无法呼吸了
That took my breath away.

207
00:08:11,480 --> 00:08:13,263
好 那接下来
Yeah. Okay, next,

208
00:08:13,265 --> 00:08:14,982
我来突击 你卧倒掩护我
I'll be point guy and you lay down cover.

209
00:08:14,984 --> 00:08:16,433
-然后我...  -哇哦×N
-So I'm... -Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa...

210
00:08:16,435 --> 00:08:18,435
你的意思说不该让我当突击手吗
are you suggesting that I will not be point guy?

211
00:08:19,455 --> 00:08:21,121
听着 如果迈克尔•乔丹没有伤病缠身的话
Look, if Michael Jordan's healthy,

212
00:08:21,123 --> 00:08:23,373
你还会让斯科蒂•皮蓬去主导进攻吗
you don't let Scottie Pippen run the offense.

212
00:08:19,455 --> 00:08:23,373
{\a6}迈克尔•乔丹和斯科蒂•皮蓬均为NBA球员

213
00:08:24,242 --> 00:08:26,443
对了 你是加拿大人
Oh, you're from Canada, right.

214
00:08:26,445 --> 00:08:28,045
我该怎么说呢
If... how do I put this?

215
00:08:28,047 --> 00:08:30,581
如果韦恩•格雷茨基健康的话 你不会让
If Wayne Gretzky's healthy, you don't let...

215
00:08:28,047 --> 00:08:30,581
{\a6}韦恩•格雷茨基为加拿大职业冰球明星

216
00:08:30,583 --> 00:08:32,082
呃
uh...

217
00:08:32,084 --> 00:08:33,617
弗朗索瓦
Francois...

218
00:08:33,619 --> 00:08:37,971
我的意思是 冰球蠢毙了 而且我才是突击手
What I'm saying is: hockey is stupid and I'm point guy.

219
00:08:37,973 --> 00:08:40,257
行吧 要么我是突击手 要么我就离队
Well, I'm point guy or I'm off the team.

220
00:08:40,259 --> 00:08:43,177
你是我至今为止认识的最固执的家伙
Gah! You are the most stubborn human being I have ever met!

221
00:08:43,179 --> 00:08:44,228
那你最好给我习惯起来
You better get used to it...

222
00:08:44,230 --> 00:08:45,430
你娶的可是舍巴斯基家族的女人
you're marrying a Scherbatsky.

223
00:08:45,431 --> 00:08:47,981
你女儿连哪怕是一丝丝的如同你那样的
Your daughter is not even a fraction

224
00:08:47,983 --> 00:08:52,135
又顽固 又倔强 又疯疯癫癫都没有
as obstinate, stubborn and... insane as you are!

225
00:08:52,137 --> 00:08:55,606
狗娘养的 到底埋在哪里了
Where are you, you son of a bitch?!

226
00:08:56,474 --> 00:08:58,075
别看这边 孩子们 她马上要尿尿了
Look away, kids, she's about to pee.

227
00:08:58,077 --> 00:08:59,026
什么
What...?

228
00:08:59,028 --> 00:09:00,611
我才不是什么动物
I am not some animal.

229
00:09:00,613 --> 00:09:02,246
我20分钟前才尿过
I peed 20 minutes ago

230
00:09:02,248 --> 00:09:04,581
而且我很利落地埋好了 因为我可是淑女
and I buried it neatly because I am a lady!

231
00:09:09,413 --> 00:09:12,452
泰德 我们从去年开始就没用过豆袋椅了
Ted, we haven't used this chair in the last year.

232
00:09:12,453 --> 00:09:14,920
因此 放大三角
Ergo, Triangle.

233
00:09:14,922 --> 00:09:16,672
我想我知道你要表达什么
Yeah, I guess I see your point.

234
00:09:16,674 --> 00:09:19,341
我是说 如果你从去年起就没有用过这个豆袋椅
I mean, if you haven't used it in the last year...

235
00:09:19,343 --> 00:09:20,793
哦
Oh!

236
00:09:20,795 --> 00:09:21,760
你正在用
Using it!

237
00:09:21,762 --> 00:09:22,761
带去意大利
Italy!

238
00:09:22,763 --> 00:09:24,096
放到大三角
Triangle!

239
00:09:24,098 --> 00:09:25,631
带去意大利
Italy.

240
00:09:25,633 --> 00:09:26,915
-放大三角  -放大三角
-Triangle! -Triangle!

241
00:09:26,917 --> 00:09:27,916
带去意大利
Italy.

242
00:09:27,918 --> 00:09:28,917
好了 打住
Okay, stop!

243
00:09:28,919 --> 00:09:30,019
每次你把他推到椅子上
Every time he lands,

244
00:09:30,021 --> 00:09:32,271
椅子里就放出托里诺十年的灰尘屁
that chair farts out ten-year-old Dorito dust.

244
00:09:30,021 --> 00:09:32,271
{\a6}托里诺为意大利西北部城市

245
00:09:32,273 --> 00:09:34,490
就是这个豆袋椅
Yeah, it's the chair.

246
00:09:34,492 --> 00:09:37,443
伙计们 相信我 你们在意大利会用到这个豆袋椅的
Guys, trust me: you're gonna want this chair in Italy.

247
00:09:37,445 --> 00:09:39,945
我...它会有家的感觉
I... it'll feel like home.

248
00:09:40,797 --> 00:09:41,864
好了 兄弟
All right, buddy.

249
00:09:41,866 --> 00:09:44,316
败给你了 带去意大利
You win. Italy.

250
00:09:44,318 --> 00:09:46,035
真的吗 太好了
Really? Yeah.

1
00:09:46,037 --> 00:09:47,619
我们请你来做决断
We asked you to be the judge here

2
00:09:47,621 --> 00:09:49,621
就该信你信到底
and we gotta trust your opinion.

3
00:09:49,623 --> 00:09:50,606
她说得对
She's right.

4
00:09:50,608 --> 00:09:53,242
在我们四处去郊游的时候
And with all the traveling that we'll be doing...

6
00:09:53,244 --> 00:09:55,377
我们可能需要几个
we could probably use a couple of your...

7
00:09:55,379 --> 00:09:57,329
你那种免提小书包
hands-free belt satchels.

8
00:09:58,214 --> 00:09:59,614
你们不是说很挫吗
You said they were lame.

9
00:09:59,616 --> 00:10:01,166
我不得不承认
I hate to admit it,

10
00:10:01,168 --> 00:10:04,119
这听起来还是很实用的
but they actually sound useful.

11
00:10:04,121 --> 00:10:06,555
你能帮我们买两个吗
Could you buy us a couple?

12
00:10:07,507 --> 00:10:10,142
两个免提小书包马上就到
Two hands-free belt satchels, coming right up.

13
00:10:10,144 --> 00:10:12,261
而且不用担心 我会挑最潮色
Oh, and don't worry, I'll get cool colors

14
00:10:12,263 --> 00:10:13,679
这样你们就不会是西班牙习语里
so you guys don't look like

15
00:10:13,681 --> 00:10:16,265
所谓的腰包呆子了 
whatever the Spanish term really is for "Fanny Pack Dork."

16
00:10:16,865 --> 00:10:20,565
好一朵 腰包呆子啊

17
00:10:22,439 --> 00:10:26,992
弟兄们 这是我们和他们之间的决战
Men, it's us... versus them.

18
00:10:28,194 --> 00:10:30,696
我们今天的壮举
Our actions here today

19
00:10:30,698 --> 00:10:32,614
将永垂青史
will echo through eternity...

20
00:10:32,616 --> 00:10:34,500
站直了小子
Stand up straight, Kaden!

21
00:10:35,485 --> 00:10:38,820
你们这些废物懒蛆们听好了 我只有一条原则 
I only have one rule, you worthless maggots:

22
00:10:39,422 --> 00:10:41,790
我们要互相尊重
We all respect each other.

23
00:10:42,842 --> 00:10:43,842
我只有一条原则
I only have one rule:

24
00:10:43,844 --> 00:10:46,178
每上三个十分女
For every three tens you bang,

25
00:10:46,180 --> 00:10:47,763
给个五分赏一炮
throw a bone to a five.

26
00:10:47,765 --> 00:10:50,082
她们会感激并加倍努力 而且这么说吧
They're grateful and hard-working and let's face it,

27
00:10:50,084 --> 00:10:51,700
有时候你基本上就只想躺着不动了
sometimes you just want to lay there.

28
00:10:51,702 --> 00:10:53,852
这和真人激光枪有什么关系
What's that got to do with Laser Tag?

29
00:10:57,006 --> 00:11:00,192
关系大了去了
Everything!

30
00:11:00,194 --> 00:11:01,393
我们必将夺得胜利
...and we will prevail,

31
00:11:01,395 --> 00:11:03,562
就算激战到天明
even if it takes all night!

32
00:11:04,280 --> 00:11:05,147
小白脸
Tanner.

33
00:11:05,149 --> 00:11:07,199
我四点必须回家
I have to be home by 4:00.

34
00:11:10,687 --> 00:11:13,038
还有谁要提早回家的
Anyone else have any scheduling issues?

35
00:11:13,040 --> 00:11:14,923
对面其他人你们可以随便打
You can take down anyone on their team...

36
00:11:14,925 --> 00:11:17,409
但那个大个子留给我来处理
but I want the big man for myself.

37
00:11:17,411 --> 00:11:19,661
你干嘛和那老家伙过不去
What's your beef with oldie?

38
00:11:19,663 --> 00:11:22,047
他是
He's...

39
00:11:22,049 --> 00:11:23,215
我爹
my father.

40
00:11:23,217 --> 00:11:24,216
老丈人吧
Father-in-law.

41
00:11:24,218 --> 00:11:25,534
闭嘴 小凯子
Shut up, Kai.

42
00:11:30,590 --> 00:11:32,641
等一下
Wait a second...

43
00:11:32,643 --> 00:11:35,260
懂了 看到啥都塞你腰包里
We get it, you pack a lot in your fanny.

44
00:11:35,262 --> 00:11:37,896
言之有理
Obvious yet delightful.

45
00:11:37,898 --> 00:11:39,431
噢 不
Oh, no!

46
00:11:44,737 --> 00:11:47,906
不
No!

47
00:11:49,225 --> 00:11:51,360
这呆子×2
-El Ganso! -El Ganso!

48
00:11:51,362 --> 00:11:52,578
一对骗子
Liars!

49
00:11:52,580 --> 00:11:54,196
你们支开我去白跑一趟
You sent me on a fool's errand.

50
00:11:54,198 --> 00:11:55,531
好了好了 你讲讲道理
Okay, to be fair,

51
00:11:55,533 --> 00:11:58,233
买腰包本身就是多此一举
buying a fanny pack is inherently a fool's errand.

301
00:11:58,235 --> 00:12:00,369
这可是免提小书包
Hands-free belt satchels.

302
00:12:00,371 --> 00:12:02,704
而且你们居然欺骗我感情 除非你们要把这椅子留下
And just for that, I will not move from this chair

303
00:12:02,706 --> 00:12:04,006
不然我就杵在这上面不走了
until you agree to keep it!

304
00:12:04,008 --> 00:12:05,791
泰德 和这椅子恰巧相反
Ted, unlike that chair,

305
00:12:05,793 --> 00:12:08,093
你还真是精力旺盛呢
you, sir, are full of beans.

305
00:12:05,793 --> 00:12:09,744
{\a6}{\fs16}双关语 full of beans词义同时为装满了豆子 与豆袋椅的豆子都漏出来对比

306
00:12:08,095 --> 00:12:09,744
半小时后你可有个面试啊
You have a job interview in half an hour.

307
00:12:11,747 --> 00:12:12,714
管它妹的面试
Screw the interview.

308
00:12:12,716 --> 00:12:13,799
我就要留下来
I'm staying.

309
00:12:13,801 --> 00:12:18,270
而且听说好像要下雨了
And because the forecast calls for rain...

310
00:12:18,272 --> 00:12:20,389
介 可是个雨衣哦 
This... is a raincoat.

311
00:12:29,282 --> 00:12:31,116
巴尼在此
Go for Barney.

312
00:12:31,118 --> 00:12:33,485
嘿
Hey. Um...

313
00:12:33,487 --> 00:12:34,786
我这出了点问题
I'm having an issue.

314
00:12:34,788 --> 00:12:36,071
听着 罗宾
Now, listen, Robin...

315
00:12:36,073 --> 00:12:38,073
这事很急吗 还是可以过会再说
is this urgent or can we talk about it later?

316
00:12:39,392 --> 00:12:40,909
算了 蠢得要死
Nah, it's stupid.

317
00:12:40,911 --> 00:12:43,495
玩得开心哦
Have fun.

318
00:12:45,382 --> 00:12:46,999
再见啦 弱子们
So long, losers!

319
00:12:50,053 --> 00:12:51,003
呃
Um...

320
00:12:51,005 --> 00:12:52,921
你们可不可以把我弄下来啊
Look, can you guys help me down?

321
00:12:52,923 --> 00:12:54,590
我
I... um...

322
00:12:54,592 --> 00:12:57,092
泰德 如果这椅子对你来说真的那么重要
Ted, if this chair really means that much to you,

323
00:12:57,094 --> 00:12:58,894
你怎么不自己留着它呢
why don't you just take it for yourself?

324
00:12:58,896 --> 00:13:01,463
不 重要的是你们留着它啊
No, it's important that you keep it.

325
00:13:01,465 --> 00:13:02,564
为什么啊
Why?

326
00:13:02,566 --> 00:13:04,466
这是我们大学毕业搬过来后
This is the first thing we bought

327
00:13:04,468 --> 00:13:05,901
买的第一件东西啊
when we moved here after college.

328
00:13:05,903 --> 00:13:09,271
刚开始的那一周我们仅有的家具就是它
It was the only piece of furniture we had for a week.

329
00:13:09,273 --> 00:13:10,656
可是现在你们俩
And now you two are

330
00:13:10,658 --> 00:13:12,157
都要搬去意大利了
moving to Italy.

331
00:13:12,159 --> 00:13:13,442
要是我们之间的友谊没有通过
What if our friendship doesn't pass

332
00:13:13,444 --> 00:13:15,777
那个"一年内是否用过"的测试怎么办
the "Have you used it in a year" Test?

333
00:13:15,779 --> 00:13:18,697
如果你们可以扔掉这椅子
If you can throw out this chair...

334
00:13:18,699 --> 00:13:21,416
谁又能保证你们不会连我也不要了呢
who's to say you can't throw me out, too?

335
00:13:21,418 --> 00:13:22,918
那种事绝对不可能发生的
That could never happen.

336
00:13:22,920 --> 00:13:25,003
你又不是椅子 你可是我们最好的朋友
You're not a chair, you're our best friend.

337
00:13:25,005 --> 00:13:27,873
你现在是这么说 但这一年之内什么事情都会发生
You can say that, but a lot can change in a year.

338
00:13:27,875 --> 00:13:29,658
兄弟 我
Buddy, I...

339
00:13:29,660 --> 00:13:30,926
听着 我知道是我有点不理智
Look, I know I'm being crazy.

340
00:13:30,928 --> 00:13:33,512
我只是
I just...

341
00:13:33,514 --> 00:13:36,098
我需要和这椅子独处一下
I just need a moment with this chair.

342
00:13:36,100 --> 00:13:38,217
你懂的 就好好的告别一下
You know... to say good-bye.

343
00:13:38,219 --> 00:13:40,886
我们会给你俩一些空间的
We'll give you two some space.

344
00:13:43,690 --> 00:13:47,609
孩子们 你抓不住已经消逝的过去
Kids, you can't cling to the past.

345
00:13:53,616 --> 00:13:57,903
因为无论你抓得有多么紧
Because no matter how tightly you hold on...

346
00:13:58,854 --> 00:14:01,423
它都已经不见了
...it's already gone.

347
00:14:05,912 --> 00:14:06,912
喂
Hello?

348
00:14:06,914 --> 00:14:08,130
嗨
Hi.

349
00:14:08,132 --> 00:14:11,333
我现在在中央公园的旋转木马这里
I'm at the Central Park Carousel and, um...

350
00:14:11,335 --> 00:14:13,719
出了一点小问题
I'm having a little bit of an issue.

351
00:14:13,721 --> 00:14:15,203
恩 什么情况
Uh, what kind of issue?

352
00:14:15,205 --> 00:14:18,090
这个嘛 还真是说来话长了
Actually, it's a long story...

353
00:14:18,092 --> 00:14:20,092
呃 罗宾 听着 我有一个重要会议快迟到了
Um, Robin, listen, I'm-I'm late for a big meeting.

354
00:14:20,094 --> 00:14:21,226
你那边重要吗
Is it important?

355
00:14:22,545 --> 00:14:24,680
算了 蠢得要死
Nah, it's stupid.

356
00:14:24,682 --> 00:14:26,381
祝你好运
Good luck.

357
00:14:27,517 --> 00:14:29,651
好 已经到了最后时刻了 小强们
All right, here's the bottom line, cockroaches.

358
00:14:29,653 --> 00:14:31,403
胜利遥遥无期
There's no end in sight

359
00:14:31,405 --> 00:14:34,256
而且我们也没有补给
and we've got no provisions.

360
00:14:34,258 --> 00:14:35,407
如果已成定局了的话
If it comes down to it,

361
00:14:35,409 --> 00:14:38,827
我需要一个志愿者让我们剩下的人能够...
I need a volunteer to let the rest of us...

362
00:14:38,829 --> 00:14:39,861
干掉他
eat him.

363
00:14:39,863 --> 00:14:41,896
巴尼队看起来好玩多了
Barney's team seems way more fun.

364
00:14:41,898 --> 00:14:42,731
胡说八道
Nonsense.

365
00:14:42,733 --> 00:14:44,299
每个人都有糖糖吃
Candy for everyone!

366
00:14:45,536 --> 00:14:47,919
好 动物之家队 谁想试试雪茄的滋味
Okay, Team Animal House... who wants to try a cigar?

367
00:14:47,921 --> 00:14:49,421
耶 耶
Yeah! Yay!

368
00:14:49,423 --> 00:14:51,673
我又没有说要拿你的脸或其他什么来当炮灰
I'm not saying we're gonna start with your face or anything,

369
00:14:51,675 --> 00:14:53,175
但真的没人愿意
but is there seriously no one here

370
00:14:53,177 --> 00:14:55,294
牺牲一只手或者一只脚吗
willing to give up a hand or a foot?

371
00:14:55,296 --> 00:14:56,628
我们不干了
We're outta here!

372
00:15:17,831 --> 00:15:19,856
泰德 你怎么来了
Ted, why are you here?

373
00:15:19,857 --> 00:15:21,941
你不是有会要开吗 我都告诉你别来了
You had that meeting; I told you not to come.

374
00:15:21,943 --> 00:15:23,776
你说"算了 蠢得要死"时
You said, "Nah, it's stupid,"

375
00:15:23,778 --> 00:15:26,528
这是罗宾语的"这事很重要"
which is Robin-ese for, "It's important."

376
00:15:26,530 --> 00:15:28,113
大家都知道的
Everyone knows that.

377
00:15:30,149 --> 00:15:32,668
唉 也不是每个人
Well... not everyone.

378
00:15:33,703 --> 00:15:35,287
但你不该翘掉那会议的
But you shouldn't have skipped that meeting.

379
00:15:35,289 --> 00:15:36,488
它重要吗
Was it important?

380
00:15:36,490 --> 00:15:39,124
算了 蠢得要死
Nah, it's stupid.

381
00:15:40,010 --> 00:15:42,544
现在 我的未来丈夫
And yet, my future husband--

382
00:15:42,546 --> 00:15:45,330
那个有的时候惹起事来像极了
who I sometimes fear is troublingly similar

383
00:15:45,332 --> 00:15:48,183
我那难以亲近的老爸的人
to my emotionally unavailable father--

384
00:15:48,185 --> 00:15:51,220
抛下我去和某人打真人激光枪了 噢 对 你没猜错
is off shooting laser guns with, oh, yeah, you guessed it:

385
00:15:51,222 --> 00:15:53,355
就是和我那难以亲近的老爸
my emotionally unavailable father.

386
00:15:53,357 --> 00:15:54,723
噢 别这样啊 这不公平
Oh, come on, that's not fair.

387
00:15:54,725 --> 00:15:56,308
如果你告诉巴尼你需要他的话
If you told Barney that you needed him,

388
00:15:56,310 --> 00:15:57,526
他会立刻赶到的
he'd be here in a heartbeat.

389
00:15:57,528 --> 00:15:59,778
可我不需要告诉你
I didn't have to tell you.

390
00:15:59,780 --> 00:16:02,014
你就出现了啊
And you're here.

391
00:16:02,983 --> 00:16:04,850
你连为什么都还不知道
You don't even know why.

392
00:16:06,853 --> 00:16:09,989
看来我是来挖宝的啊
Seems like I'm here to dig.

393
00:16:22,035 --> 00:16:24,586
是在找这些电池吗
Looking for "D"S?

394
00:16:25,755 --> 00:16:28,707
长话短说吧 我向未来的自己许诺说
Long story short, I promised my future self

395
00:16:28,709 --> 00:16:31,543
这个吊坠小盒会成为我婚礼上的"旧物"
the locket would be my "Something old" At my wedding.

396
00:16:32,812 --> 00:16:33,929
怎么
What?

397
00:16:34,564 --> 00:16:37,382
没什么 我只是很喜欢曾经有这种版本的你
No, I just like that there was ever a version of you

399
00:16:37,384 --> 00:16:40,019
会想象着在婚礼上要有一份"旧物"
who imagined having a "Something old" At your wedding.

400
00:16:40,937 --> 00:16:43,322
罗宾•舍巴斯基 你是个小女生
Robin Scherbatsky-- you're a girl.

401
00:16:43,324 --> 00:16:44,556
闭嘴吧你 你才是小女生
Shut up. You're a girl.

402
00:16:44,558 --> 00:16:45,774
那早就说烂掉了
That's been established.

403
00:16:45,776 --> 00:16:48,694
新情报告诉我们你居然也是个小女生
The new information here is that you're a girl.

404
00:16:51,081 --> 00:16:53,165
等等...那是不是...
Wait... is that...?

405
00:16:53,167 --> 00:16:55,367
噢 天哪 我找到了
Oh, my God, I found it.

406
00:16:58,505 --> 00:17:00,422
好吧
Okay...

407
00:17:00,424 --> 00:17:02,407
这吊坠小盒到底意味着什么
what's really going on with this locket?

408
00:17:04,962 --> 00:17:06,428
我有一些我一直无法确信的东西
I'm gonna admit something that I couldn't admit

409
00:17:06,430 --> 00:17:07,796
找到这个之后 我愿意去相信了
until I found this.

410
00:17:09,099 --> 00:17:11,834
我对嫁给巴尼这件事一直都怀有恐惧感
I've been having fears about marrying Barney.

411
00:17:12,919 --> 00:17:14,303
我是说 在很多方面
I mean, in many ways,

412
00:17:14,305 --> 00:17:17,356
他已经变得成熟 会关心人了
he's-he's grown up into a mature, caring adult...

413
00:17:17,358 --> 00:17:20,192
我要用你的枪干掉你
I'm gonna shoot you with your own gun.

414
00:17:22,697 --> 00:17:25,230
但是我还是不知道他是否已经做好结婚的准备
...but I still don't know if he's ready for this.

415
00:17:26,316 --> 00:17:28,734
我也不知道我是否准备好了
I still don't know if I am.

416
00:17:29,602 --> 00:17:31,787
但如果我能找到这个吊坠小盒
But if I could find this locket--

417
00:17:31,789 --> 00:17:34,439
如果它仍然在这 等待着我
if it was still here, waiting for me

418
00:17:34,441 --> 00:17:36,291
就意味着这个宇宙
that would mean that the Universe

419
00:17:36,293 --> 00:17:37,793
希望我嫁给巴尼
wanted me to marry Barney.

420
00:17:37,795 --> 00:17:39,912
这样的话 万事大吉
And that everything was gonna be okay.

421
00:17:41,247 --> 00:17:43,882
如果它不见了 就像是
And when it was gone, it was like...

422
00:17:43,884 --> 00:17:47,553
我对巴尼有过的的种种怀疑
every doute I-I ever had about Barney,

423
00:17:47,555 --> 00:17:50,422
以及对我自己的怀疑 都被挖出来大白于天下了
about myself, got dug up.

424
00:17:51,424 --> 00:17:53,092
但是我找到了
But I found it.

425
00:17:54,177 --> 00:17:55,978
这样一切都没事了
And everything's gonna be okay.

426
00:17:58,765 --> 00:18:00,899
你临死前想说什么吗
Any last words?

427
00:18:00,901 --> 00:18:02,851
看着你在战场上
You know, seeing you on the field of battle--

428
00:18:02,853 --> 00:18:06,105
无情无义 工于心计 不可信赖
ruthless, manipulative, untrustworthy--

429
00:18:06,107 --> 00:18:09,241
你具备了我想要的儿子的所有品质
you've got all the qualities I would've wanted in a son.

430
00:18:10,643 --> 00:18:12,111
现在我对你说
Now I say to you

431
00:18:12,113 --> 00:18:14,279
我爸爸给我留的遗言
the last words my father said to me:

432
00:18:14,281 --> 00:18:16,498
杀了我吧
"Shoot me already."

433
00:18:17,333 --> 00:18:20,986
或者我们接着玩 如果你想的话
Or we could keep playing, if you want.

434
00:18:20,988 --> 00:18:23,839
算了 蠢得要死
Nah, it's stupid.

435
00:18:24,624 --> 00:18:27,159
好吧 动物之家队 我抓到他了
Okay, Team Animal House, I got him!

436
00:18:27,161 --> 00:18:28,293
出来吧
Come on out!

437
00:18:28,295 --> 00:18:29,545
你是突击手 老罗狗
You're point guy, R-dawg.

438
00:18:29,547 --> 00:18:31,880
汪汪
Woof, woof.

439
00:18:40,538 --> 00:18:42,654
意大利

439
00:18:50,038 --> 00:18:52,354
我爱你们 还是把那个垃圾沙发扔了吧

439
00:18:54,038 --> 00:18:56,354
噢 谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.

440
00:19:08,601 --> 00:19:09,968
这是宇宙的暗示
This is a sign from the Universe.

441
00:19:09,970 --> 00:19:11,386
这不是宇宙的暗示
It's not a sign from the Universe...

442
00:19:11,388 --> 00:19:12,387
不 这就是
Yes, it is!

443
00:19:12,389 --> 00:19:13,922
吊坠都找不到了
The-the locket is just gone

444
00:19:13,924 --> 00:19:15,974
你还告诉我这不是什么暗示
and you're telling me that doesn't mean anything?

445
00:19:15,976 --> 00:19:19,595
你明明知道这是个不好的暗示 泰德 你不很吃这一套的吗
You know this is a bad omen, Ted-- you're Universe Guy!

446
00:19:19,597 --> 00:19:20,929
你是怀疑论者
And you're Skeptic Girl!

447
00:19:20,931 --> 00:19:22,314
你不该相信这些鬼东西的
You're-you're not supposed to believe any of that.

448
00:19:22,316 --> 00:19:25,217
也许我已经变得对怀疑论起疑心了
Well, maybe I've grown skeptical of being skeptical.

449
00:19:26,019 --> 00:19:28,053
这就是个暗示
This is a sign.

450
00:19:28,055 --> 00:19:29,188
听着 这不是个暗示
Look, it's not a sign.

451
00:19:29,190 --> 00:19:31,406
你嫁给巴尼是正确的
You're doing the right thing marrying Barney.

452
00:19:31,408 --> 00:19:34,109
宇宙不是在给你什么暗示
The Universe isn't sending you some message.

453
00:19:37,330 --> 00:19:38,897
我们都知道 根据科学
As we know from science,

454
00:19:38,899 --> 00:19:42,701
雨水是水蒸气凝结成液态水
rain is liquid water in the form of droplets

455
00:19:42,703 --> 00:19:45,070
之后在大气层中形成水滴
which have condensed from atmospheric vapor

456
00:19:45,072 --> 00:19:46,404
然后降下来变成雨
and then precipitated.

457
00:19:46,406 --> 00:19:47,339
这不是暗示
It's not a sign.

458
00:19:47,341 --> 00:19:50,575
泰德 你知道这就是个暗示
Ted, this is a sign and you know it.

459
00:19:50,577 --> 00:19:54,179
我是说 宇宙现在正朝我尖叫大喊
I mean, the Universe is screaming at me right now!

460
00:19:54,181 --> 00:19:55,881
所有人中 怎么偏偏就是你
How-how-how can you, of all people,

461
00:19:55,883 --> 00:19:57,549
告诉我要无视这个暗示
tell me to ignore that?

462
00:19:57,551 --> 00:20:01,086
因为寻找宇宙的暗示是很愚蠢的
Because maybe it's dumb to look for "Signs from the Universe."

463
00:20:01,088 --> 00:20:03,939
我是说 宇宙还有别的更重要的事要做
I mean, maybe the Universe has better things to do.

464
00:20:03,941 --> 00:20:05,691
天啊 我真希望是这样的
Dear God, I hope it does.

465
00:20:05,693 --> 00:20:07,425
你知道我有多少关于
Do you know how many "Signs" I've gotten

466
00:20:07,427 --> 00:20:09,528
我该或者不该和谁在一起的暗示吗
that I should or shouldn't be with someone?

467
00:20:09,530 --> 00:20:11,446
暗示的结果又去了哪里呢
And where has it gotten me?

468
00:20:12,565 --> 00:20:20,982
{\a6}How To Fight Loneliness by Wilco

468
00:20:12,565 --> 00:20:13,982
也许压根就没有什么暗示
Maybe there aren't any signs.

469
00:20:13,984 --> 00:20:16,902
也许 也许吊坠小盒就只不过是个吊坠小盒罢了
Maybe... maybe a locket's just a locket,

470
00:20:16,904 --> 00:20:19,488
就如同沙发不过是沙发
a chair is just a chair.

471
00:20:19,490 --> 00:20:20,739
我们可能不需要
Maybe we don't have to

472
00:20:20,741 --> 00:20:24,126
给每样东西都附上意义
give meaning to every little thing.

473
00:20:24,128 --> 00:20:26,295
也许我们不...
Maybe we don't...

474
00:20:26,297 --> 00:20:28,213
也许我们不需要宇宙
maybe we don't need the Universe

475
00:20:28,215 --> 00:20:30,615
告诉我们想要的是什么
to tell us what we really want.

476
00:20:30,617 --> 00:20:34,169
也许我们内心深处都清楚
Maybe we already know that, deep down.

477
00:20:34,171 --> 00:20:37,422
* 谎言磨砺露寒光 *
Sharpen them with lies

478
00:20:41,010 --> 00:20:46,815
* 无论跌倒在何方 *
And whatever's going down

479
00:20:50,270 --> 00:20:54,139
* 都会伴随你身旁 *
Will follow you around

480
00:20:54,141 --> 00:20:59,691
* 如此把孤单抵抗 *
That's how you fight loneliness... 

481
00:20:59,693 --> 00:21:01,693
HIMYM字幕组 谢谢观看

481
00:21:01,695 --> 00:21:06,693
欢迎关注字幕组新浪微博及人人网主页
@HIMYM字幕组
