1
00:00:02,087 --> 00:00:04,015
孩子们 故事发生在巴尼的生活
Kids, this is the story of the night

2
00:00:04,016 --> 00:00:05,925
完完全全的分崩离析的那天晚上
Barney's life completely fell apart.

3
00:00:06,610 --> 00:00:08,327
我的生活终于完美了
My life is finally perfect,

3
00:00:06,610 --> 00:00:10,245
{\a6}六小时前

4
00:00:08,329 --> 00:00:10,245
而且再也不会变了
and that is never going to change.

5
00:00:10,247 --> 00:00:12,314
准备好今晚跟我妈妈吃饭了吗
Fired up for dinner with my mom tonight?

6
00:00:12,316 --> 00:00:14,082
这样吧 为了让我们今后的生活更有效率
Yeah. To help streamline the rest of our lives,

7
00:00:14,084 --> 00:00:16,868
你可以一直默认我对这个问题的答案是否定的
you can always assume my answer to that question is no.

8
00:00:16,870 --> 00:00:18,837
-这...  -我就是挺紧张的
-W... -I'm pretty nervous.

9
00:00:18,839 --> 00:00:21,290
紧张 有什么好紧张的 不就是两个小时的
Nervous? Why? It's just gonna be two hours

10
00:00:21,292 --> 00:00:24,593
"我最爱巴尼了" "不 我才最爱巴尼呢"
of "I love Barney the most." "No, I love Barney the most."

11
00:00:24,595 --> 00:00:26,795
你说的没错 那我可能连话都插不上
You're right. I may not even get a chance to talk.

12
00:00:26,797 --> 00:00:27,829
但我还是...
But I'm still...

13
00:00:27,831 --> 00:00:29,047
我不知道 我只是担心
I-I don't know. I'm worried

14
00:00:29,049 --> 00:00:30,716
她会觉得我没那么好
she won't think I'm good enough to be engaged

15
00:00:30,718 --> 00:00:32,684
配不上跟她的小可爱订婚
to her precious little Love-Love.

16
00:00:32,686 --> 00:00:35,687
好吧 首先 应该是"小口耐"
Okay, first of all, it's "Wuv-Wuv."

17
00:00:35,689 --> 00:00:36,504
其次
And second,

18
00:00:36,506 --> 00:00:37,839
就放一百个心吧
don't worry.

19
00:00:37,841 --> 00:00:39,224
我先去把婚宴承办人的定金交了
I'm just gonna drop off our catering deposit,

20
00:00:39,226 --> 00:00:40,892
然后就来陪你 亲一下
and then I will be there for you. Mm.

21
00:00:40,894 --> 00:00:42,277
好吧 千万别来晚了
Okay, well, please don't be late.

22
00:00:42,279 --> 00:00:43,562
今晚我就指望你了
I am counting on you tonight.

23
00:00:43,564 --> 00:00:45,731
还有小心点 那里面可是五千块钱呢
And be careful-- that's 5,000 bucks in there.

24
00:00:45,733 --> 00:00:49,034
我觉得我在上东区就走上四个街区
Uh, I think I'll be okay walking four blocks here

25
00:00:49,036 --> 00:00:51,620
是完全没有问题的
on the Upper East Side.

26
00:00:57,911 --> 00:01:00,362
求你们了 我发誓我没跟北朝鲜人说过话
Please, I swear I never talked to the North Koreans!

27
00:01:00,364 --> 00:01:01,696
除非你们就是北朝鲜人 这样的话
Unless you are the North Koreans, in which case

28
00:01:01,698 --> 00:01:02,881
我就从来没跟南朝鲜的人说过话
I never talked to the South Koreans!

29
00:01:02,883 --> 00:01:04,499
巴尼•斯丁森
Barney Stinson,

30
00:01:04,501 --> 00:01:06,885
你被绑架了
you are being kidnapped.

31
00:01:06,887 --> 00:01:09,871
绑你去惊喜单身派对
For your surprise bachelor party!

1
00:01:12,911 --> 00:01:14,911
{\a1}{\fs17}　　　　 老爸\N　　　  　　 老妈\N　　 　　 浪漫史\N{\fs16}{\bord1}{\3c&H00DCE1&}　　  　　　　第八季  第二十二集\N
{\fnDaxlinePro-Regular}{\fs19}{\b0}{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\3c&H2F2F2F&}{\4c&H000000&}{\a1}　　　　　S08E22 The Bro Mitzvah

2
00:01:15,021 --> 00:01:18,021
{\fs17}翻译: @Mr_Gao703 @rubink2011 @纷扬DLL\N{\3c&H00DCE1&}{\bord1}@卟哒哒伽马 @麟礡 @阿狸小H\N{\3c&H007EFF&}校对: @我叫肉鸭鸭 @晒小花

3
00:01:18,022 --> 00:01:21,022
{\fs17}{\3c&H00DCE1&}{\bord1}压制: @Big-Fudge\N{\3c&H007EFF&}统筹+后期: @我叫肉鸭鸭 @晒小花

4
00:01:21,306 --> 00:01:23,706
HIMYM字幕组 倾情奉献


35
00:01:24,687 --> 00:01:26,355
绑架是吧
A kidnapping.

36
00:01:26,357 --> 00:01:27,489
不错不错
Respect.

37
00:01:27,491 --> 00:01:28,740
我私下里还担心
I was secretly worried

38
00:01:28,742 --> 00:01:31,559
你们俩搞定不了我的单身派对呢
you might not be able to pull off my bachelor party.

39
00:01:31,561 --> 00:01:33,328
少来 哪有私底下
Yeah, it wasn't that secret.

40
00:01:33,330 --> 00:01:35,730
就你们俩 计划我的单身派对
You two? Planning my bachelor party?

40
00:01:33,330 --> 00:01:35,730
{\a6}三周前

41
00:01:35,732 --> 00:01:38,250
听着 你们真是乖娃娃
Look, you seem like nice kids.

42
00:01:38,252 --> 00:01:40,168
但这是件庄严神圣的大事
But this is a sacred event,

43
00:01:40,170 --> 00:01:42,621
一个男人跟他的兄弟们一起度过的仪式
a man's rite of passage with his bros.

44
00:01:42,623 --> 00:01:45,257
他的...兄弟受诫礼
His... bro mitzvah!

45
00:01:45,259 --> 00:01:46,508
这才不是你刚灵机一动想出来的
You didn't just think of that.

46
00:01:46,510 --> 00:01:47,759
你这几个月就一直在念叨...
You've been saying it for months every...

47
00:01:47,761 --> 00:01:49,094
但我也有我的难处
But here's my dilemma:

48
00:01:49,096 --> 00:01:51,346
平常人的单身派对 对我来说也就是平常的夜生活
my average night is like an average guy's bachelor party.

49
00:01:51,348 --> 00:01:53,382
所以 无意冒犯 但是如果你俩来计划
So, no offense, but if you two plan it,

50
00:01:53,384 --> 00:01:56,251
这也就会是 平...凭什么要等一下..了个常
it's gonna be ordi-- why wait for it?-- nary.

51
00:01:56,253 --> 00:01:57,769
平常
Ordinary.

52
00:01:57,771 --> 00:01:58,520
我可以帮忙
I can help.

53
00:01:58,522 --> 00:02:00,138
就你
You?

54
00:02:00,140 --> 00:02:01,890
听好 你看起来也算蛮会倒腾的
Look, you seem like a nice kid,

55
00:02:01,892 --> 00:02:02,858
但是兄弟的未婚妻
but bros' fiancées

56
00:02:02,860 --> 00:02:04,376
不能参与计划单身派对
cannot plan bachelor parties.

57
00:02:04,378 --> 00:02:05,927
不好意思 你俩自己搞定
Sorry. You two are on your own.

58
00:02:05,929 --> 00:02:07,863
你们一定会让我失望的
And you will disappoint me.

59
00:02:08,781 --> 00:02:10,949
但尽量弄好点 行吧
But make it great, okay?

60
00:02:10,951 --> 00:02:13,235
这个开头很带劲啊
But this is a strong start.

61
00:02:13,237 --> 00:02:15,603
这些学生们 已然成为
The students have become...

62
00:02:15,605 --> 00:02:17,939
中级学生了
the intermediate students.

63
00:02:17,941 --> 00:02:20,442
我先打个电话
I just have to make one call.

64
00:02:22,045 --> 00:02:23,445
喂
Hello.

65
00:02:23,447 --> 00:02:24,880
罗宾 好消息
Robin, great news!

66
00:02:24,882 --> 00:02:26,748
我被绑去参加一个惊喜单身派对去了
I've been kidnapped for a surprise bachelor party

67
00:02:26,750 --> 00:02:28,383
所以我来不了了
so I won't be there at all!

68
00:02:28,385 --> 00:02:31,136
什么 巴尼 我做不到就我一人陪你妈妈吃饭啊
What? Barney, I-I can't do dinner with your mom alone.

69
00:02:31,138 --> 00:02:33,922
好吧 我给她打个电话 找个借口把它取消了
Okay, I'll call her, make up an excuse and cancel.

70
00:02:33,924 --> 00:02:35,924
别担心 有事我全扛着
And don't worry, I'll take all the blame.

71
00:02:35,926 --> 00:02:38,310
等会
Hold on.

72
00:02:38,312 --> 00:02:39,428
嗨 小口耐
Hi, Wuv-Wuv.

73
00:02:39,430 --> 00:02:40,896
嗨 麻麻
Hi, Momsies.

74
00:02:40,898 --> 00:02:43,849
我都忘了 我今晚要给一个失学儿童补课呢
I forgot, I'm mentoring an underprivileged child tonight,

75
00:02:43,851 --> 00:02:47,469
罗宾又受不了就她一个人陪你吃饭
and Robin can't stand the idea of dinner with you by herself,

76
00:02:47,471 --> 00:02:49,104
所以我们就不能...
so we're not gonna be able to...

77
00:02:49,106 --> 00:02:50,472
不用麻烦了 她都已经到了
Don't bother. She's already here.

78
00:02:50,474 --> 00:02:52,741
等会
Hold on.

79
00:02:52,743 --> 00:02:55,277
罗宾 太晚了 她已经到了
Robin? Too late. She's already there.

80
00:02:55,279 --> 00:02:56,661
巴尼 别...
Barney, don't...

81
00:02:56,663 --> 00:02:59,581
罗宾受不了一个人陪我吃饭吗
Robin can't stand the idea of dinner with me?

82
00:02:59,583 --> 00:03:00,982
太好了 那我们都说好了
Great! We're all set then.

83
00:03:00,984 --> 00:03:02,684
别让我一个人陪她 我跟你说过...
Don't you leave me alone with her. I told you...

84
00:03:02,686 --> 00:03:05,320
问题解决
That problem is solved.

85
00:03:05,322 --> 00:03:07,038
现在你们什么计划
So what's the plan?

86
00:03:07,040 --> 00:03:09,157
好吧 你知道大西洋城的泰姬陵赌场吗
Well, you know the Taj Mahal in Atlantic City?

87
00:03:09,159 --> 00:03:11,126
知道
Yeah.

88
00:03:11,128 --> 00:03:13,044
你知道大西洋城的泰姬陵赌场的楼顶
You know the secret penthouse

89
00:03:13,046 --> 00:03:15,830
有一套秘密豪华套房吗
in the top of the Taj Mahal in Atlantic City?

90
00:03:15,832 --> 00:03:18,049
知道
Yeah!

91
00:03:18,051 --> 00:03:19,885
看呐 就在那儿
Boom! There it is.

92
00:03:19,887 --> 00:03:21,720
从我们的窗户可以看见
Visible from our window.

93
00:03:21,722 --> 00:03:24,005
就是有点距离
In the distance.

94
00:03:24,007 --> 00:03:25,107
在炼油厂后面
Behind the refinery.

95
00:03:25,109 --> 00:03:26,892
好吧 基本上看不见
Okay, you can't quite see it.

96
00:03:26,894 --> 00:03:29,811
为什么我们就偏偏在大西洋城外围啊 
Why are we outside Atlantic City?

97
00:03:29,813 --> 00:03:31,396
呃 我们觉得这样才能不负恩泽
Well, we thought it was best,

98
00:03:31,398 --> 00:03:34,366
因为你玩机会博弈那类游戏真真是极弱的
what with your weakness for games of chance.

99
00:03:34,368 --> 00:03:35,750
孩子们 巴尼痴迷于
Kids, Barney was addicted

100
00:03:35,752 --> 00:03:37,235
一种中国的赌博游戏
to one Chinese gambling game

100
00:03:35,752 --> 00:03:37,235
{\a6}这个游戏在S02E08出现过

101
00:03:37,237 --> 00:03:40,322
那游戏 呃 有点复杂
that was, well, sort of complicated.

102
00:03:40,324 --> 00:03:41,356
不过别担心
But don't worry.

103
00:03:41,358 --> 00:03:43,074
你早在和昆茵订婚那会儿
Back when you were engaged to Quinn,

104
00:03:43,076 --> 00:03:45,877
就告诉过我们你今晚想要什么了
you told us everything you wanted for tonight.

105
00:03:45,879 --> 00:03:48,830
单身派对是一个男人的
A bachelor party is a man's...

105
00:03:45,879 --> 00:03:48,830
{\a6}十个月前

106
00:03:48,832 --> 00:03:51,533
兄弟受诫礼
bro mitzvah!

107
00:03:51,535 --> 00:03:53,051
你刚瞎掰出来的吗
Did you just think of that?

108
00:03:53,053 --> 00:03:55,303
正是如此 我们可以戴上
Totally! We can wear...

109
00:03:55,305 --> 00:03:57,305
黑色小哥帽
bro-mulkes...

110
00:03:57,307 --> 00:04:01,309
转个兄贵小陀螺
spin the bro-del...

111
00:04:01,311 --> 00:04:06,982
还要聆听伟大的兄弟卷轴中的智慧
and consult the wisdom of the Bro-rah.

113
00:04:06,984 --> 00:04:10,202
用希哥来文写的
Written in... He-bro.

114
00:04:10,204 --> 00:04:12,521
哥们真是一点也不冒犯呢
Not at all bro-ffensive.

115
00:04:12,523 --> 00:04:15,023
对了对了 还有些别的主意呢 我就全一股脑写上去了
Ooh, ooh! Couple other ideas-- and I'm just spitballing here--

116
00:04:15,025 --> 00:04:16,575
爱要要 不要拉倒
so take 'em or leave 'em.

117
00:04:16,577 --> 00:04:19,494
美酒 不用说 雪茄 少不了 脱衣舞娘 必须有
Booze, duh; cigars, duh; strippers, duh...

118
00:04:19,496 --> 00:04:21,246
对了 既然我们迟早会玩过头
Ooh! Things should get so crazy that at some point

119
00:04:21,248 --> 00:04:22,931
某种程度上我们还该敬畏生命
we should fear for our lives.

120
00:04:22,933 --> 00:04:25,617
我们一定会敬畏生命的 
Oh, we'll fear for our lives, all right.

121
00:04:25,619 --> 00:04:29,421
那就一起来看艾尔•戈尔的《难以忽视的真相》吧
When we watch Al Gore's An Inconvenient Truth!

122
00:04:29,423 --> 00:04:30,905
好啊 我们可以玩每听到一次
Yeah. We're gonna pound a beer

123
00:04:30,907 --> 00:04:33,741
"灾难性"这个词 就吹掉一瓶啤酒的游戏呢
every time we hear the word "Catastrophic"

125
00:04:33,743 --> 00:04:35,410
哦
Oh!

126
00:04:35,412 --> 00:04:37,245
会不会是
Could that be...

127
00:04:37,247 --> 00:04:40,432
你清单上的下一条项目呢
the next item on your list?

128
00:04:40,434 --> 00:04:42,551
爽翻天的视听盛宴
Mind-blowing entertainment,

129
00:04:42,553 --> 00:04:46,388
比如裸体火舞或者裸体魔术之类的
like a naked fire show or a naked magic show.

130
00:04:46,390 --> 00:04:47,556
我们的婚约很有可能
There's a good chance our engagement

131
00:04:47,558 --> 00:04:48,640
会告吹 不是吗
doesn't work out, isn't there?

132
00:04:48,642 --> 00:04:49,474
{\a6}双关 "暂时不会"

132
00:04:48,642 --> 00:04:49,474
不谈这个啊 亲爱的
Not now, honey.

133
00:04:49,476 --> 00:04:51,926
又或者是裸体柔术
Or a naked contortionist!

134
00:04:51,928 --> 00:04:55,146
或者是 气球柔术
Or... A balloon contortionist!

135
00:04:58,934 --> 00:05:00,318
气球
Balloons.

136
00:05:00,320 --> 00:05:02,937
不是我今晚想看见的那种
Not the inflatable, round, squishy pouches

137
00:05:02,939 --> 00:05:04,623
充气的 圆圆的 黏糊糊的小气球
I was hoping to see tonight.

138
00:05:05,876 --> 00:05:06,958
等一下
Hold on.

139
00:05:06,960 --> 00:05:08,610
我跟你说了不要叫小丑
I told you no clown.

140
00:05:08,612 --> 00:05:11,379
但你也不喜欢那个吹泡泡的啊
Well, you didn't like the bubble guy either.

141
00:05:11,381 --> 00:05:12,214
好啊 罗宾
Hey, Robin.

142
00:05:12,216 --> 00:05:13,381
你是不是跟你妈妈说
Did you tell your mother

143
00:05:13,383 --> 00:05:14,449
我是处女啊
I'm a virgin?

144
00:05:14,451 --> 00:05:17,335
什么 你为什么会这么想
What? Why would you think that?

145
00:05:17,337 --> 00:05:19,721
留着点肚子吃甜点
Save yourself room for dessert. Mmm.

146
00:05:19,723 --> 00:05:22,974
据说你在自我保留方面极其突出呢
And I hear you excel at saving yourself.

147
00:05:24,760 --> 00:05:26,428
你太逗了
You are so funny.

148
00:05:26,430 --> 00:05:27,846
是不是什么东西上身了
What's gotten into you?

149
00:05:27,848 --> 00:05:30,982
哦 没错 从来没有过
Oh, that's right, nothing ever.

150
00:05:32,985 --> 00:05:34,302
你可能会对
You may be nervous

151
00:05:34,304 --> 00:05:36,905
新婚夜将要发生的事情感到很紧张
as to what goes where on your wedding night.

152
00:05:36,907 --> 00:05:38,607
很简单的
It's really simple.

153
00:05:38,609 --> 00:05:40,808
我给你演示一下
Let me show you.

154
00:05:42,978 --> 00:05:46,081
我们从最基本的姿势开始学吧
Let's start with the fundamentals.

155
00:05:46,083 --> 00:05:48,149
你为什么告诉她我是处女
Why would you tell her I'm a virgin?

156
00:05:48,151 --> 00:05:49,084
我慌了嘛
I panicked.

157
00:05:49,086 --> 00:05:50,818
就是 我真心希望她会喜欢你
Look, I really want her to like you,

158
00:05:50,820 --> 00:05:52,704
就忍受一下吧 好吗 好的
so just go with it, okay? Okay!

159
00:05:52,706 --> 00:05:54,623
听着 小口耐 你最好立刻马上滚回...
Listen, Wuv-Wuv, you better get your ass back...

160
00:05:56,660 --> 00:05:58,009
又有人来了呀
Another guest?

161
00:05:58,011 --> 00:06:00,662
会是谁呢
Who could this be?

162
00:06:01,380 --> 00:06:02,430
哇 是莉莉
Why, it's Lily!

163
00:06:02,432 --> 00:06:03,665
她是来满足
And she's here to deliver

164
00:06:03,667 --> 00:06:04,683
你的一个要求的
one of your requests!

165
00:06:04,685 --> 00:06:06,968
哦 谢谢 马修
Oh, thank you, Marshall.

166
00:06:06,970 --> 00:06:08,270
哦 不是这个要求
Oh, not that one.

167
00:06:08,272 --> 00:06:10,972
见到我一直以来的偶像
An appearance by my all-time idol,

168
00:06:10,974 --> 00:06:13,024
龙威小子
the Karate Kid!

169
00:06:13,026 --> 00:06:15,009
《龙威小子》是80年代一部振奋人心的经典电影
The Karate Kid was an uplifting '80s classic

170
00:06:15,011 --> 00:06:17,145
讲的是拉尔夫•马奇奥扮演的一个少年的故事
about a teen, played by Ralph Macchio,

171
00:06:17,147 --> 00:06:20,365
他打败了威廉•扎布卡饰演的地头蛇
who defeats the local jerk, played by William Zabka.

172
00:06:20,367 --> 00:06:22,734
至少大部分人是这么认为的
At least, that's how most people saw it.

173
00:06:22,736 --> 00:06:24,653
他来了 还是和以前一样帅
Here he is, just as hot

174
00:06:24,655 --> 00:06:28,123
正如同当年他的《老虎队》杂志照给了一个年轻姑娘
as when his Tiger Beat photo spread gave a young girl

175
00:06:28,125 --> 00:06:29,324
十足的勇气去探索
the courage to explore

176
00:06:29,326 --> 00:06:33,245
自己那突然变得凹凸有致的身体
the suddenly unfamiliar topography of her changing body...

178
00:06:34,247 --> 00:06:36,266
龙威小子
the Karate Kid!

179
00:06:37,668 --> 00:06:38,967
嘿 巴尼 我是拉尔夫
Hey, Barney. It's Ralph.

180
00:06:38,969 --> 00:06:40,302
一直以来 我十分荣幸...
Listen, it's always flattering...

181
00:06:40,304 --> 00:06:41,553
不
No!

182
00:06:42,471 --> 00:06:43,871
我讨厌拉尔夫•马奇奥
I hate Ralph Macchio!

183
00:06:43,873 --> 00:06:46,174
我讨厌他 讨厌他 讨厌他
I hate him, hate him, hate him!

184
00:06:46,176 --> 00:06:48,209
他才不是什么龙威小子
He is not the Karate Kid!

185
00:06:48,211 --> 00:06:50,395
威廉•扎布卡才是龙威小子
The Karate Kid was William Zabka,

186
00:06:50,397 --> 00:06:53,064
眼镜蛇道馆的明星学员
star pupil of the Cobra Kai Dojo,

187
00:06:53,066 --> 00:06:54,599
这头禽兽
who this monster

188
00:06:54,601 --> 00:06:57,885
用一记卑鄙的 违规的高踢腿击败了他
defeated with a cheap, illegal head-kick

190
00:06:57,887 --> 00:07:03,108
成就了电影史上最让人怨念的悲剧结局
in the most tragically haunting film ending of all time.

191
00:07:03,110 --> 00:07:06,161
哦 懂了 我还以为你说他是有趣的那种疯子呢
Oh, see, I thought you meant fun-crazy.

192
00:07:06,163 --> 00:07:07,729
闭嘴 拉尔夫•马奇奥
Shut it, Ralph Macchio.

193
00:07:07,731 --> 00:07:09,781
你干嘛不去找卢克•天行者
Why don't you go have a party with Luke Skywalker

194
00:07:09,783 --> 00:07:13,401
哈利•波特还有战马之类的其他电影大反派们开派对
and Harry Potter and War Horse and all the other movie bad guys

193
00:07:07,731 --> 00:07:13,401
{\a6}巴尼对电影正反派总有自己独到的认知

195
00:07:13,403 --> 00:07:16,538
别来毁我的派对
and stop ruining mine!

196
00:07:16,540 --> 00:07:19,073
真是灾难性的一晚
This night has been catastrophic.

197
00:07:19,075 --> 00:07:21,743
灾难性 大家吹瓶
"Catastrophic"! Everybody pound.

198
00:07:22,678 --> 00:07:23,762
对不起 兄弟
Sorry, bro.

199
00:07:23,764 --> 00:07:24,713
我留下了
I'm staying.

200
00:07:24,715 --> 00:07:26,131
如果这
If this is anything

201
00:07:26,133 --> 00:07:27,749
像我的单身派对一样 脱衣舞娘 美酒
like my bachelor party-- strippers, booze,

202
00:07:27,751 --> 00:07:29,267
绝对不做手活儿 你懂的
definitely no hand stuff-- wink-wink--

203
00:07:29,269 --> 00:07:33,021
这将会变得不可...等一下...思议
it is gonna be in-- wait for it-- credible.

204
00:07:33,023 --> 00:07:34,055
不可思议
Incredible!

205
00:07:34,057 --> 00:07:34,973
哇
Wow.

206
00:07:34,975 --> 00:07:36,591
你们俩还真是挺像的
You guys are actually a lot alike.

207
00:07:36,593 --> 00:07:37,642
你最好把话收回去 先生
You take that back, sir!

208
00:07:37,644 --> 00:07:41,429
我一点都不像拉尔夫•马奇奥
I am nothing like Ralph Macchio!

209
00:07:41,431 --> 00:07:44,315
我说 你们到底有没有去请脱衣舞娘啊
I mean, did you guys even get a stripper?

210
00:07:44,317 --> 00:07:45,483
兄弟
Bro.

211
00:07:45,485 --> 00:07:46,735
兄弟
Bro.

212
00:07:46,737 --> 00:07:48,436
我们当然请脱衣舞娘了
Of course we got a stripper.

213
00:07:48,438 --> 00:07:50,538
我们难道看起来像那种傻到
Do we look like the kind of dweebs

214
00:07:50,540 --> 00:07:52,457
连脱衣舞娘都不请的傻帽吗
who wouldn't get a stripper?

215
00:07:54,444 --> 00:07:55,460
就像谚语里说的一样
And as the saying goes,

216
00:07:55,462 --> 00:07:57,078
在大西洋城外面的平价商务旅馆
what happens in the sensibly-priced

217
00:07:57,080 --> 00:07:59,280
里发生的事情就留在
business hotel outside Atlantic City stays

218
00:07:59,282 --> 00:08:02,283
大西洋城外面的平价商务旅馆里
in the sensibly-priced business hotel outside Atlantic City.

216
00:07:55,462 --> 00:08:02,283
{\a6}{\fs19}改编自 在维加斯发生的一切就留在维加斯里

219
00:08:04,119 --> 00:08:05,620
是谁
Who is it?

220
00:08:05,622 --> 00:08:07,789
警察 我们接到了一个噪声扰民举报...
Police. We got a noise complaint from...

221
00:08:07,791 --> 00:08:10,842
噢 我在骗谁呢 这里都死气沉沉的
Oh, who am I kidding? I can tell it's dead in there.

222
00:08:10,844 --> 00:08:13,011
我是脱衣舞娘
I'm the stripper!

223
00:08:14,963 --> 00:08:16,931
巴尼
Barney?

224
00:08:16,933 --> 00:08:18,266
昆茵
Quinn?

225
00:08:24,347 --> 00:08:27,375
这是你的单身派对吗 你又订婚了吗
This is your bachelor party? You're engaged again,

226
00:08:27,376 --> 00:08:29,660
我们分手还不到一年啊
less than a year after we broke up?

227
00:08:29,662 --> 00:08:31,446
是和罗宾吗
Is it Robin?

228
00:08:31,448 --> 00:08:32,630
等会儿
Now, hold on.

229
00:08:32,632 --> 00:08:35,900
你不是唯一的一个有这么多问题想问的
You're not the only one with questions here.

230
00:08:35,902 --> 00:08:38,252
你们连脱衣舞娘的底细都不摸清吗
You didn't vet the stripper?!

231
00:08:39,121 --> 00:08:40,304
好吧 看到你幸福我很开心
Well, I'm glad you're so happy.

232
00:08:40,306 --> 00:08:42,590
我们分手以后 我不得不搬出纽约
After we broke up, I had to move out of the city,

233
00:08:42,592 --> 00:08:44,792
我的车也被毁掉了 我只好重操旧业
my car got totaled, and I had to go back

234
00:08:44,794 --> 00:08:46,127
继续当脱衣舞娘来付房租
to stripping just to pay rent.

235
00:08:46,129 --> 00:08:49,897
举目四望 我的人生都已经无路可走了
It's like everywhere I look, my life is a dead-end.

236
00:08:49,899 --> 00:08:51,983
哇
Wow.

237
00:08:51,985 --> 00:08:55,302
我很...我很抱歉 昆茵
I am... I'm so sorry, Quinn.

238
00:08:55,304 --> 00:08:56,637
那 你想怎么样
So, how does this work?

239
00:08:56,639 --> 00:08:58,823
是给我私人演出呢 还是其他人也...
Do you give me a private show, or does everyone...?

240
00:08:58,825 --> 00:09:01,192
我不会为你跳脱衣舞的
I am not stripping for you.

241
00:09:01,194 --> 00:09:02,977
你们保证我会有咪咪看的
I was promised boobs.

242
00:09:02,979 --> 00:09:04,112
噢 拉尔夫 如果你想的话 我可以...
Oh, Ralph, if you want, I can...

243
00:09:04,114 --> 00:09:05,663
莉莉
Lily.

244
00:09:05,665 --> 00:09:06,480
那是龙威小子吗
Is that the Karate Kid?

245
00:09:06,482 --> 00:09:07,331
是 是 是
Yes! Yes! Yes!

246
00:09:07,333 --> 00:09:08,282
不是
No!

247
00:09:08,284 --> 00:09:09,333
他还真挺像巴尼的 是吧
He's a lot like Barney, huh?

248
00:09:09,335 --> 00:09:10,868
你最好把这话收回去 女士
You take that back, madam.

249
00:09:10,870 --> 00:09:13,454
我一点都不像拉尔夫•马奇奥
I am nothing like Ralph Macchio!

250
00:09:13,456 --> 00:09:14,756
好 好
Okay, okay.

251
00:09:14,758 --> 00:09:15,840
这样吧
I'll tell you what.

252
00:09:15,842 --> 00:09:18,126
我要为在场的每一个人表演脱衣舞
I am going to strip for everyone here

253
00:09:18,128 --> 00:09:20,628
巴尼除外
except Barney.

254
00:09:20,630 --> 00:09:22,764
我会跳的相当淫荡的
And I'm gonna make it dirty.

255
00:09:22,766 --> 00:09:25,550
搞清楚状况 我是单身派对的主角
Yeah, um, I'm the bachelor.

256
00:09:25,552 --> 00:09:28,186
新郎的首席大腿怎么能不在场呢
Kind of no stripping without the lap of honor.

257
00:09:28,188 --> 00:09:29,837
帮我说几句啊 兄弟们
Back me up, bros.

260
00:09:36,679 --> 00:09:38,196
嘿 罗宾
Hey, Robin.

261
00:09:38,198 --> 00:09:40,347
嘿 亲爱的 在你的单身派对上玩得开心吗
Hey, sweetie, having fun at your bachelor party?

262
00:09:40,349 --> 00:09:43,151
-不开心  -太好了 我在这里简直是生不如死
-No. -Good, 'cause my night's been hell!

263
00:09:43,153 --> 00:09:45,787
这就是倒扫烟囱式
And that's the inverted chimney sweep,

264
00:09:45,789 --> 00:09:48,739
十七种基本爱爱姿势的最后一种
the last of the 17 basic sexual positions.

265
00:09:48,741 --> 00:09:49,907
现在 捆绑...
Now, bondage...

266
00:09:49,909 --> 00:09:52,026
停 我根本不是处女
Stop! I'm not a virgin!

267
00:09:52,028 --> 00:09:54,162
我的餐巾环已经接待过无数的面包条了
My napkin ring has seen plenty of breadsticks.

268
00:09:54,663 --> 00:09:56,547
还有一根法式长棍面包
And one baguette.

269
00:09:56,549 --> 00:09:58,166
我和尼克斯队的一个中锋约会过
I dated a center for the Knicks.

270
00:09:58,168 --> 00:10:00,885
谢天谢地你不是老处女
Oh, thank God you're not a prude.

271
00:10:00,887 --> 00:10:03,037
我们终于可以说人话了
Now we can really talk.

272
00:10:03,039 --> 00:10:05,206
来四杯科斯莫葡萄酒 快点
Four cosmos, pronto!

273
00:10:05,208 --> 00:10:06,507
现在她喝醉了
Now she's drunk,

274
00:10:06,509 --> 00:10:08,810
正抓着一个餐巾环和三个面包棍
holding up a napkin ring and three breadsticks,

275
00:10:08,812 --> 00:10:11,429

275
00:10:08,812 --> 00:10:11,429
大谈特谈她大战克罗斯比 斯蒂尔和纳什的那一夜
and talking about her night with Crosby, Stills and Nash.

275
00:10:08,812 --> 00:10:11,429
{\a6}克罗斯比 斯蒂尔和纳什是一个乐队

276
00:10:11,431 --> 00:10:13,681
服务员 可以给我再来一条面包吗
Waiter, can I have another breadstick?

277
00:10:13,683 --> 00:10:14,649
还有杨
And Young.

277
00:10:13,683 --> 00:10:14,649
{\a6}{\fs16}乐队全称是Crosby, Stills and Nash (and Young)

278
00:10:14,651 --> 00:10:16,234
你回来好吗
Please come back.

279
00:10:16,236 --> 00:10:18,152
好
Okay.

280
00:10:18,154 --> 00:10:20,822
我很快就到
I'll be there soon.

281
00:10:20,824 --> 00:10:22,190
相当漂亮 非常美妙
Real nice. So beautiful.

282
00:10:22,192 --> 00:10:23,774
我觉得我们做到啦 我们真的做到啦 是吧
I think we really did it. I think we did it, you know?

283
00:10:23,776 --> 00:10:25,860
你啥也没错过哈
You didn't miss a thing.

284
00:10:25,862 --> 00:10:27,245
-噢 昆茵  -怎么啦
-Oh, Quinn? -Yeah?

285
00:10:27,247 --> 00:10:30,414
你那里沾了...一点东西
You got a little... something.

286
00:10:30,416 --> 00:10:32,583
噢 哦
Oh! Oh.

287
00:10:36,539 --> 00:10:37,905
咱们调头回去吧
Let's head back, guys.

288
00:10:37,907 --> 00:10:40,241
这一晚上从头到尾都是低能
This night has been completely half-assed.

289
00:10:40,243 --> 00:10:41,575
你显然错过了脱衣舞表演
You obviously missed the strip show.

291
00:10:43,246 --> 00:10:45,596
泰德 这可是我的单身派对
Ted, this was my bachelor party.

292
00:10:45,598 --> 00:10:49,050
一个人一生中就那么两三次
A man only gets two or three of these in his lifetime.

293
00:10:49,052 --> 00:10:51,252
你就是这么对我的吗
And this is all you do for me?

294
00:10:51,254 --> 00:10:53,187
够了 就此结束吧
That's it, I'm calling it.

295
00:10:53,189 --> 00:10:55,439
谁需要搭便车回纽约
Who needs a ride back to the city?

296
00:10:57,192 --> 00:10:58,142
噢
Oh.

297
00:10:58,144 --> 00:11:00,194
噢 大伙儿 等下 先等下
Oh, guys, wait, hold on, hold on.

298
00:11:01,930 --> 00:11:03,264
喝酒
Drinking.

299
00:11:03,932 --> 00:11:04,866
一口闷
A shot.

300
00:11:06,268 --> 00:11:07,601
射击
Shooting.

2
00:11:07,603 --> 00:11:08,703
枪
A gun.

3
00:11:09,705 --> 00:11:11,072
枪击
Shot, gun.

4
00:11:11,074 --> 00:11:12,273
你要副驾驶位吗
Shotgun?

5
00:11:13,293 --> 00:11:15,576
天 真是挤死了
Man, it's crowded in here.

6
00:11:15,578 --> 00:11:18,296
没错 就跟坐在小丑车里面似的
I know, it's like a clown car.

7
00:11:15,578 --> 00:11:18,296
{\a6}小丑的车子通常很小很拥挤

8
00:11:18,298 --> 00:11:20,614
如果我磨在拉尔夫的大腿上 倒是可以腾出些地方
Well, I can make some room by grinding on Ralph's lap.

9
00:11:20,616 --> 00:11:21,632
坐在
sitting!

10
00:11:21,634 --> 00:11:22,917
我 我是说 坐在
I-I meant, I meant sitting.

11
00:11:22,919 --> 00:11:25,753
这简直是史上最烂的单身派对
This is the worst bachelor party ever.

12
00:11:25,755 --> 00:11:29,891
哦 我的单身派对简直是天...等一下...
Man, my bachelor party was incr-- wait for it--

13
00:11:29,893 --> 00:11:31,142
你们最好是饿了
and I hope you're hungry,

14
00:11:31,144 --> 00:11:34,345
因为这个词的后一半是...菜啊
'cause the second half of this word is-- edible!

15
00:11:34,347 --> 00:11:35,629
天才啊
Incredible!

16
00:11:35,631 --> 00:11:37,732
自我握手
Self-shake.

17
00:11:39,686 --> 00:11:41,135
你快把你说的咽回去 小丑
You take that back, clown.

18
00:11:41,137 --> 00:11:43,237
我跟拉尔夫•马奇奥完全是两派
I am nothing like Ralph Macchio!

19
00:11:43,239 --> 00:11:44,355
没错
Yeah.

20
00:11:44,357 --> 00:11:45,990
你和小丑的共同点还多些呢
You've got more in common with the clown,

21
00:11:45,992 --> 00:11:47,141
只不过他那套衣服比你的贵些
except his suit's more expensive.

22
00:11:47,143 --> 00:11:48,142
嘿呦
Hey, yo!

23
00:11:49,162 --> 00:11:50,311
我是说 哪个怂货会在
I mean, what kind of loser

24
00:11:50,313 --> 00:11:52,413
离亚特拉大城不远的地方办单身派对
has his bachelor party ten yards from A.C.

25
00:11:52,415 --> 00:11:54,115
却没去赌一把
and doesn't even gamble?

26
00:12:01,157 --> 00:12:02,990
哦 不好意思
Oh. Oh, sorry.

27
00:12:02,992 --> 00:12:05,710
对不起啊 不是故意的啊
Sorry. Sorry.

28
00:12:05,712 --> 00:12:07,545
不好意思
Sorry.

29
00:12:07,547 --> 00:12:08,930
哦 等一下
Oh... oh, wait.

30
00:12:08,932 --> 00:12:09,931
再来一小下
Just a little more.

31
00:12:09,933 --> 00:12:11,349
好啦 对不起啦
Okay, sorry.

32
00:12:11,351 --> 00:12:12,633
好啦
Okay.

31
00:12:13,038 --> 00:12:14,939
金龙翻来 哩个系

33
00:12:15,038 --> 00:12:18,439
兄弟受诫礼
bro mitzvah!

34
00:12:18,441 --> 00:12:20,524
孩子们 赌博的细节就不详细说了
Kids, I'll skip over the gambling.

35
00:12:20,526 --> 00:12:22,893
跟我之前提到过的一样 这规则十分繁琐
Like I said, it was a complicated game.

36
00:12:22,895 --> 00:12:25,446
不过你们老爹倒是很快就搞懂规则了
Although your old man did pick it up pretty quickly.

37
00:12:27,567 --> 00:12:28,532
嘿
Hey!

38
00:12:28,534 --> 00:12:30,568
你一下就赢了300刀啊
You just won 300 bucks!

39
00:12:30,570 --> 00:12:32,937
我一下就输了5000刀
I just lost $5,000.

40
00:12:32,939 --> 00:12:34,438
哦 对 因为是只鸡
Oh, right. 'Cause the chicken.

41
00:12:34,440 --> 00:12:36,690
没错 这样就是5000刀
Yep, that-that's $5,000, yeah.

42
00:12:38,661 --> 00:12:39,794
你看 我笑是因为
See, I'm laughing

43
00:12:39,796 --> 00:12:41,662
你没能领略我脱去上装的风采
because you couldn't see me take my top off,

44
00:12:41,664 --> 00:12:43,998
-我却能目睹你把衬衣都输掉了的惨样  -嘿呦
-but I just saw you lose your shirt. -Hey-yo!

45
00:12:44,000 --> 00:12:45,683
咱该回去了
We have to go back.

46
00:12:45,685 --> 00:12:47,885
怂货 对不起 刚才真的打了个喷嚏
Loser! Sorry, that was a real sneeze.

47
00:12:47,887 --> 00:12:50,388
你们怕是没听清我刚说什么吧
Might have made you miss what I was saying.

48
00:12:50,390 --> 00:12:51,422
怂货
Loser!

49
00:12:53,042 --> 00:12:54,708
我们哪都不去了
We're not going anywhere.

50
00:12:54,710 --> 00:12:57,878
我还有机会力挽狂澜让今晚变成传奇
I can still make this night legendary.

51
00:12:57,880 --> 00:12:59,897
啊 啊
Uh, uh...

52
00:13:01,985 --> 00:13:03,717
哦哦
Oh, oh.

53
00:13:03,719 --> 00:13:06,354
好 我赊到钱了
Okay, I got some credit.

54
00:13:06,356 --> 00:13:08,222
我只需要 呃
I just... mm...

55
00:13:08,224 --> 00:13:09,774
马修 站那边去给我些好运
Marshall, stand over there for good luck?

56
00:13:09,776 --> 00:13:11,309
哦 没问题
Oh, sure.

57
00:13:15,947 --> 00:13:17,731
好的 好的
Okay, okay.

57
00:13:17,747 --> 00:13:18,731
一

57
00:13:18,747 --> 00:13:19,431
二

57
00:13:19,447 --> 00:13:20,331
三

57
00:13:20,337 --> 00:13:21,731
四

58
00:13:24,674 --> 00:13:27,408
哦 哦
Oh! Oh!

59
00:13:27,410 --> 00:13:30,378
你这个狗娘养的 你成功啦
You crazy son of a bitch, you did it!

60
00:13:30,380 --> 00:13:33,097
我刚输了八万刀
I just lost $80,000.

61
00:13:33,099 --> 00:13:34,849
哦 对对 没错 因为那个黑色软糖
Oh, right, right, yeah. 'Cause the black jelly bean.

62
00:13:34,851 --> 00:13:36,183
那就是八万刀 他说的没错
That-That's $80,000. He's right.

63
00:13:37,970 --> 00:13:40,438
告诉你哦 拉尔夫
You know, Ralph,

64
00:13:40,440 --> 00:13:44,425
之前我去了沙龙 身上涂满蜜蜡 然后统统都刮掉了
Earlier at the salon,I waxed on,then waxed off

65
00:13:44,427 --> 00:13:46,260
一丝不剩
Everywhere.

66
00:13:46,262 --> 00:13:49,363
呃 听着 女士 你的老公就在...
Uh, listen, lady, your husband is, like...

67
00:13:49,365 --> 00:13:51,649
嘿 你老公哪去了
Hey, where is your husband?

68
00:13:51,651 --> 00:13:52,783
马修
Marshall?

69
00:13:52,785 --> 00:13:54,068
马修哪去了
Where's Marshall?!

70
00:13:54,070 --> 00:13:57,872
好吧 莉莉 别反应过激哦 其实呢
Okay, Lily, don't overreact, but...

71
00:13:59,376 --> 00:14:02,374
{\a6}你有乜嘢俾我

71
00:13:59,376 --> 00:14:02,374
我可以信任你 但是你要给我个抵押品

72
00:14:02,578 --> 00:14:04,795
好啦 他们又赊了点给我
Okay, I got some credit.

73
00:14:04,797 --> 00:14:06,914
马修 站那边去给我些好运
Marshall, stand over there for good luck?

74
00:14:06,916 --> 00:14:09,083
哦 没问题
Oh, sure.

75
00:14:10,187 --> 00:14:12,539
给金龙八万块的筹码

75
00:14:12,787 --> 00:14:14,839
你把我老公卖掉了吗
You sold my husband?!

76
00:14:14,841 --> 00:14:16,891
莉莉 你能不能多学学中国黑帮
Lily, can you be more like the Chinese mobster

77
00:14:16,893 --> 00:14:18,292
给我也放个高利贷啊
and give me some credit?

78
00:14:18,294 --> 00:14:21,562
我会去赎马修回来的 只是需要弄些钱
I'm going back for Marshall; I just need to get some money.

79
00:14:21,564 --> 00:14:24,598
完全用不着担心 他们是"好的"黑帮
You have nothing to worry about; these are the "Good" Mobsters.

80
00:14:24,600 --> 00:14:27,234
哇哦 什么样的跳梁小丑会这样对待朋友
Wow, what kind of bozo does that to a friend?

80
00:14:24,600 --> 00:14:27,234
{\a6}bozo也有混蛋的意思 通常用来骂白人

81
00:14:27,236 --> 00:14:29,854
闭嘴 拉尔夫•马奇奥
Shut it, Ralph Macchio!

82
00:14:29,856 --> 00:14:30,938
不 你才闭嘴
No, you shut it!

83
00:14:30,940 --> 00:14:34,358
拉尔夫•马奇奥说的没错 你就是个跳梁小丑
Ralph Macchio's right, you are a bozo.

84
00:14:34,360 --> 00:14:36,527
呃 我觉得他们的意思是"浅色人种"
Um, I think they prefer "People of bright color."

85
00:14:34,360 --> 00:14:36,527
{\a6}昆茵也是金发白人

85
00:14:36,529 --> 00:14:38,145
你知道单身派对的意义何在吗
You know what a bachelor party's about?

86
00:14:38,147 --> 00:14:40,664
就在于和你的朋友在一起玩的尽兴
Hanging out with your friends and having a good time.

87
00:14:40,666 --> 00:14:43,701
但是只在乎自己尽兴 把朋友放一边去了
But you only care about the good time, not the friends.

88
00:14:43,703 --> 00:14:44,818
所以说你给我听好了
So you know what?

89
00:14:44,820 --> 00:14:47,004
我也不再关心你了
I'm-I'm done caring about you then.

90
00:14:47,006 --> 00:14:48,489
我走了
I'm out of here.

91
00:14:48,491 --> 00:14:49,790
泰德
Ted...

92
00:14:51,659 --> 00:14:53,878
泰德 泰德 我刚...
Ted, Ted, I have...

93
00:14:53,880 --> 00:14:56,347
我刚刚好不容易摆脱掉 你那尼克•诺尔特的正面照
I just tore your mom away from a living version

94
00:14:56,349 --> 00:14:59,433
活物版的老娘 然后叫了辆车送他回家
of a Nick Nolte mug shot and put her in a cab home.

95
00:14:53,880 --> 00:14:59,433
{\a6}{\fs16}"尼克•诺尔特的正面照"美国明星烂醉被捕照片 形容烂醉如泥

96
00:14:59,435 --> 00:15:01,005
我谢谢你在我
Thank you for abandoning me

97
00:15:01,007 --> 00:15:03,771
人生中最糟糕的夜晚 抛弃了我
on what has been one of the worst nights of my life.

98
00:15:03,773 --> 00:15:06,173
好的 你知道我的价码 不过我会因为
So, it's my usual fee, plus I always charge

99
00:15:06,175 --> 00:15:08,559
小丑蹭酥胸的环节多要一百刀
an extra hundred for girl-on-clown action.

100
00:15:08,561 --> 00:15:10,978
她在这干什么呢
What the hell is she doing here?

101
00:15:10,980 --> 00:15:12,847
罗宾 我发誓 什么都没发生
Robin, I swear, nothing happened.

101
00:15:12,980 --> 00:15:14,547
意思就是只有手活
That means just handstuff

401
00:15:14,901 --> 00:15:17,034
-你  -嗷
-You...! -Oh!

402
00:15:17,036 --> 00:15:20,871
不 住手 别打了
No, no, stop, stop, stop!

403
00:15:20,873 --> 00:15:21,956
对不起 巴尼
Sorry, Barney,

404
00:15:21,958 --> 00:15:25,876
这事 这件事我没法原谅你
this... this-this is unforgivable.

405
00:15:25,878 --> 00:15:27,328
我们结束了
It's over.

406
00:15:29,548 --> 00:15:32,082
其实
You know...

407
00:15:32,084 --> 00:15:34,034
我一直没机会这样做
I never got to do that.

408
00:15:43,646 --> 00:15:45,212
泰德吗
Ted?

409
00:15:45,214 --> 00:15:47,014
我是罗宾
Robin.

410
00:15:47,016 --> 00:15:49,817
一切按计划进行
We're right on schedule.

411
00:15:53,574 --> 00:15:55,665
-巴尼都想死了算了呢  -我知道 这太棒了
-Barney is suicidal. -I know, it's awesome!

412
00:15:56,722 --> 00:15:58,389
是的 孩子们 我们计划好了
Yep, kids, we had planned out

413
00:15:58,391 --> 00:15:59,757
那天晚上的每一个步骤
every step of the night.

414
00:15:59,759 --> 00:16:01,792
这一切都从三周前开始说起
It started three weeks earlier.

415
00:16:01,794 --> 00:16:03,811
你们一定会让我失望的
...and you will disappoint me.

416
00:16:04,813 --> 00:16:06,931
但尽量弄好点 行吧
But make it great, okay?

417
00:16:06,933 --> 00:16:08,983
哦 一定会很棒的 放心吧
Oh, it'll be great, all right!

418
00:16:08,985 --> 00:16:10,868
经过整整两周的苦思冥想
Okay, after two weeks of brainstorming,

419
00:16:10,870 --> 00:16:13,320
目前我就想到了普瑞来
all I have on my list so far is Purell.

419
00:16:10,870 --> 00:16:13,320
{\a6}普瑞来 洗手液公司

420
00:16:13,322 --> 00:16:14,855
马修 你呢
Marshall, what do you got?

421
00:16:14,857 --> 00:16:17,107
多亏你 现在没了
Well, nothing now.

422
00:16:17,109 --> 00:16:18,626
这根本不可能完成啊
This is impossible!

423
00:16:18,628 --> 00:16:20,744
你要怎么给一个将人生每个夜晚都安排的有声有色的人
How do you make something memorable for a guy

424
00:16:20,746 --> 00:16:22,997
设计另一个另人难忘的夜晚呢
who makes every night the best night of his life?

425
00:16:22,999 --> 00:16:26,400
给他最糟糕的夜晚就行了
Give him the worst night of his life.

426
00:16:26,402 --> 00:16:30,371
我们订个最差的房间
We'll give him the worst hotel room

426
00:16:26,402 --> 00:16:28,471
{\a6}招数之"巴尼"

427
00:16:30,373 --> 00:16:32,155
安排最烂的节目
with the worst entertainment,

428
00:16:32,157 --> 00:16:34,091
错的龙威小子
the wrong Karate Kid,

429
00:16:34,093 --> 00:16:37,327
还有他最不想见到的脱衣舞女
and the absolute last stripper he would want to see.

430
00:16:37,329 --> 00:16:38,512
等等
Hold on.

431
00:16:38,514 --> 00:16:40,764
你希望我装作生活一团糟
You want me to pretend my life's gone to crap

432
00:16:40,766 --> 00:16:43,333
不得不重操旧业 只是为了整蛊前未婚夫吗
and I'm back to stripping just screw with my ex-fiance?

433
00:16:44,102 --> 00:16:45,102
这我喜欢
I love it!

434
00:16:46,254 --> 00:16:48,973
派对太糟糕 差到他急着想离开
That party will be so terrible, he'll have to leave it.

435
00:16:48,975 --> 00:16:52,676
然后我会让他狡猾的宿敌说...
Then I'll instruct his arch-nemesis to say...

436
00:16:52,678 --> 00:16:54,529
什么样的怂货才会在
what kind of loser has his bachelor party

437
00:16:54,531 --> 00:16:57,531
离亚特拉大城不远的地方办单身派对 却不去赌一把
ten yards from A.C. And doesn't even gamble?

438
00:16:57,533 --> 00:16:59,867
巴尼会拿着我给他的一信封现金
Barney will take the envelope of cash I gave him

439
00:16:59,869 --> 00:17:02,236
掉头直奔我们的陷阱
and head straight into our trap.

440
00:17:02,238 --> 00:17:03,387
等等
Hold on.

441
00:17:03,389 --> 00:17:05,489
你希望我们在赌局中出老千
You want us to rig a casino game

442
00:17:05,491 --> 00:17:07,574
来整蛊一名以前挥土如金的高级常客吗
to trick one of our former high rollers?

443
00:17:07,576 --> 00:17:09,410
呃
Um...

444
00:17:09,412 --> 00:17:10,244
我爱这个计划
I love it.

445
00:17:10,246 --> 00:17:11,879
恩 那到时候你就让
Well, then you get Barney

446
00:17:11,881 --> 00:17:14,197
巴尼选他们中的一个作为抵押
to use one of these guys as collateral.

447
00:17:14,199 --> 00:17:15,866
-他应该会选我  -什么
-He'll probably choose me. -What?

448
00:17:15,868 --> 00:17:17,217
是啊 我更值钱
Well, I'd be worth more.

449
00:17:17,219 --> 00:17:18,936
有一口好牙
Yeah. Perfect teeth.

450
00:17:18,938 --> 00:17:20,338
是哈 只是
Yeah, it's just, uh,

451
00:17:20,339 --> 00:17:22,056
只是我的运动神经比你好多了
just I'm way more athletic than you.

452
00:17:22,058 --> 00:17:23,390
是哈 这句话是从一个
Yeah, this coming from the guy

453
00:17:23,392 --> 00:17:25,392
滑雪球从没赢过我的人嘴里说出来的
who's never beaten me at skee-ball.

454
00:17:25,394 --> 00:17:27,511
人家黑道爷会选择你的唯一理由是
The only reason a mobster might choose you is because

455
00:17:27,513 --> 00:17:29,880
他们怕遭到我"被解救的马修"的报复
they'd be afraid I'd go all "Marshall Unchained" On them,

456
00:17:29,882 --> 00:17:31,382
而明显你就构不成什么威胁
which obviously isn't a risk with you.

457
00:17:31,384 --> 00:17:34,401
是吗 你想看看"被解救的泰德"吗 啊
Oh, you want to see some "Ted Unchained," Huh?

458
00:17:34,403 --> 00:17:36,236
我就让你看看"被解救的泰德"
I'll show you Ted Unchained!

459
00:17:37,238 --> 00:17:38,355
马修 你能不能
Marshall, would you mind

460
00:17:38,357 --> 00:17:39,890
站到那边去 给我点好运
standing over there for good luck?

461
00:17:39,892 --> 00:17:41,659
哦 当然可以
Oh, yeah, sure.

462
00:17:45,780 --> 00:17:47,164
与此同时 我会确保
Meanwhile, I'll make sure

463
00:17:47,166 --> 00:17:50,167
他会在我最噩梦的场景中 放我鸽子
he's abandoned me in my nightmare scenario.

464
00:17:50,169 --> 00:17:53,454
等等 你希望我帮你整自己的儿子吗
Hold on. You want me to help you trick my own son?

465
00:17:54,456 --> 00:17:55,622
我爱这个计划
I love it.

466
00:17:56,509 --> 00:17:57,508
巴尼活该
Barney deserves it.

467
00:17:57,510 --> 00:17:59,710
你知不知道 他告诉我你是处女
You know, he told me you were a virgin.

468
00:17:59,712 --> 00:18:01,462
太荒谬了
Ridiculous!

469
00:18:01,464 --> 00:18:02,513
我也觉得
I know.

470
00:18:02,515 --> 00:18:05,966
你是个荡妇 跟我一样的
You are a dirty ho-bag just like me.

471
00:18:06,685 --> 00:18:08,251
可他却这么地爱你
But he loves you so much.

472
00:18:08,253 --> 00:18:09,303
我也好爱你哦
And so do I.

473
00:18:11,757 --> 00:18:13,590
等等 这些事情对巴尼
Wait, hold on. Is there any chance

474
00:18:13,592 --> 00:18:16,643
会不会有点太过分了
this is all too mean to Barney?

475
00:18:19,699 --> 00:18:21,331
开个玩笑
Just kidding.

476
00:18:21,333 --> 00:18:23,150
好了 现在只需要完成最终乐章了
Okay, we just need the finale.

477
00:18:23,152 --> 00:18:25,319
哦 中国黑帮把我的手咔嚓砍下来
Oh! The Chinese mobsters chop off my hand

478
00:18:25,321 --> 00:18:26,870
让巴尼亲眼目睹
right in front of Barney!

479
00:18:27,706 --> 00:18:29,907
就是这样 我们全都一样兴奋
Yes, we're all equally enthused!

480
00:18:32,043 --> 00:18:34,044
好了 计划是这样 在我甩手走人之后...
Okay, here's the plan. After I storm off...

481
00:18:34,046 --> 00:18:35,879
巴尼
Barney!

482
00:18:35,881 --> 00:18:37,965
巴尼 快点 把钱给他们
Barney, hurry! Give them the money!

483
00:18:37,967 --> 00:18:39,833
-求你了 快点啊  -哦 不好
-Please, hurry! -Oh, no!

484
00:18:39,835 --> 00:18:41,802
中国黑帮要把马修送回来
The Chinese mobster is giving Marshall back

485
00:18:41,804 --> 00:18:43,387
换我去当人质
and taking me hostage instead,

486
00:18:43,389 --> 00:18:46,123
因为他说明显是我更值钱
because he says I'm obviously more valuable!

487
00:18:46,125 --> 00:18:48,008
你能 能把门打开吗
Can you, can you unlock the door?

488
00:18:48,010 --> 00:18:49,059
巴尼 求你了
Barney, please!

489
00:18:49,061 --> 00:18:50,761
不然他们就要砍掉我的手
They're gonna chop off my hand!

490
00:18:50,763 --> 00:18:51,795
他们不会的
No, they're not!

491
00:18:51,797 --> 00:18:53,296
他们说了你自由了 而且我记得 
They said you're free, and I think

492
00:18:53,298 --> 00:18:55,399
我们都同意这不是黑道爷会做的事
we agreed that's not something mobsters would do.

493
00:18:55,401 --> 00:18:57,234
泰德 别闹了 这是我的戏份
Ted, come on! This is my thing!

494
00:18:57,236 --> 00:18:58,402
别伤害他
Don't hurt him.

495
00:18:58,404 --> 00:18:59,570
我有钱
I've got the money.

496
00:18:59,572 --> 00:19:00,988
太迟了
Too late!

497
00:19:03,942 --> 00:19:06,026
别砍我玩滑雪球这只手啊
Not my skee-ball hand!

498
00:19:06,978 --> 00:19:08,695
-不  -不
-No...! -No...!

499
00:19:08,697 --> 00:19:10,064
不要
No!

500
00:19:11,816 --> 00:19:14,317
求你们 别射我的脸 或者裆部
Please, just don't shoot me in the face... or the crotch!

501
00:19:14,319 --> 00:19:16,670
惊喜吧
Surprise!

502
00:19:16,672 --> 00:19:19,206
这是怎么回事
What's going on?

503
00:19:19,208 --> 00:19:20,707
是这样 我们决定帮你
Well, we decided to give you

504
00:19:20,709 --> 00:19:23,093
完成你在单身派对上想做的每一件事情
everything you wanted for your bachelor party

505
00:19:23,095 --> 00:19:25,162
而且让你毫不知情
without you even realizing it.

506
00:19:26,931 --> 00:19:29,883
等等 这就是你让我以为马修可能会死的原因吗
Wait, so that's why you made me think Marshall might die?

507
00:19:31,102 --> 00:19:33,670
还让我以为我输光了所有钱 我的朋友们都讨厌我
And I'd lost all that money and my friends hated me

508
00:19:33,672 --> 00:19:35,439
我的婚礼也取消了 是吗
and my wedding was off?

509
00:19:35,441 --> 00:19:38,225
你就决定用所能想象到的
You just decided to-to check off

511
00:19:38,227 --> 00:19:42,980
最极端最扭曲的方式来完成单子上的每一项吗
everything on this list in the most twisted way imaginable?

513
00:19:42,982 --> 00:19:45,365
真真是太赞了
That is awesome!

514
00:19:45,367 --> 00:19:48,535
而且这全是某个女孩一手策划的哦
And it was all planned by a girl.

515
00:19:48,537 --> 00:19:49,620
哇哦
Wow!

516
00:19:51,689 --> 00:19:54,124
那 莉莉...
So, Lily...

517
00:19:54,126 --> 00:19:56,076
一会儿你想不想 呃...
later on tonight, you want to, um...?

518
00:19:56,078 --> 00:19:58,295
喔 喔 喔
Whoa, whoa, whoa.

519
00:19:58,297 --> 00:20:00,664
刚才那只是演戏的一部分
That was all just part of the act.

520
00:20:00,666 --> 00:20:02,382
你是知道的 对吧
Y-You knew that, right?

521
00:20:03,218 --> 00:20:04,802
知道啊 当然知道
Yeah! Totally.

522
00:20:04,804 --> 00:20:06,536
咱们圆满完成了 不是吗
We pulled it off, right?

523
00:20:06,538 --> 00:20:08,038
柏拉图式握手
Platonic shake!

524
00:20:14,078 --> 00:20:19,650
大家听我说 感谢你们为我办这么棒的兄弟受诫礼
Everyone, everyone, thank you for an incredible bro mitzvah.

525
00:20:19,652 --> 00:20:20,734
恭喜兄弟
Mazel brov!

525
00:20:19,652 --> 00:20:22,552
{\a6}原为Mazel tov 希伯来语里恭喜的意思

526
00:20:20,736 --> 00:20:22,552
恭喜兄弟
Mazel brov!

527
00:20:24,406 --> 00:20:26,607
嗯 你其实没有把单子上的每一项都做完
Mm, oh, you didn't really get everything on the list.

528
00:20:26,609 --> 00:20:28,826
无意冒犯啊 拉尔夫•马奇奥
N-No offense to Ralph Macchio,

530
00:20:28,828 --> 00:20:31,161
但他才不是龙威小子呢
but he ain't the Karate Kid.

531
00:20:31,163 --> 00:20:33,113
我完全同意你的说法
I couldn't agree with you more.

532
00:20:35,083 --> 00:20:38,085
你知道 他们差点就不能请到我了
You know, they almost didn't get me.

533
00:20:39,838 --> 00:20:43,790
但在18个语音留言之后
But after 18 voice mails...

534
00:20:43,792 --> 00:20:46,593
我回了罗宾的电话
I returned Robin's call.

535
00:20:46,595 --> 00:20:47,961
她告诉我
And she told me

536
00:20:47,963 --> 00:20:50,848
你是这世界上少数几个
how you're one of the few people in the world

537
00:20:50,850 --> 00:20:53,100
真正理解《龙威小子》这部电影的人之一
who truly gets The Karate Kid movie.

538
00:20:54,252 --> 00:20:57,938
所以当她问我能不能帮忙时
So when she asked if I'd help,

539
00:20:57,940 --> 00:21:00,357
我的答案只可能是...
well, my answer just had to be...

540
00:21:02,527 --> 00:21:04,311
是
{\fs16}{\b0}{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\3c&H2F2F2F&}{\4c&H000000&}はい

541
00:21:04,853 --> 00:21:07,153
威廉•扎布卡
William Zabka!

542
00:21:07,155 --> 00:21:11,755
HIMYM字幕组 谢谢观看

542
00:21:11,957 --> 00:21:37,255
欢迎关注字幕组新浪微博及人人网主页
@HIMYM字幕组
