1
00:00:02,080 --> 00:00:04,303
孩子们 2013年春天
Kids, in the spring of 2013,

1
00:00:02,080 --> 00:00:06,303
{\a6}2030年

2
00:00:04,403 --> 00:00:07,154
在那场重大婚礼前 我们都在处理一些余留的问题
we were all tying up loose ends before the big wedding.

3
00:00:07,263 --> 00:00:08,929
我正是在这个房间里
I was right here in this very room,

4
00:00:08,931 --> 00:00:10,681
给房子装修画上句号
putting the finishing touches on the house.

5
00:00:14,686 --> 00:00:17,771
饶了我吧
Oh, come on!

6
00:00:17,773 --> 00:00:20,074
巴尼和罗宾都已经快排练好
Barney and Robin were wrapping up rehearsal

7
00:00:20,076 --> 00:00:21,008
他们跳的第一支舞了
for their first dance.

8
00:00:21,010 --> 00:00:23,444
那真太棒了 我们可以做得更好
That was amazing. We can do better.

9
00:00:23,446 --> 00:00:24,644
从头开始 各位
Back to one, everyone!

10
00:00:24,646 --> 00:00:28,015
重新装好炮弹 我们准备再来一次
Reload the cannons, we'll go again right away.

11
00:00:30,152 --> 00:00:31,502
莉莉和马修正忙着打包行李
And Lily and Marshall were packing

12
00:00:31,504 --> 00:00:33,754
准备去意大利工作生活一年
for their year in Italy.

13
00:00:34,957 --> 00:00:36,924
喂
Hello.

14
00:00:36,926 --> 00:00:38,842
我的宝贝儿媳妇怎么样啊
How's my favorite daughter-in-law?

15
00:00:38,844 --> 00:00:41,044
呃 事情有点多
Oh, things are a bit crazy here.

17
00:00:41,046 --> 00:00:43,013
我们正准备举家搬到罗马
We've got this big move to Rome coming up,

18
00:00:43,015 --> 00:00:44,715
而且 我一直觉得
and I, I just can't shake the feeling

19
00:00:44,717 --> 00:00:46,967
我好像忘带了什么 
that I'm forgetting something, you know.

20
00:00:46,969 --> 00:00:49,520
我懂 我懂 我是有点不正常了 是吧
I know, I know, I'm being crazy, right?

21
00:00:49,522 --> 00:00:51,271
是吧 朱迪
Right, Judy?

22
00:00:51,273 --> 00:00:52,356
是吧 朱迪
Right, Judy?

23
00:00:52,358 --> 00:00:55,109
你们居然要搬去罗马
You're moving to Rome?!

24
00:00:55,944 --> 00:00:57,010
是我妈妈吗
Is that my mom?

25
00:00:57,012 --> 00:00:59,646
别提罗马
Don't mention Rome.

1
00:01:02,200 --> 00:01:04,200
{\a1}{\fs17}　　　　 老爸\N　　　  　　 老妈\N　　 　　 浪漫史\N{\fs16}{\bord1}{\3c&H00DCE1&}　　  　　　　第八季  第二十四集\N
{\fnDaxlinePro-Regular}{\fs19}{\b0}{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\3c&H2F2F2F&}{\4c&H000000&}{\a1}　　　　　S08E24 Something New

2
00:01:04,310 --> 00:01:07,310
{\fs16}翻译: @卟哒哒伽马 @麟礡 @阿狸小H @moonywen文妹\N{\3c&H00DCE1&}{\bord1}@KRengine达 @Big-Fudge @纷扬DLL @Mr_Gao703 @@KRengine达\N{\3c&H007EFF&}校对: @我叫肉鸭鸭 @晒小花

3
00:01:07,311 --> 00:01:10,311
{\fs17}{\bord1}校对: @麟礡 @阿狸小H\N{\3c&H00DCE1&}{\bord1}压制: @Big-Fudge\N{\3c&H007EFF&}统筹+后期: 相约九月肉小鸭 下季再见晒小花

4
00:01:10,595 --> 00:01:12,995
HIMYM字幕组 倾情奉献

29
00:01:13,774 --> 00:01:15,807
你没有跟你老妈说要去罗马的事啊
You didn't tell your mom about Rome?

30
00:01:15,808 --> 00:01:17,617
感觉不太合适吧
It didn't feel right.

31
00:01:17,618 --> 00:01:19,168
这消息不应该在电话上说啊
This isn't over-the-phone news.

32
00:01:19,170 --> 00:01:20,586
必须得当面说才行
This is face-to-face news.

33
00:01:20,588 --> 00:01:23,288
所以我准备到了圣诞节见面的时候再告诉她
I was gonna tell her when we see her at Christmas.

34
00:01:23,290 --> 00:01:24,673
你准备一直等到
You were gonna wait and tell her

35
00:01:24,675 --> 00:01:27,176
我们都搬去住了六个月了再告诉她吗
after we had already been living there for six months?

36
00:01:27,178 --> 00:01:29,962
那...可真是一个好主意啊
That... was a great plan.

37
00:01:29,964 --> 00:01:31,096
喵的
Damn it.

38
00:01:33,049 --> 00:01:34,800
喂 麻麻 我是马修
Hey, Mom, it's Marshall.

39
00:01:34,802 --> 00:01:36,268
如果你们真要搬去罗马
If you're moving to Rome,

40
00:01:36,270 --> 00:01:40,472
我起码得在你们走之前见见我孙子
I at least need to see my grandson before you go!

41
00:01:40,474 --> 00:01:42,891
那是自然 所以呢 我们很乐意
Of course, and that is why we would love

42
00:01:42,893 --> 00:01:45,144
让您来我们这住上一个星期
for you to come visit us for a week.

43
00:01:45,146 --> 00:01:47,196
不行
No.

44
00:01:47,198 --> 00:01:48,897
这地方都已经打包好了
The place will be all packed up.

45
00:01:48,899 --> 00:01:51,683
哦 好吧 对了 老妈 有个更好的主意
Oh, oh, uh, okay, hey, Mom, better idea:

46
00:01:51,685 --> 00:01:54,069
要不我们一起上你那儿住一个星期怎么样
how about we all come visit you for a week?

47
00:01:54,071 --> 00:01:55,788
我没法去明尼苏达待一个星期啊
I can't go to Minnesota for a week.

48
00:01:55,790 --> 00:01:57,873
我得上班
I have a job.

49
00:01:57,875 --> 00:02:00,526
好吧 老妈 是这样的 莉莉得上班
Okay, Mom, here's the plan: um, Lily has to work,

50
00:02:00,528 --> 00:02:04,029
所以我和马尔文去你那儿待一个星期
so Marvin and I will come visit you for a whole week,

51
00:02:04,031 --> 00:02:05,951
我看看能不能赶上下一班飞机
and I-I'll see if I can get a last-minute flight.

52
00:02:06,800 --> 00:02:10,385
你要把我襁褓中的宝贝儿子
You are going to take my infant son

53
00:02:10,387 --> 00:02:12,671
从我身边带走 整整一个星期吗
away from me for a whole week?

54
00:02:12,673 --> 00:02:15,674
呜哈
Whoo!

55
00:02:15,676 --> 00:02:17,860
你今晚想要干嘛
So, what do you want to do tonight--

56
00:02:17,862 --> 00:02:20,262
喝到看不清路 还是放火烧掉一辆车
drink ourselves blind, set a car on fire?

57
00:02:20,264 --> 00:02:22,815
或者看一个电影
Ooh, watch a movie that doesn't start

58
00:02:22,817 --> 00:02:25,684
开头不是一盏台灯跳到大写字母I上的那种
with a desk lamp jumping on top of a capital "I"?

58
00:02:22,817 --> 00:02:25,684
{\a6}皮克斯动画出品电影经典开头

59
00:02:26,136 --> 00:02:27,936
我都听你的啦 西区泰迪
I'm all yours, Teddy Westside.

60
00:02:27,938 --> 00:02:30,522
其实呢 今晚我叫泰迪•西区切斯特吧
Actually, tonight it's Teddy Westchester.

61
00:02:30,524 --> 00:02:32,741
我得去我的房子那边 再修整一些东西
Got to head up to the house, take care of some stuff.

62
00:02:32,743 --> 00:02:35,110
噢 对哦 房子修的怎么样了
Oh, yeah, how's the restoration going?

63
00:02:35,112 --> 00:02:37,779
事实上 搞定了
Actually, done.

64
00:02:37,781 --> 00:02:38,831
已经完工了吗
You finished the house?

65
00:02:38,833 --> 00:02:40,616
我要去看看
Well, I want to see it.

66
00:02:40,618 --> 00:02:42,167
马修已经把网断了 是吗
Marshall already canceled the cable, huh?

67
00:02:42,169 --> 00:02:42,885
连无线也没有了
And the Wi-Fi.

68
00:02:42,887 --> 00:02:44,903
就像住在那该死的草原上的小木屋里一样
It's like Little House on the Freaking Prairie up there.

68
00:02:42,887 --> 00:02:44,903
{\a6}草原上的小木屋 美国经典童话名著

70
00:02:47,624 --> 00:02:50,175
好了 婚礼也计划完毕
Well, the wedding planning is done,

71
00:02:50,177 --> 00:02:55,848
今晚呢 完全是用来放松并庆祝我们的一切不凡
{\fs17}so tonight is all about relaxing and celebrating everything that makes us awesome,

72
00:02:53,848 --> 00:02:55,848

73
00:02:55,850 --> 00:02:56,748
所以我呢
which is why

74
00:02:56,750 --> 00:02:58,967
特意要了那张我们最喜欢的那个位子
I requested our favorite table.

75
00:02:58,969 --> 00:03:01,019
靠窗的那个
The one by the window.

76
00:03:01,021 --> 00:03:04,439
在那里 我们观赏了两个流浪汉的彻夜激斗
Where we were sitting the night we saw those two bums fighting.

77
00:03:04,441 --> 00:03:06,191
为了一个三明治
Over a sandwich.

78
00:03:08,779 --> 00:03:10,229
我们都快要叫警察了
We almost called the cops.

79
00:03:10,231 --> 00:03:12,648
然后我们突然意识到 是我们会错意了
And then we realized they weren't fighting at all.

80
00:03:12,650 --> 00:03:14,032
他们在进行爱之激斗
They were making love.

81
00:03:14,869 --> 00:03:16,535
在一个三明治上
Over a sandwich.

82
00:03:16,537 --> 00:03:18,871
噢 我差点忘了
Oh, I almost forgot.

83
00:03:20,374 --> 00:03:21,456
不会吧 这不是
Ha-ha, yeah. No way, is that...?

84
00:03:21,458 --> 00:03:23,659
金字塔
El Piramide.

84
00:03:21,458 --> 00:03:26,245
{\a6}{\fs16}S01E14中 蒙特二号 也叫鱼雷 BR一起抽的第一支雪茄

85
00:03:23,661 --> 00:03:26,245
我们一起抽的第一支雪茄
The first cigar we ever smoked together.

86
00:03:26,247 --> 00:03:27,913
噢 巴尼
Aw, Barney.

87
00:03:28,716 --> 00:03:30,382
不好意思
Excuse me.

88
00:03:30,384 --> 00:03:31,449
你们好
Hi.

89
00:03:31,451 --> 00:03:33,018
你们能不能 别... 谢谢
Could you not? Thanks.

91
00:03:34,138 --> 00:03:35,504
老兄 我又不会在这点上
dude, I'm not gonna light 'em up in here.

92
00:03:35,506 --> 00:03:37,289
我就是看看罢了
I'm just looking at 'em.

93
00:03:37,291 --> 00:03:39,258
是啊 但是即使没有点上
Right, but even when they're unlit,

94
00:03:39,260 --> 00:03:41,626
这味道也很...
the smell-- it's very...

95
00:03:41,628 --> 00:03:42,511
冲鼻子
Pungent.

96
00:03:42,513 --> 00:03:44,563
完全正确 谢谢
Exactly-- thank you.

97
00:03:44,565 --> 00:03:47,983
这气味非常冲鼻子
It's a very pungent smell.

98
00:03:47,985 --> 00:03:50,402
所以 你们能不能别...
So, could you not?

99
00:03:50,404 --> 00:03:51,603
再谢谢啊
Thanks.

100
00:03:52,789 --> 00:03:55,274
好
Okay.

101
00:03:57,861 --> 00:04:02,030
不好意思 能把袋子也拿开吗
I'm sorry, can you also put the bag away?

102
00:04:02,032 --> 00:04:07,085
这个看着实在倒胃口
It-It's just really unappetizing to look at.

103
00:04:07,087 --> 00:04:08,620
你个死光头才倒胃口嘞
You're unappetizing to look at.

104
00:04:08,622 --> 00:04:11,156
好了好了 我把雪茄拿开 好吧
You know what? Um, I'll put them away, okay?

105
00:04:11,158 --> 00:04:12,291
祝你们有个愉快的夜晚
Enjoy your night.

106
00:04:12,293 --> 00:04:14,710
我们尽量愉快吧
We'll try.

107
00:04:16,179 --> 00:04:17,996
这两只现在变成我们的死敌了
Did those two just become our archenemies?

108
00:04:17,998 --> 00:04:20,349
不 罗宾 他们一直是我们的死对头
No, Robin, they've always been our archenemies.

110
00:04:20,351 --> 00:04:23,769
只是刚刚暴露而已
They've only just revealed themselves.

111
00:04:23,771 --> 00:04:24,937
嗨 克里斯汀
Hi, Kristen?

112
00:04:24,939 --> 00:04:26,888
每个人都读错
Everyone pronounces it wrong.

113
00:04:26,890 --> 00:04:29,141
R在I后面
The "R" Is after the "I""

114
00:04:29,143 --> 00:04:30,058
克尔斯汀
Kirsten.

115
00:04:30,060 --> 00:04:31,643
I前面还有一个R呢
And before the "I""

116
00:04:31,645 --> 00:04:34,563
是克里耳屎汀
It's Krirsten.

117
00:04:34,565 --> 00:04:36,098
您的桌子好了
Your table's ready.

118
00:04:37,400 --> 00:04:40,619
哇 他们还真混里个蛋
Wow, they're "Trerrible""

119
00:04:40,621 --> 00:04:41,570
听我说
You know what?

120
00:04:41,572 --> 00:04:43,205
不要去想他们 好吗
Don't even think about them, okay?

121
00:04:43,207 --> 00:04:45,540
-今晚我们是来庆祝的  -你是对的
-Tonight is about celebrating us. -You're right, you're right.

122
00:04:45,542 --> 00:04:48,243
-我们不应该让另外一对  -不行 绝对不行
-We shouldn't let a couple... -Nope, nope.

123
00:04:48,245 --> 00:04:49,828
我是一名自封的幽闭恐惧症患者
I'm a self-diagnosed claustrophobic.

124
00:04:49,830 --> 00:04:52,047
我必须要坐在窗户边
I have to sit next to the window.

125
00:04:52,049 --> 00:04:53,799
不要 那是我们的桌子×3
No, that's our table, that's our table,that's our table, 

126
00:04:53,801 --> 00:04:57,169
那是我们的桌子×3
that's our table, that's our table, that's our table,

128
00:04:59,089 --> 00:05:00,472
你知道吗
You know what?

129
00:05:00,474 --> 00:05:02,391
去他妹的庆祝咱俩 知道咱们该怎么做吗
Screw celebrating us. You know what we're gonna do?

130
00:05:02,393 --> 00:05:05,543
让那俩得意又烦人的狗娘养的付出代价×2
Make those smug, obnoxious sons of bitches pay.

131
00:05:05,545 --> 00:05:06,878
啊呜
Aw...

132
00:05:08,816 --> 00:05:11,149
莉莉阿姨和我开车去了西区特切斯特
So Aunt Lily and I drove up to Westchester.

132
00:05:08,816 --> 00:05:11,149
{\a6}西区特切斯特 泰德房子所在地 详见S05E20

133
00:05:12,186 --> 00:05:14,552
嘿 宝贝
Hey, baby,

134
00:05:14,554 --> 00:05:15,437
明尼苏达那边情况怎么样
how's Minnesota?

135
00:05:15,439 --> 00:05:17,155
简直太有趣了
It is so much fun.

136
00:05:17,157 --> 00:05:18,440
等一会儿
Oh, hold on one sec.

137
00:05:18,442 --> 00:05:21,576
马修 我专门为你做了欢迎回家的冰淇淋圣代
Marshall, I made you this welcome-home ice cream sundae.

138
00:05:21,578 --> 00:05:23,456
但是我不记得 你喜欢碎果仁吗
But I can't remember, do you like crushed nuts?

138
00:05:23,456 --> 00:05:24,445
别 别
no, no

139
00:05:24,445 --> 00:05:26,448
我超爱碎果仁
I love crushed nuts.

139
00:05:24,445 --> 00:05:26,448
{\a6}crush有打碎的意思 nut又有蛋蛋的意思

141
00:05:26,450 --> 00:05:28,000
哦
Oh!

142
00:05:29,285 --> 00:05:32,437
总之 回到家真是太好了
Anyway, it's, it's great to be home.

143
00:05:32,439 --> 00:05:33,789
朱迪还好吧
How's Judy doing?

144
00:05:33,791 --> 00:05:34,873
她很好
Oh, she's great.

145
00:05:34,875 --> 00:05:36,041
很有意思 知道吗 她一直在开玩笑说
It's cute, you know, she keeps joking

146
00:05:36,043 --> 00:05:37,909
她多么不想让我们离开
about how she's not gonna let us leave.

147
00:05:37,911 --> 00:05:39,411
我真没有
I'm really not.

148
00:05:39,413 --> 00:05:40,912
这不是玩笑哦
It's not a joke.

149
00:05:46,136 --> 00:05:47,969
朱迪还跟他说要一起去罗马呢
Judy's going to talk him out of going to Rome.

150
00:05:47,971 --> 00:05:50,355
我就知道会有事情搅和我们的计划
I knew something was going to screw up our plans,

151
00:05:50,357 --> 00:05:51,690
就是这事
and this is it.

152
00:05:51,692 --> 00:05:54,059
她肯定会说服他永远不要离开这里的
She is going to convince him never to leave the country.

153
00:05:54,061 --> 00:05:55,944
我觉得你可能想多了
I think you're imagining things.

154
00:05:55,946 --> 00:05:58,197
哦 是吗 看看她发在脸书上的东西
Oh, yeah? Well, check out what's already on Facebook.

154
00:05:58,599 --> 00:05:59,597
大美利坚

155
00:05:59,599 --> 00:06:00,932
没有说服力
Inconclusive.

156
00:06:00,934 --> 00:06:01,868
真的吗
Oh, really?

156
00:06:01,870 --> 00:06:03,868
罗马弱爆

157
00:06:04,737 --> 00:06:05,987
现在有点说服力了
It's getting conclusiver.

158
00:06:05,989 --> 00:06:06,938
嘿 莉莉
Hey, Lily.

159
00:06:06,940 --> 00:06:09,241
-怎么  -跟我来
-What? -Come on.

160
00:06:09,243 --> 00:06:12,127
好了 张开吧
Okay, open'em.

161
00:06:12,129 --> 00:06:14,746
你的眼睛 对不起 你应该闭上眼睛的
Your eyes-- sorry, they should have been closed.

162
00:06:14,748 --> 00:06:15,747
这得怪我
That one's on me.

163
00:06:15,749 --> 00:06:16,748
我们再试一次
Let's try again.

164
00:06:16,750 --> 00:06:17,782
哇哦
Wow.

165
00:06:17,784 --> 00:06:21,136
泰德 这些都是你一个人做的吗
Ted, you did this all yourself?

166
00:06:21,138 --> 00:06:24,306
就像恋恋笔记本中的瑞恩•高斯林那样
Just like Ryan Gosling in The Notebook.

166
00:06:21,138 --> 00:06:24,306
{\a6}瑞恩•高斯林 加拿大演员

167
00:06:24,308 --> 00:06:26,258
我今天一直很男人 直到我提到
I was pretty manly till I mentioned

168
00:06:26,260 --> 00:06:28,393
恋恋笔记本中的瑞恩•高斯林 对吧
Ryan Gosling in The Notebook, huh?

169
00:06:28,395 --> 00:06:29,978
连我都没看过这部电影 泰德
Even I haven't seen it, Ted.

170
00:06:30,847 --> 00:06:32,564
想象一下吧 你的孩子们
Just think, this is the house

171
00:06:32,566 --> 00:06:34,182
会在这间房子里长大
your kids are going to grow up in.

172
00:06:34,184 --> 00:06:38,970
他们会在这个壁炉里烤棉花糖
They are going to roast marshmallows in this fireplace.

174
00:06:38,972 --> 00:06:40,023
他们会在前庭那边
They're gonna experiment

175
00:06:40,023 --> 00:06:42,190
尝尝快活小丸丸
with recreational drugs on that porch.

177
00:06:43,527 --> 00:06:44,776
他们会坐在放在这里的沙发上
They're gonna sit on a couch right here

178
00:06:44,778 --> 00:06:46,495
听你讲那些无聊的故事 关于
and listen to your boring stories about...

179
00:06:46,497 --> 00:06:49,698
"待售"牌
"For sale" Sign?

180
00:06:50,616 --> 00:06:52,284
你要把这间房子卖了吗
Are you selling this place?

181
00:06:52,286 --> 00:06:54,453
是啊
Yeah.

182
00:06:54,455 --> 00:06:55,954
为什么啊
Why?

183
00:06:56,789 --> 00:07:00,926
因为我要搬去芝加哥
Because I'm moving to Chicago.

184
00:07:06,887 --> 00:07:08,805
嗷
Ow.

185
00:07:09,054 --> 00:07:10,353
那 我们要怎么弄
So, what are we gonna do--

186
00:07:10,355 --> 00:07:11,555
在他们吃的东西里加点料
put something in their food,

187
00:07:11,557 --> 00:07:13,573
在他们车子上划几道 噢
key their car? Ooh,

188
00:07:13,575 --> 00:07:15,275
你的雪茄里面有会爆炸的那种吗
do either of those cigars explode?

189
00:07:15,277 --> 00:07:18,378
悠着点 大野狼 我想到一个好点子
Hold on, Wile E. Coyote, I think I got something.

189
00:07:15,277 --> 00:07:18,378
{\a6}来源于动画《哔哔鸟和大野狼》

190
00:07:19,080 --> 00:07:21,631
他在打量那个迎宾员
He's checking out the hostess.

191
00:07:21,633 --> 00:07:25,101
正处于欢快约会中的男人用这样的眼光偷瞄
Now, a guy who's happily in a relationship sees a girl

192
00:07:25,103 --> 00:07:29,823
别的女人的话 他偷瞄的次数将可达14-15次
like that, he'll check her out maybe 14, 15 times, tops.

193
00:07:30,741 --> 00:07:32,375
16次 封顶了
16 times, tops.

194
00:07:32,377 --> 00:07:36,246
这么说 克里耳屎汀在这段关系里比她奸夫
So Krirsten's more invested in the relationship

195
00:07:36,248 --> 00:07:38,381
要投入的多啊
than her fella is.

196
00:07:38,383 --> 00:07:40,166
这可以用来大做文章
That could spell trouble.

197
00:07:40,168 --> 00:07:42,135
接受挑战
Challenge accepted.

198
00:07:43,220 --> 00:07:45,288
嘿 你说一个新娘在她婚礼之前
Hey, do you think it's bad luck for a bride

199
00:07:45,290 --> 00:07:48,258
把一对陌生人给拆散了会不会有点败人品啊
to break up two strangers a week before her wedding?

200
00:07:48,260 --> 00:07:52,646
我说这相当败人品啊...败克里耳屎汀的人品
I'd say it's very bad luck... for Krirsten.

201
00:07:57,768 --> 00:08:00,637
噢 我恨死这桌子了
Ow, I hate this table so much!

202
00:08:00,639 --> 00:08:03,356
你为什么要搬去芝加哥啊
Why would you move to Chicago?

204
00:08:03,358 --> 00:08:05,158
因为那儿是我的完美之城
Because it's the perfect town for me.

205
00:08:05,160 --> 00:08:07,277
它像是克利夫兰化的纽约
I-It's like a Clevelandy New York,

206
00:08:07,279 --> 00:08:08,811
而且 不知道你有没有注意到
and-- don't act like you haven't noticed--

207
00:08:08,813 --> 00:08:11,114
我的头发风中凌乱时特别好看
my hair excels in the wind.

207
00:08:08,813 --> 00:08:11,114
{\a6}芝加哥外号风城 常年大风

208
00:08:11,116 --> 00:08:12,165
另外
Besides,

209
00:08:12,167 --> 00:08:13,416
你们也搬去罗马了
you're moving to Rome.

210
00:08:13,418 --> 00:08:16,002
但是只去一年啊 而且等我们回来时
Yeah, for a year, a-and when we get back,

211
00:08:16,004 --> 00:08:18,171
需要看到你在这儿等着我们啊
we need you to be here waiting for us,

212
00:08:18,173 --> 00:08:21,841
没准是和你未来的新娘生活在这间房子里
hopefully living in this house with your future bride.

213
00:08:21,843 --> 00:08:24,044
什么...什么未来的新娘
Wha... what future bride?

214
00:08:24,046 --> 00:08:25,095
那个女孩
The girl.

215
00:08:25,097 --> 00:08:26,112
她现在正在
She's out there

216
00:08:26,114 --> 00:08:28,131
外面的纽约城里四处溜达
walking around New York City right now,

217
00:08:28,133 --> 00:08:30,767
没准穿着一双特别可爱的靴子
probably in a pair of really cute boots

218
00:08:30,769 --> 00:08:32,669
我想穿的时候 她就会借给我
that she's gonna let me borrow whenever I want

219
00:08:32,671 --> 00:08:33,887
因为我们有一样的尺码
because we're the same size.

220
00:08:33,889 --> 00:08:35,555
她就在那外面 泰德
She is out there, Ted.

221
00:08:35,557 --> 00:08:38,274
她真的在吗 可是我都找遍了
Is she, really? Because I've looked.

222
00:08:38,276 --> 00:08:39,309
我苦苦寻觅
I have looked high

223
00:08:39,311 --> 00:08:41,561
希望能找到一个可以让我喜欢
and low for someone I can love

224
00:08:41,563 --> 00:08:43,980
让我爱慕 让我为她做华夫饼的人
and adore and cook waffles for.

225
00:08:43,982 --> 00:08:45,532
可是现在最接近的人就只有马修啊
The closest I've come is Marshall.

226
00:08:45,534 --> 00:08:46,683
他确实挺喜欢你做的华夫饼的
He does love your waffles.

227
00:08:46,685 --> 00:08:47,850
是肉桂的缘故啦
It's the cinnamon.

228
00:08:47,852 --> 00:08:49,369
我都会加肉桂的
I add cinnamon.

229
00:08:50,204 --> 00:08:52,322
她根本没在纽约
She's not in New York.

230
00:08:52,324 --> 00:08:53,856
或许她会在芝加哥
Maybe she's in Chicago.

231
00:08:53,858 --> 00:08:56,660
好 你现在是越说越离谱了
Okay, you are being ridiculous.

232
00:08:56,662 --> 00:08:59,162
你会在这儿 在纽约城里 找到那个人
You are going to find someone here in New York

233
00:08:59,164 --> 00:09:01,247
而且你会爱她 就像我爱马修一样
that you love just as much as I love Marshall.

234
00:09:01,249 --> 00:09:02,632
至于你
And you,

235
00:09:02,634 --> 00:09:06,703
如果你让朱迪说服你不去意大利的话 我发誓
if you let Judy talk you out of going to Italy, so help me,

236
00:09:06,705 --> 00:09:10,507
我的意大利饺子将永远对你的馅料关上大门
I will never let you stuff my ravioli again.

237
00:09:10,509 --> 00:09:12,258
我还是把扬声器关了吧
I'm gonna take you off speaker.

238
00:09:12,260 --> 00:09:13,543
莉莉 你就放一百万个心吧
Lily, you got to relax.

239
00:09:13,545 --> 00:09:16,596
我妈对意大利这事可激动了
Okay, my mom is psyched about Italy.

240
00:09:16,598 --> 00:09:18,064
她一直在开玩笑说
She keeps making jokes about how she's gonna

241
00:09:18,066 --> 00:09:21,768
她要跟我们一起去罗马睡沙发
come live with us in Rome and sleep on the couch

242
00:09:21,770 --> 00:09:23,069
给我们做饭
and cook every meal for us

243
00:09:23,071 --> 00:09:25,071
我们在那的一整年
so we never have to go to a restaurant

244
00:09:25,073 --> 00:09:26,222
都不用下馆子
the whole year we're there.

245
00:09:26,224 --> 00:09:27,273
这不是玩笑哦
It's not a joke.

246
00:09:27,275 --> 00:09:28,841
现在不准对我说不
By not saying no to me right now,

247
00:09:28,843 --> 00:09:32,529
你得保证让我跟你们去罗马才行
you are giving me your full consent for that to happen.

249
00:09:37,402 --> 00:09:38,735
我得挂了
I got to go.

250
00:09:38,737 --> 00:09:40,903
我要说些政治上的东西
"I'm probably saying some political stuff

251
00:09:40,905 --> 00:09:42,172
以显得我很聪明
right now to sound smart."

252
00:09:42,174 --> 00:09:44,708
我更喜欢傲慢自大的播客
"I'm probably referring to some snooty podcast

253
00:09:44,710 --> 00:09:46,593
以显得我更聪明
to sound even smarter."

254
00:09:46,595 --> 00:09:48,128
我要讲法语了
"I'm probably saying something in French."

255
00:09:48,130 --> 00:09:49,345
啊
Aah!

256
00:09:49,347 --> 00:09:50,346
我的天...
My God...

257
00:09:50,348 --> 00:09:52,265
噢
Ow.

258
00:09:52,267 --> 00:09:53,266
好了
Okay,

259
00:09:53,268 --> 00:09:54,284
你想要拆散他们吗
you want to break them up?

260
00:09:54,286 --> 00:09:55,468
我有一个计划
I got a plan.

261
00:09:55,470 --> 00:09:57,637
这计划以前成功过
It's something I know has worked in the past,

262
00:09:57,639 --> 00:09:59,055
但是 有风险
but it-it's, it's risky,

263
00:09:59,057 --> 00:10:01,558
所以 现在取消还来得及
so it's, it's not too late to call it off.

264
00:10:01,560 --> 00:10:02,290
不 我也参与
No way, I'm in.

265
00:10:02,315 --> 00:10:04,145
很好 其实现在想取消已经来不及了
Good, 'cause it's too late to call it off.

266
00:10:04,146 --> 00:10:05,979
好戏开始
Observe.

267
00:10:05,981 --> 00:10:07,197
这就是为什么参议院
And that is why the senate

268
00:10:07,199 --> 00:10:08,698
不能通过任何议案
can't push anything through.

269
00:10:08,700 --> 00:10:10,018
道格•曼德在他的播客里也是这么说的
And Doug Mand said the same thing in his podcast.

270
00:10:10,019 --> 00:10:12,725
就像是"身后之事与我何干"
It's like, "Apres moi le deluge!"

271
00:10:16,707 --> 00:10:18,775
噢
Ooh.

272
00:10:18,777 --> 00:10:19,793
噢 天啊
Oh, my gosh.

273
00:10:19,795 --> 00:10:21,327
噢 我的天 噢 我的神
Oh, my gosh, oh, my gosh.

274
00:10:21,329 --> 00:10:23,580
好 好 好
Yes, yes, yes.

275
00:10:23,582 --> 00:10:24,714
我愿意
Yes!

276
00:10:24,716 --> 00:10:25,465
什么
What?

277
00:10:25,467 --> 00:10:26,783
我愿意
Yes!

278
00:10:26,785 --> 00:10:27,950
我愿意嫁给你
I will marry you!

279
00:10:27,952 --> 00:10:29,502
就算是香槟杯子里的戒指
Even though a ring in a champagne glass

280
00:10:29,504 --> 00:10:31,254
这样的老套的方法 就算这是个长角阶梯型戒指
is a total cliche and this is a cushion cut.

281
00:10:31,256 --> 00:10:33,289
就算我暗示过你 我想要公主方形的戒指
And how long have I been hinting that I want a princess cut?

282
00:10:33,291 --> 00:10:34,424
我也愿意
But yes!

283
00:10:34,426 --> 00:10:35,975
这是个误会 这戒指不是我的
That's a mistake. That's not from me.

284
00:10:35,977 --> 00:10:37,960
不是你的
It's not?

285
00:10:37,962 --> 00:10:41,231
我们在一起才七年而已
We've only been together seven years.

286
00:10:41,233 --> 00:10:44,150
-现在清楚了 -开始了
-Now it becomes clear. -Here we go.

287
00:10:44,152 --> 00:10:44,981
你想像当时承诺
You want commitment the

288
00:10:44,982 --> 00:10:46,603
给我弟弟工作那样敷衍我
same way you want my brother to work for you.

289
00:10:46,605 --> 00:10:49,356
很抱歉我没有在酒杯里面放戒指
I'm sorry I didn't put an engagement ring in your drink.

290
00:10:49,357 --> 00:10:52,642
从你以往大口喝酒的经验来看 我很惊讶你居然发现了戒指
The way you chug booze, I'm surprised you even noticed.

291
00:10:52,644 --> 00:10:54,811
那么 你什么时候走
So, when are you leaving?

292
00:10:54,813 --> 00:10:56,279
婚礼后的第一天
Day after the wedding.

293
00:10:56,281 --> 00:10:57,447
什么
What?

294
00:10:57,449 --> 00:10:59,616
你不能错过婚礼后的第一天
You can't miss the day after the wedding.

295
00:10:59,618 --> 00:11:02,836
那一天我们要不醉不归 喝含羞草鸡尾酒
That's when we sit around all hungover, drinking mimosas

296
00:11:02,838 --> 00:11:05,038
然后八卦一下谁长胖了
and talking smack about who looked fat.

297
00:11:05,040 --> 00:11:07,006
那相当于我的圣诞节
That's my Christmas.

298
00:11:07,008 --> 00:11:10,176
你为什么这么着急要走呢
Why are you in such a rush to get out of there?

299
00:11:11,579 --> 00:11:14,013
噢
Oh.

300
00:11:14,015 --> 00:11:16,499
当然了
Of course.

301
00:11:16,501 --> 00:11:18,601
你离开这里的原因并不是因为
You're not leaving because you think

302
00:11:18,603 --> 00:11:20,770
你认为你的真命天女不在纽约
the love of your life isn't in New York.

303
00:11:20,772 --> 00:11:22,939
你离开这里是因为 你觉得你的她就在那里
You're leaving because you think she is.

304
00:11:22,941 --> 00:11:24,324
然而下周的这个时候
And this time next week,

305
00:11:24,326 --> 00:11:27,360
她就嫁给你最好的朋友了
she'll be married to your best friend.

306
00:11:29,147 --> 00:11:30,814
亲爱的
Baby!

307
00:11:30,816 --> 00:11:32,014
我这里正在上演
I am in the middle

308
00:11:32,016 --> 00:11:33,366
非常戏剧化的一幕
of something super dramatic here.

309
00:11:33,368 --> 00:11:36,202
但是 你记住了 如果你让朱迪和我们一起去罗马
But real quick: If you let Judy come to Rome with us,

310
00:11:36,204 --> 00:11:38,071
你就得另找人
you are going to have to find someone else

311
00:11:38,073 --> 00:11:40,156
帮你洗衣服 做脚底按摩了
to do your laundry and massage your feet.

312
00:11:40,158 --> 00:11:43,293
哦 天 她都做得到是吧
Oh, my gosh, she's going to do all that, won't she?

313
00:11:43,295 --> 00:11:45,211
莉莉 你不用再这么抓狂了
Lily, you have to stop freaking out.

314
00:11:45,213 --> 00:11:47,630
没有任何事情会打破我们的计划
Nothing is going to screw up the plan.

315
00:11:47,632 --> 00:11:49,115
我们一定会按计划执行
We're doing this.

316
00:11:49,117 --> 00:11:50,550
我爱你
I love you.

317
00:11:50,552 --> 00:11:52,502
我爱你 亲爱的 拜拜
I love you, baby. Bye.

318
00:11:55,757 --> 00:11:57,140
你好
Hello?

319
00:11:57,142 --> 00:11:58,508
请问是马修•艾瑞克森吗
Hi. Marshall Eriksen?

320
00:11:58,510 --> 00:12:01,594
这里是纽约州司法委员会
I'm calling from the New York State Judiciary Committee.

321
00:12:01,596 --> 00:12:04,013
你还记得 几个月前你申请了法官资格吗
Uh, you applied for a judgeship a few months ago, remember?

322
00:12:04,015 --> 00:12:05,682
哦 当...当然
Uh, of... of course.

323
00:12:05,684 --> 00:12:06,933
是这样的 我有个好消息
Well, I have good news.

324
00:12:06,935 --> 00:12:09,102
我们现在有个紧急的席位空缺
We have a last-minute opening on the bench.

325
00:12:09,104 --> 00:12:11,154
你说什么
What are you saying to me right now?

326
00:12:11,156 --> 00:12:12,739
我在说 恭喜你
I'm saying congratulations.

327
00:12:12,741 --> 00:12:14,908
我们希望你来做法官
We want you to be a judge.

328
00:12:20,738 --> 00:12:22,495
-所以你想让我做个法官  -是的
-So, you want me to be a judge? -Yes.

329
00:12:22,496 --> 00:12:24,628
-然后我还要从下一周的周二开始工作  -是的
-And I would start a week from Tuesday? -Yes.

330
00:12:24,676 --> 00:12:26,464
我可不可以从下一年度的周二开始工作
Could I maybe start a year from Tuesday?

331
00:12:26,489 --> 00:12:27,128
不行
No.

332
00:12:27,129 --> 00:12:28,828
-一定要从下周二开始  -是的
-Got to be a week from Tuesday? -Yes.

333
00:12:28,830 --> 00:12:30,330
-然后我会成为一名真正的法官  -是的
-And I'd be a real judge? -Yes.

334
00:12:30,332 --> 00:12:31,364
-穿长袍的那种  -是的
-With a robe? -Yes.

335
00:12:31,366 --> 00:12:32,332
-有小锤的那种  -是的
-Gavel? -Yes.

336
00:12:32,334 --> 00:12:34,134
-有奇怪的南方口音那种  -不是
-Wacky Southern accent? -No.

337
00:12:34,136 --> 00:12:35,402
好吧 律师先生
Now, counselor,

338
00:12:35,404 --> 00:12:36,553
你完全确定你在说什么吗
are you absolutely sure?

339
00:12:36,555 --> 00:12:37,055
是的
Yes.

340
00:12:37,064 --> 00:12:38,372
还有我还必须在纽约做这种事情
And I have to be in New York for this?

341
00:12:38,373 --> 00:12:39,856
-是的  -我可以远程通话吗
-Yes. -I can't telecommute?

342
00:12:39,858 --> 00:12:40,364
不行
No.

343
00:12:40,389 --> 00:12:42,142
我可以做那种疯狂的扬声器法官吗
I couldn't be the crazy speakerphone judge?

344
00:12:42,143 --> 00:12:43,976
-不行  -我可以用全息图像办案吗
-No. -Could I be a hologram?

345
00:12:43,978 --> 00:12:45,578
-不行  -仿生机器人呢
-No. -Animatronic robot

346
00:12:45,580 --> 00:12:49,515
{\a6}{\fs16}迪士尼乐园游乐项目之一 有会演讲的林肯总统机器人

346
00:12:45,580 --> 00:12:47,664
像总统大厅里面机器人亚伯拉罕•林肯那种
like Abe Lincoln from the Hall of Presidents

347
00:12:47,666 --> 00:12:49,515
我可以用操纵杆遥控那种
that I control from afar with a joystick?

348
00:12:49,540 --> 00:12:50,451
不行
No.

349
00:12:50,452 --> 00:12:52,786
你记不记得超人漫画里面的乔•艾尔的头
Do you remember the giant Jor-El head from Superman?

349
00:12:50,452 --> 00:12:52,786
{\a6}详见S8E19里Barney的投影仪

350
00:12:52,788 --> 00:12:54,087
-记得  -那 我可不可以...
-Yes. -Well, what if I...?

351
00:12:54,089 --> 00:12:55,672
-不行  -那有没有任何办法
-No. -Is there any way

352
00:12:55,674 --> 00:12:57,340
能让我在做这项工作的同时
that I could do this

353
00:12:57,342 --> 00:13:01,343
又能和我妻子搬去意大利住一年呢
and also spend the next year of my life in Italy with my wife?

354
00:13:01,345 --> 00:13:02,228
没有
No.

355
00:13:02,230 --> 00:13:04,297
这真是个重大决定啊
This is such a big decision.

356
00:13:04,299 --> 00:13:06,516
我真的不擅长做重大决定
I-I'm not good at big decisions.

357
00:13:06,518 --> 00:13:09,302
你确定你真要当法官吗
Are you sure you want to be a judge?

358
00:13:10,671 --> 00:13:14,023
哇噢 我们刚刚打碎了一段长达7年的恋情
Wow. Now that we've broken up a seven-year relationship

359
00:13:14,025 --> 00:13:15,725
只是因为他们占了我们的桌子
just 'cause they stole our table,

360
00:13:15,727 --> 00:13:17,610
-我觉得有点...  -棒极了
-I feel kind of... -Awesome?

361
00:13:17,612 --> 00:13:20,196
我打算说"欲火中烧" 但没错 也很棒
I was going to say horny, but yeah, awesome, too.

362
00:13:22,234 --> 00:13:23,450
不是吧
No way.

363
00:13:23,452 --> 00:13:24,868
-开玩笑吧  -什么
-Are you kidding me? -What?

364
00:13:24,870 --> 00:13:26,069
哇 这是要来打架吗
Whoa. Is there going to be a fight?

365
00:13:26,071 --> 00:13:27,320
好吧 那就这样
Okay, here's the play.

366
00:13:27,322 --> 00:13:29,289
你负责放倒那个妞 还有那个男的 我旁观
You take the girl, and the guy and I will watch.

367
00:13:29,291 --> 00:13:31,858
你们好呀 我们正想找你们呢
Hello. Just the people we want to see.

368
00:13:31,860 --> 00:13:35,528
因为你们 我俩大吵了一架
We got in a pretty big fight because of you guys.

369
00:13:35,530 --> 00:13:37,297
还约心理医生谈了好几个小时
We had to call our therapists after hours.

370
00:13:37,299 --> 00:13:39,299
可不爽了呢
Not cool.

371
00:13:39,301 --> 00:13:41,134
总而言之 这事导致了我们现在的结果
Anyway, it got us to where we are now.

372
00:13:41,136 --> 00:13:42,585
我们要结婚了
We're getting married!

373
00:13:43,471 --> 00:13:44,671
而且我会跟她姓
And I'm taking her last name.

374
00:13:44,673 --> 00:13:46,256
你们也应该考虑这样做
You should think about doing the same thing.

375
00:13:46,258 --> 00:13:47,974
-那晚安咯  -晚安
-Well, good night. -Good night.

376
00:13:47,976 --> 00:13:49,676
-晚安  -恭喜你们
-Good night. -Congratulations.

377
00:13:49,678 --> 00:13:52,011
是啊 必须恭喜
Yes, definitely.

378
00:13:52,013 --> 00:13:54,230
是因为我们
That was us.

379
00:13:54,232 --> 00:13:57,100
我们促成了这桩喜事
We made that happen.

380
00:13:57,102 --> 00:13:59,018
我们太帅了
We're pretty cool.

381
00:13:59,020 --> 00:14:01,354
你知道 再过一周
And, you know, a week from today,

382
00:14:01,356 --> 00:14:04,691
我们就会变成一对传奇... 等一下...
we are going to be legend... wait for it...

383
00:14:04,693 --> 00:14:05,742
夫妻
Married.

384
00:14:05,744 --> 00:14:07,677
传奇夫妻×2
-Legend-married. -Legend-married.

385
00:14:09,865 --> 00:14:13,116
罗宾•舍巴斯基 我太特么爱你了
Robin Scherbatsky, I love you so damn much.

386
00:14:13,118 --> 00:14:15,702
我也爱你 巴尼•舍巴斯基
I love you, too, Barney Scherbatsky.

387
00:14:15,704 --> 00:14:17,370
听上去不错
That sounds good.

388
00:14:17,372 --> 00:14:18,922
-嘘  -考虑一下吧
-Shh. -Think about it.

389
00:14:18,924 --> 00:14:20,423
他们很幸福
They're happy.

390
00:14:20,425 --> 00:14:22,342
我也很为他们高兴
And I'm happy for them.

391
00:14:22,344 --> 00:14:24,794
我希望他们共度精彩的人生 只是
I want them to have an amazing life together. I just...

392
00:14:24,796 --> 00:14:26,846
我只是觉得 我不参与其中
I just think it would be best for everyone

393 
00:14:26,848 --> 00:14:28,131
会对所有人都好
if I wasn't around for it.

394
00:14:28,133 --> 00:14:32,051
最近你跟罗宾之间发生什么事了吗
Did something happen recently between you and Robin?

395
00:14:32,053 --> 00:14:33,636
没有
No.

396
00:14:33,638 --> 00:14:35,338
便便埋哪儿了 泰德
Where's the poop, Ted?

396
00:14:33,638 --> 00:14:35,338
{\a6}{\fs16}S06E03出现过 罗宾和唐分手后莉莉追问罗宾的台词

397
00:14:37,257 --> 00:14:39,442
那天她给我打电话
She called me up the other day.

398
00:14:39,444 --> 00:14:41,260
想要挖出那个埋在中央公园
She was trying to dig up this locket

399
00:14:41,262 --> 00:14:43,196
旋转木马后面的吊坠小盒
she had buried behind the Central Park Carousel,

400
00:14:43,198 --> 00:14:46,265
我推掉了一场很重要的面试去帮她
and I blew off that big interview to go help her.

401
00:14:46,267 --> 00:14:50,286
后来 下起了雨
And then... it started raining.

402
00:14:53,574 --> 00:14:55,408
我 呃
I'll, uh...

403
00:14:55,410 --> 00:14:56,626
婚礼上见
I'll see you at the wedding.

404
00:14:56,628 --> 00:14:58,277
嗯
Yeah.

405
00:14:58,279 --> 00:15:00,296
即使是现在 已经过了这么多年
Even now, after all these years,

406
00:15:00,298 --> 00:15:02,632
我心中仍然有一个角落驱使着我
there's still just this part of me where,

407
00:15:02,634 --> 00:15:04,250
就算只有最渺茫的机会
if there's even the slightest chance

408
00:15:04,252 --> 00:15:06,118
能让我使罗宾展开笑颜
something I do could make Robin smile,

409
00:15:06,120 --> 00:15:09,222
我都绝不多想 义无反顾
I don't even think about it-- I just do it.

410
00:15:09,224 --> 00:15:10,473
我是说 如果我能让吊坠小盒
I mean, if I could make

411
00:15:10,475 --> 00:15:12,392
奇迹般出现 我肯定去做
that locket magically appear, I would.

412
00:15:12,394 --> 00:15:14,460
哪怕要切开我手臂上的脉络
I would open a vein in my arm

413
00:15:14,462 --> 00:15:16,646
让吊坠从我的血液中流淌出来
if I could bleed that locket out,

414
00:15:16,648 --> 00:15:18,815
只要能让她开心
just to make her happy.

415
00:15:19,900 --> 00:15:23,102
而对方却是你最好朋友的未婚妻
That's just a really sucky way to feel

416
00:15:23,104 --> 00:15:25,471
这真的再难堪不过了
about your best friend's fiancee.

417
00:15:27,140 --> 00:15:30,410
所以 我会去参加婚礼
So I'm going to come to the wedding,

418
00:15:30,412 --> 00:15:33,363
你知道 愉快地度过 但那之后...
you know, I'll have a good time, but after that, I...

419
00:15:34,265 --> 00:15:35,565
怎么了
What?

420
00:15:36,617 --> 00:15:39,836
我知道那个吊坠小盒在哪
I know where the locket is.

421
00:15:39,838 --> 00:15:41,421
什么
What?

422
00:15:41,423 --> 00:15:43,539
我知道那个吊坠小盒在哪
I know where the locket is.

423
00:15:43,541 --> 00:15:45,458
那是几年之前
It-it was a few years ago,

424
00:15:45,460 --> 00:15:47,126
就在你要和斯黛拉结婚之前
right before you were supposed to marry Stella.

424
00:15:45,460 --> 00:15:47,800
{\a6}2008年

425
00:15:47,128 --> 00:15:48,805
有天晚上我去酒吧喝点东西
I went down to the bar one night to get a drink

426
00:15:48,827 --> 00:15:50,713
然后碰见了谁呢
and what should I see?

427
00:15:50,715 --> 00:15:51,848
莉莉
Lily!

428
00:15:51,850 --> 00:15:53,683
嘿 小妞
Hey, girl.

429
00:15:53,685 --> 00:15:55,568
问你个问题啊
I got a question for you.

430
00:15:56,887 --> 00:15:59,171
泰德要娶的为什么不是我
Why isn't Ted marrying me?

431
00:15:59,173 --> 00:16:00,440
噢
Whoa

432
00:16:00,442 --> 00:16:02,442
对不起 哦 天哪
I'm sorry. Oh, God.

433
00:16:02,444 --> 00:16:03,943
对不起
I'm sorry.

434
00:16:03,945 --> 00:16:07,313
我只是... 我应该为他感到开心的
I just... I-I should be happy for him,

435
00:16:07,315 --> 00:16:09,348
可我却是这个样子
and yet here I am,

436
00:16:09,350 --> 00:16:13,069
打算搬去日本住 仅仅是为了躲开他
moving off to Japan just to get away from him.

437
00:16:13,071 --> 00:16:15,154
还有大概想去看看
And-and I guess to see those...

438
00:16:15,156 --> 00:16:18,041
兵马俑和长城什么的
those terra-cotta warriors and the Great Wall.

439
00:16:18,043 --> 00:16:19,626
那是中国
Well, that's China.

440
00:16:19,628 --> 00:16:20,860
哪个 这个吗
What? This?

441
00:16:20,862 --> 00:16:22,295
不 这只是个纸盘子
No, it's just a paper plate.

442
00:16:19,628 --> 00:16:22,305
{\a6}china还有陶瓷的意思 罗宾以为莉莉说盘子是陶瓷的

442
00:16:24,249 --> 00:16:25,715
呃 咱还是离开这儿吧
Uh, we should get out of here.

443
00:16:25,717 --> 00:16:26,966
-快点 走啦  -哦 没错
-Come on. Come on. -Oh, totally.

444
00:16:26,968 --> 00:16:29,636
我知道我们应该去哪
I know just where we should go.

445
00:16:32,222 --> 00:16:34,090
天啊 你喝醉后行动还真是迅速
Man, you're fast when you're drunk.

446
00:16:34,092 --> 00:16:37,093
不过至少你做的决定还是正确的
But at least you're still making good decisions.

447
00:16:37,095 --> 00:16:38,811
中央公园 大半夜的
Central Park, around midnight,

448
00:16:38,813 --> 00:16:40,763
用勺子挖洞
digging a hole with a spoon.

449
00:16:40,765 --> 00:16:41,931
太靠谱了
Solid.

450
00:16:41,933 --> 00:16:44,150
有啦
Jackpot.

451
00:16:44,152 --> 00:16:45,184
那是个什么
What is that?

452
00:16:45,186 --> 00:16:47,937
我的"旧物"
My something old.

452
00:16:45,186 --> 00:16:47,937
{\a6}西方习俗中婚礼必备品

453
00:16:51,025 --> 00:16:53,776
这个吊坠小盒是我祖母的
This locket was my grandma's.

454
00:16:53,778 --> 00:16:57,730
二战期间她一直把这个藏在自己屁股里
She kept it hidden in her butt all through World War II.

455
00:16:57,732 --> 00:16:58,931
什么 她当时在哪
What? Where was she?

456
00:16:58,933 --> 00:17:01,584
温尼泊
Winnipeg.

456
00:16:58,933 --> 00:17:01,584
{\a6}加拿大城市名

457
00:17:02,787 --> 00:17:03,920
哦 拜托
Oh, come on.

458
00:17:03,922 --> 00:17:06,205
莉莉 我开玩笑的啦
Lily, it's a joke.

459
00:17:06,207 --> 00:17:09,342
我本来打算嫁给泰德的时候戴着它的
Yeah, I was going to wear this when I married Ted.

461
00:17:09,344 --> 00:17:10,877
现在看来是没戏了
I guess that's not going to happen.

462
00:17:10,879 --> 00:17:14,263
所以我要把它带去日本
So I am taking it with me to Japan.

463
00:17:14,265 --> 00:17:17,850
好了莉莉 帮忙把这个吊坠小盒放到我屁股里
Okay, Lily, help me put this locket in my butt.

464
00:17:17,852 --> 00:17:19,635
好了 你知道吗
Okay. Uh, you know what?

465
00:17:19,637 --> 00:17:23,923
不如我们把它放在这个铅笔盒里
Why don't we put it in this pencil box instead?

466
00:17:23,925 --> 00:17:27,860
哦 那我就把这个铅笔盒带去日本
Oh, and then I will take the pencil box with me to Japan.

467
00:17:27,862 --> 00:17:30,646
好啦 莉莉
Okay. Hey, Lily?

468
00:17:30,648 --> 00:17:33,866
帮忙把这个铅笔盒放到我屁股里
Help me put this pencil box in my butt.

469
00:17:36,570 --> 00:17:38,154
等下
Wait!

470
00:17:38,156 --> 00:17:40,656
我还有另一件事情要做
There's one other thing I have to do.

471
00:17:40,658 --> 00:17:42,492
莉莉 这个很重要
Lily, it's very important.

472
00:17:42,494 --> 00:17:44,961
这事情必须要做成
It's something that needs to happen

473
00:17:44,963 --> 00:17:47,296
-刻不容缓  -啥事
-right now. -Yeah?

474
00:17:47,298 --> 00:17:48,831
然后她吐了我一脸
Then she barfed in my face.

475
00:17:48,833 --> 00:17:50,133
真是美好的一晚上
It was a lovely night.

476
00:17:50,135 --> 00:17:53,886
等下 你把吊坠小盒放在赛车铅笔盒里了吗
Wait. You put the locket in the race car pencil box?

477
00:17:53,888 --> 00:17:56,889
对 然后罗宾把它带到日本去了
Yep. And then Robin took it to Japan.

478
00:17:56,891 --> 00:17:59,225
不 她没带
No, she didn't.

479
00:17:59,227 --> 00:18:04,296
它现在就放在我家的写字台上
It's sitting on my desk at home right now.

480
00:18:04,298 --> 00:18:06,482
它一直都在我那
It's been with me all along.

481
00:18:06,484 --> 00:18:09,352
-泰德  -吊坠小盒居然在铅笔盒里
-Ted. -The locket is in the pencil box.

482
00:18:09,354 --> 00:18:11,137
这太棒了
This is awesome.

483
00:18:11,139 --> 00:18:12,438
泰德
Ted.

484
00:18:12,440 --> 00:18:13,940
不 我是说
No, I just... I just mean,

485
00:18:13,942 --> 00:18:16,492
这将是有史以来最棒的结婚礼物了
this is going to be the best wedding gift ever.

486
00:18:16,494 --> 00:18:18,828
绝对会让她惊喜万分
It's going to blow her mind.

487
00:18:18,830 --> 00:18:20,029
泰德
Ted.

488
00:18:20,914 --> 00:18:23,616
小心点
Be careful.

489
00:18:24,701 --> 00:18:28,786
{\a10}周五
上午10点

489
00:18:26,701 --> 00:18:28,786
{\a10} \N婚礼前56小时

489
00:18:24,701 --> 00:18:29,986
{\a6}Simple Song by The Shins

490
00:18:33,177 --> 00:18:36,829
{\a6}Well this is just a simple song
这首歌平淡无常

491
00:18:36,831 --> 00:18:41,100
{\a6}To say what you've done
讲述你曾经的过往

492
00:18:41,102 --> 00:18:45,271
{\a6}I told you about all those fears
我曾将恐惧对你讲

493
00:18:45,273 --> 00:18:47,690
{\a6}And away they did run
它们果然就此消亡

494
00:18:47,692 --> 00:18:51,644
{\a6}You sure must be strong
你是那么的坚强

495
00:18:53,180 --> 00:18:57,700
{\a6}When you feel like an ocean being warmed by the sun
当你化身大海 沐浴温暖日光

497
00:18:57,702 --> 00:18:58,951
快点 我们该走了
Come on, we got to go.

498
00:18:58,953 --> 00:19:00,319
等等 我是不是忘了什么
Wait. What am I forgetting?

499
00:19:00,321 --> 00:19:03,072
什么也没有 你什么都没忘 咱们走吧 
Nothing. You're not forgetting anything. Let's go.

7
00:19:01,549 --> 00:19:05,540
{\a6}When I was just nine-years-old
当我正值九岁懵懂

500
00:19:03,074 --> 00:19:04,323
哦 等等 我忘了点事儿
Oh, wait, I'm forgetting something.

501
00:19:04,325 --> 00:19:05,708
什么
What?

502
00:19:05,710 --> 00:19:08,694
{\a6}I swear that I dreamt
我做过一个梦

503
00:19:08,696 --> 00:19:10,196
-咱们去结婚吧  -好
-Let's go get married. -Yeah.

504
00:19:09,529 --> 00:19:13,483
{\a6}Your face on a football field
你面朝绿茵球场

504
00:19:13,499 --> 00:19:15,840
{\a6}And a kiss that I kept
当时本该给你的一个吻

11
00:19:15,849 --> 00:19:20,190
{\a6}Under my vest
却藏在衣衫下方

12
00:19:20,199 --> 00:19:27,720
{\a6}Apart from everything, but the heart in my chest
不偏不倚 我的心房之上


505
00:19:14,385 --> 00:19:15,751
给马尔文准备起飞时咬的瓶子
Bottle for Marvin during takeoff.

506
00:19:15,753 --> 00:19:16,719
知道了 宝贝
Got it, baby.

507
00:19:16,721 --> 00:19:18,037
嘿 想想看
And hey, just think,

508
00:19:18,039 --> 00:19:19,872
从现在开始一周以后
one week from right now...

509
00:19:19,874 --> 00:19:20,923
我们就在意大利了
We'll be in Italy.

510
00:19:20,925 --> 00:19:22,675
我们就在意大利了
We'll be in Italy.

511
00:19:22,677 --> 00:19:24,644
好了 呃 我得挂了 亲爱的
Okay, um, I-I got to go, baby.

512
00:19:24,646 --> 00:19:27,146
我爱你
Um, I love you.

513
00:19:27,148 --> 00:19:29,182
你还没告诉她呢
You still haven't told her.

514
00:19:29,184 --> 00:19:30,883
没有
No.

515
00:19:30,885 --> 00:19:33,102
这是个当面说的消息
This is face-to-face news.

516
00:19:33,104 --> 00:19:34,971
祝你好运
Good luck with that...

517
00:19:34,973 --> 00:19:36,772
法官大人
Your Honor.

518
00:19:36,774 --> 00:19:41,527
{\a6}Don't go thinking you gotta be tough
不要觉得你必须做到坚强

519
00:19:41,529 --> 00:19:43,029
{\a6}and play like a stone
像顽石那样抵抗

520
00:19:43,031 --> 00:19:44,730
哈啰
Hello.

521
00:19:45,732 --> 00:19:49,251
{\a6}Could be there's nothing else in our lives
也许生命中不会有第二个地方

521
00:19:49,252 --> 00:19:52,251
{\a6}as this little home
像这个小家一样

522
00:19:48,253 --> 00:19:50,036
-你需要我帮你提[抓]一下包[蛋]吗  -是的 谢谢
-You want me to grab your bag? -Yeah. Thanks.

523
00:19:53,573 --> 00:19:56,959
嘿 我不想在婚礼分散大家的注意力 所以
Hey, I don't want to draw focus from the wedding, so...

524
00:19:56,961 --> 00:19:59,011
芝加哥的事不要告诉任何人
don't tell anyone about Chicago.

525
00:19:59,013 --> 00:20:01,747
那是个大城市 有一堆体育队伍
It's a major city with a bunch of sports teams

526
00:20:01,749 --> 00:20:03,099
还有好吃的匹萨
and some pretty good pizza.

527
00:20:03,101 --> 00:20:04,967
我觉得人们都知道芝加哥
I think people know about Chicago.

528
00:20:06,720 --> 00:20:08,721
你周一几点走
What time do you leave on Monday?

529
00:20:08,723 --> 00:20:10,022
一大早
Early.

530
00:20:10,024 --> 00:20:12,558
周日晚上就得回城
Gonna have to head back to the city Sunday night.

531
00:20:12,560 --> 00:20:14,060
那你要怎么回来
How are you going to get back?

532
00:20:14,895 --> 00:20:17,113
大概坐火车吧
Guess I'll take the train.

16
00:19:53,529 --> 00:19:57,560
{\a6}Well is just a simple song
这首歌平淡无常

17
00:19:58,179 --> 00:20:01,490
{\a6}To say what you've done
讲述你曾经的过往

18
00:20:01,499 --> 00:20:05,490
{\a6}I told you about all those fears
我曾将恐惧对你讲

19
00:20:05,499 --> 00:20:07,550
{\a6}And away they did run
它们果然就此消亡

20
00:20:07,560 --> 00:20:12,570
{\a6}You sure must be strong
你是那么的坚强

20
00:20:13,259 --> 00:20:17,560
{\a6}You feel like an ocean being warmed by the sun
当你化身大海 沐浴温暖日光

533
00:20:25,956 --> 00:20:29,441
{\a6}Remember walking a mile to your house
别忘了你家就在不远的前方

534
00:20:29,443 --> 00:20:32,178
{\a6}A glow in the dark
黑暗中微微发出亮光

535
00:20:33,964 --> 00:20:37,449
{\a6}I made a fumbling play for your heart
为了你能暗许芳心 我百出洋相

536
00:20:37,451 --> 00:20:40,286
{\a6}And the act struck a spark
表演中闪出一道明亮

537
00:20:42,055 --> 00:20:44,123
{\a6}You wore a charm on the chain
我窃来护符做成项链

538
00:20:44,125 --> 00:20:47,793
{\a6}That I stole especial for you
只为你一人戴上

539
00:20:49,346 --> 00:20:53,432
{\a6}Love's such a delicate thing that we do
我们的爱 如此珍贵如此精致

540
00:20:53,434 --> 00:20:56,135
{\a6}With nothing to prove
不需要任何证明

541
00:20:57,688 --> 00:21:02,158
{\a6}Which I never knew.
我却现在才明白

542
00:21:03,572 --> 00:21:06,055
你好 请给我一张去远汉普顿的车票
Hi. One ticket to Farhampton, please.

543
00:21:06,257 --> 00:21:09,257
HIMYM字幕组 谢谢观看

543
00:21:09,357 --> 00:21:38,857
{\fs15}第八季完结 期待最终季
第九季将于九月回归 HIMYM字幕组与您共同期待
\N
\N更多周边资源及全九季典藏版 欢迎关注官方微博及人人网主页
@HIMYM字幕组


