1
00:00:02,347 --> 00:00:04,039
2013年春天
In the spring of 2013,

2
00:00:04,139 --> 00:00:06,823
巴尼和罗宾距喜结连理只有几周之遥了
Barney and Robin were just weeks away from tying the knot.

3
00:00:06,825 --> 00:00:09,342
可在某些大事上 他们还未做决定
But there were still some pretty big issues they hadn't agreed on.

4
00:00:09,344 --> 00:00:11,344
领养
Adoption.

5
00:00:11,346 --> 00:00:12,496
我不知道啊
I don't know.

6
00:00:12,498 --> 00:00:14,498
只有领养才说得通
It's the only thing that makes sense.

7
00:00:14,500 --> 00:00:17,033
我真的不敢相信你会不接受
I can't... I can't believe you're not open to it.

8
00:00:17,035 --> 00:00:19,286
好吧 那就试试吧
Okay. Let's try it.

9
00:00:20,738 --> 00:00:23,006
不行 竖着的第27个词就不合适了
Nope, it doesn't work with 27 down.

10
00:00:24,375 --> 00:00:26,659
嘿 考虑到咱婚礼快到了
Hey, with the wedding so close,

11
00:00:26,661 --> 00:00:28,378
也许我们该讨论下
maybe we should talk about

12
00:00:28,380 --> 00:00:29,796
结婚后住在哪儿吧
where we're going to live.

13
00:00:29,798 --> 00:00:31,131
好吧 够了
Fine, enough.

14
00:00:31,133 --> 00:00:32,165
不用求我了
Stop begging.

15
00:00:32,167 --> 00:00:33,166
我们就住这儿
We'll live here.

16
00:00:33,168 --> 00:00:34,184
但这算你欠我的
But you owe me.

17
00:00:34,186 --> 00:00:35,552
是啊 我说不清
Yeah, I don't know...

18
00:00:35,554 --> 00:00:36,720
就是我不是完全喜欢
there's just a lot of things

19
00:00:36,722 --> 00:00:39,005
你公寓里的一些东西
I don't totally love about your apartment.

20
00:00:39,007 --> 00:00:40,357
比如什么
Like what?

21
00:00:40,359 --> 00:00:42,342
好吧 举个例子
Well, for example, why is

22
00:00:42,344 --> 00:00:45,145
为什么你的床好像放在类似铁轨的东西上
your bed on what look like train tracks?

23
00:00:46,148 --> 00:00:49,399
你太厉害了
You were wonderful.

24
00:00:49,401 --> 00:00:53,019
要是连如何取悦女人都不知道
Well, you don't get to be a state-certified orgasmologist

25
00:00:53,021 --> 00:00:54,687
怎么能成为获得国家认可的高潮大师呢
without learning how to please a woman.

26
00:00:54,689 --> 00:00:56,990
你不介意我留下来过夜吧
You don't mind if I spend the night, do you?

27
00:00:56,992 --> 00:00:58,959
呃 不这样的话
Um, how else are we gonna

28
00:00:58,961 --> 00:01:00,994
我们怎么能更深一步地了解对方呢
get to know each other on a deeper level?

29
00:01:01,695 --> 00:01:02,696
不好意思
Excuse me,

30
00:01:02,698 --> 00:01:05,549
我得把今晚的高潮报告上交给董事会
I just have to log tonight's orgasms with the licensing board.

31
00:01:20,064 --> 00:01:22,432
妞-走-人 睡眠系统
The Ho-be-gone Sleep System

32
00:01:22,434 --> 00:01:24,568
斯丁森出品 专利申请中
by Stinson, patent pending.

33
00:01:24,570 --> 00:01:27,187
墙的另外一面究竟是什么
What-what is on the other side of the wall?

34
00:01:27,189 --> 00:01:28,388
那些小妞们都去哪了
Where do the hos go?

35
00:01:28,390 --> 00:01:30,857
我哪知道 你以为我是装修公司啊
What am I, a contractor?

36
00:01:30,859 --> 00:01:35,779
我们的婚姻要有个崭新的开端
We-we need to go into this marriage with a fresh start.

37
00:01:35,781 --> 00:01:39,199
你说咱俩一起找个新房子住如何
What do you say we find a new place together?

38
00:01:39,201 --> 00:01:40,917
我爱你
I love you.

39
00:01:40,919 --> 00:01:42,452
如果那能让你高兴的话
And if that will make you happy,

40
00:01:42,454 --> 00:01:44,371
咱就找吧
then let's do it.

41
00:01:47,458 --> 00:01:51,578
喔 那我得在一个我没睡过妞的地方找个公寓
Wow, so we need to find an apartment where I haven't banged someone?

42
00:01:51,580 --> 00:01:53,152
你觉得克利夫兰怎么样
How do you feel about Cleveland?

43
00:01:53,177 --> 00:01:53,997
哈 哈
Ha, ha.

44
00:01:54,097 --> 00:01:55,583
不行 那有泰德妈妈
Nope. Ted's mom.

45
00:01:57,511 --> 00:01:59,511
{\a1}{\fs17}　　　　 老爸\N　　　  　　 老妈\N　　 　　 浪漫史\N{\fs16}{\bord1}{\3c&H00DCE1&}　　  　　　　第八季  第十九集\N
{\fnDaxlinePro-Regular}{\fs19}{\b0}{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\3c&H2F2F2F&}{\4c&H000000&}{\a1}　　　　　S08E19 The Fortress

46
00:01:59,621 --> 00:02:02,621
{\fs17}翻译: @Big-Fudge @阿狸小H @麟礡\N{\3c&H00DCE1&}{\bord1}@纷扬jas-mine @卟哒哒伽马 @苏赛晒小花\N{\3c&H007EFF&}校对: @苏赛晒小花 @阿狸小H

47
00:02:02,622 --> 00:02:05,622
{\fs17}{\3c&H00DCE1&}{\bord1}压制: @Big-Fudge\N{\3c&H007EFF&}统筹+后期: @神RoyShiCheng @苏赛晒小花

48
00:02:05,906 --> 00:02:08,306
HIMYM字幕组 倾情奉献

49
00:02:08,846 --> 00:02:11,598
嘘
Shh...

50
00:02:14,151 --> 00:02:16,686
你替莉莉给马文唱催眠曲 唱得不错啊
Nice job filling in for Lily on Marvin's lullaby.

51
00:02:16,688 --> 00:02:19,472
谢谢 就是唱小马那段时我好像快了点
Thanks, but I came in early on the horsie.

52
00:02:19,474 --> 00:02:20,740
笨死了
Stupid!

53
00:02:20,742 --> 00:02:24,728
不 你真的把莉莉的部分唱的很好了
No, you really nailed all of Lily's parts.

54
00:02:24,730 --> 00:02:27,247
我三个星期前才练好
It's been three weeks since I have.

55
00:02:27,249 --> 00:02:30,333
因为莉莉工作的事 我都没怎么见她
I barely see her anymore 'cause of this new job.

56
00:02:31,535 --> 00:02:32,737
知道什么能让你开心起来吗
Well, you know what might cheer you up?

57
00:02:33,588 --> 00:02:36,840
今晚有伍德沃斯庄园的新剧集哦
There's a new Woodworthy Manor on tonight.

58
00:02:36,842 --> 00:02:38,224
伍德沃斯庄园是一部
Woodworthy Manor

59
00:02:38,226 --> 00:02:42,395
讲述20世纪初英国上层阶级故事的电视剧
was a show about an upper class English estate at the beginning of the 20th century.

60
00:02:42,397 --> 00:02:44,631
我的天 你不可能说的是...
My word! You can't possibly mean...

61
00:02:44,633 --> 00:02:45,832
可我是这样想的
But I do!

62
00:02:45,834 --> 00:02:48,935
自从伊斯特布鲁克太太继承给了玛丽米德子爵夫人
With the succession of Lady Eastbrooke to Viscountess of Marlyemead,

63
00:02:48,937 --> 00:02:51,670
我们的侄子博德里克就成了维泽施德伯爵
our cousin Baldrick becomes the Earl of Witherstead.

64
00:02:51,672 --> 00:02:52,739
维泽施德伯爵啊
The Earl of Witherstead!

65
00:02:52,741 --> 00:02:56,175
我都在论坛上预测过15遍了
I only posted that prediction 15 times on the forums!

66
00:02:56,177 --> 00:02:57,444
不行 我不能
No, I can't.

67
00:02:57,446 --> 00:02:59,696
我答应莉莉了 要等她一起看
I promised Lily that I would wait and watch it with her.

68
00:02:59,698 --> 00:03:01,698
问题在于 船长大人
Problem is, the Captain.

69
00:03:01,700 --> 00:03:03,451
莉莉刚开始为一位有怪癖的 
Lily had just started a job

70
00:03:03,453 --> 00:03:06,686
亿万富翁 船长大人 做艺术顾问
as the art consultant for an eccentric billionaire, the Captain.

71
00:03:10,191 --> 00:03:11,324
啊嗬
Ahoy.

72
00:03:11,326 --> 00:03:12,909
瑞德虎克有个炙手可热的新艺术家
There's a hot new artist in Red Hook.

73
00:03:11,326 --> 00:03:12,909
{\a6}瑞德虎克位于布鲁克林

74
00:03:12,911 --> 00:03:15,795
他熔了世界各国的货币铸成一座雕像
He's molded world currency into a sculpture

75
00:03:15,797 --> 00:03:18,915
雕像是一位无情的大富豪在穷人身上拉翔
of a soulless plutocrat defecating on the poor.

76
00:03:18,917 --> 00:03:20,884
这是对资本主义的无情控诉
A scathing indictment of capitalism.

77
00:03:20,886 --> 00:03:22,335
我最高愿意出20万美元
I'll go as high as $200K

78
00:03:22,337 --> 00:03:24,554
如果六个月后我转手 价钱能翻倍的话
as long as you think I can flip it for double in six months.

79
00:03:24,556 --> 00:03:25,672
遵命 船长大人
Aye, aye, Cap'n.

80
00:03:25,674 --> 00:03:27,006
不好意思
Sorry.

81
00:03:33,731 --> 00:03:34,931
啊嗬
Ahoy.

82
00:03:34,933 --> 00:03:38,151
这儿有一幅画工超赞的印象主义静物画
here's this gorgeously delicate impressionist still life,

83
00:03:38,153 --> 00:03:39,986
让我想起莫奈画的池中睡莲
reminiscent of Monet's water lilies.

84
00:03:39,988 --> 00:03:40,770
在哪儿呢
Where is it?

85
00:03:40,772 --> 00:03:42,105
里克斯岛上
Rikers Island.

86
00:03:40,772 --> 00:03:42,105
{\a6}纽约著名监狱

87
00:03:42,107 --> 00:03:44,557
这位艺术家正因为恶性谋杀
The artist is serving two consecutive life sentences

88
00:03:44,559 --> 00:03:45,859
被判处两项终身监禁
for aggravated homicide.

89
00:03:45,861 --> 00:03:47,494
我最高愿意为这幅画
I'm willing to go as high as

90
00:03:47,496 --> 00:03:50,914
出六条烟和一坛子茅房酒
six cartons of cigarettes and a jug of toilet wine.

91
00:03:47,496 --> 00:03:50,914
{\a6}{\fs16}茅房酒指监狱犯人自酿的酒 通常藏在马桶的水箱里

92
00:03:50,916 --> 00:03:52,081
我负担太大了
Is it a strain,

93
00:03:52,083 --> 00:03:53,566
时不时感觉自己就像一个单亲爸爸
feeling like a single dad at times?

94
00:03:53,568 --> 00:03:56,336
的确 但是莉莉正努力在新工作领域站稳脚跟
Sure, but Lily's been busting her butt at this new job.

95
00:03:56,338 --> 00:03:58,237
她又不是在外面吃喝玩乐
It's not like she's been out there partying.

96
00:03:58,239 --> 00:03:59,672
天 我有点醉了
Man, I'm 'faced.

97
00:03:59,674 --> 00:04:02,241
我吃了一大堆鱼子酱
I ate a ton of caviar,

98
00:04:02,243 --> 00:04:03,843
还是没能把我的香槟都炸出来
but it soaked up none of the champagne.

99
00:03:59,674 --> 00:04:03,843
{\a6}{\fs16}鱼子酱配香槟会有口中噼噼啪啪的响个不停的美妙感

100
00:04:03,845 --> 00:04:05,595
-这就是周一啊  -是啊
-Mondays, right? -Yeah.

101
00:04:06,547 --> 00:04:08,181
你什么时候开始戴眼镜了
When did you get glasses?

102
00:04:08,183 --> 00:04:09,465
噢
Oh...

103
00:04:09,467 --> 00:04:11,935
你是说我的无敌防眩光眼镜
you mean my glare reduction lunettes.

104
00:04:11,937 --> 00:04:15,421
它能帮我从自命不凡的烂货中挑出真正的天才
Yeah. They help me discern genius from pretentious crap.

105
00:04:15,423 --> 00:04:16,639
你在买这副眼镜的时候
Too bad you weren't wearing those glasses

106
00:04:16,641 --> 00:04:18,107
没有戴上这副识别眼镜 真是太可惜了
when you bought those glasses.

107
00:04:19,059 --> 00:04:20,727
好了 听着 宝贝
Well, listen, baby, I-I'm just

108
00:04:20,729 --> 00:04:21,878
我很高兴见到你
happy to see you.

109
00:04:21,880 --> 00:04:23,095
如果你不是太累的话
And if you're not too tired,

110
00:04:23,097 --> 00:04:25,949
我们今晚可以一起看伍德沃斯庄园
maybe we could watch Woodworthy Manor tonight.

111
00:04:25,951 --> 00:04:26,816
可以呀
I'd love to.

112
00:04:26,818 --> 00:04:28,034
太好了 因为我想到了一个
Great! Because I've come up

113
00:04:28,036 --> 00:04:29,652
特别好玩的小游戏
with a fun little game.

114
00:04:29,654 --> 00:04:30,787
我做了一些无花果布丁
I made figgy pudding

115
00:04:30,789 --> 00:04:32,422
放在小酒杯里
and I put it in shot glasses.

116
00:04:32,424 --> 00:04:33,940
每次剧中说到
And every time they say,

117
00:04:33,942 --> 00:04:36,075
"夫人会不高兴的"
"The dowager will be less than pleased,"

118
00:04:36,077 --> 00:04:37,160
你就得
you have to...

119
00:04:37,162 --> 00:04:38,912
哦
Oh.

120
00:04:38,914 --> 00:04:39,913
呃
Ugh...

121
00:04:39,915 --> 00:04:41,214
啊嗬
Ahoy.

122
00:04:41,216 --> 00:04:43,249
一个两米多高穿异性服装的柬埔寨人
A seven-foot-tall cross-dressing Cambodian

123
00:04:43,251 --> 00:04:44,801
在往BQE的一个公告牌上
is throwing glitter and fish guts

124
00:04:44,803 --> 00:04:46,169
扔亮粉和鱼内脏
at a billboard on the B.Q.E.

125
00:04:43,303 --> 00:04:46,169
{\a6}{\fs16}B.Q.E. 连接纽约布鲁克林区和皇后区的高速公路

126
00:04:46,171 --> 00:04:48,671
那他是某个概念艺术画家吗
So he's some sort of conceptual painter?

127
00:04:48,673 --> 00:04:50,557
不是 只是一个上了地方新闻的疯子
No, no, just a crazy person on the local news.

128
00:04:50,559 --> 00:04:51,808
我以为你听了会笑呢
I thought you might have a laugh.

129
00:04:51,810 --> 00:04:53,593
你已经下班了 别紧张
You're off the clock, relax.

130
00:04:55,062 --> 00:04:56,980
我要把这个买下来
I must own it.

131
00:04:56,982 --> 00:04:59,432
遵命 船长大人
Aye, aye, Cap'n.

132
00:05:00,985 --> 00:05:03,653
嘿 你找到卖房子的经纪人了吗
Hey, did you find a Realtor to sell this place yet?

133
00:05:03,655 --> 00:05:06,155
罗宾 经纪人只会把这间公寓
Robin, a Realtor's just gonna

134
00:05:06,157 --> 00:05:07,807
卖给出价最高的人
give it to the highest bidder.

135
00:05:07,809 --> 00:05:10,076
我想卖给值得拥有的人
I need this place to go to someone worthy.

136
00:05:10,078 --> 00:05:12,478
我已经做了一些调查
And I've made some inquiries.

137
00:05:15,233 --> 00:05:17,333
巴尼
Barney?

138
00:05:17,335 --> 00:05:19,819
吾儿
My son.

139
00:05:19,821 --> 00:05:22,538
巴尼 别玩漂浮的乔•艾尔头了
Barney, enough with the floating Jor-El head

140
00:05:22,540 --> 00:05:25,041
这是超人的孤独堡垒里的
from the Fortress of Solitude in Superman, okay?

141
00:05:25,043 --> 00:05:26,175
这太老套了
It's getting old.

142
00:05:26,177 --> 00:05:30,013
我只用这个来说非常重要的事情
I only use it to say really important stuff.

143
00:05:30,015 --> 00:05:31,631
上次你用这个是告诉我
Last time you used it to tell me

144
00:05:31,633 --> 00:05:34,601
云狄斯新出了辣味版的培根汉堡
Wendy's had introduced a spicy version of "The Baconator."

145
00:05:31,633 --> 00:05:34,601
{\a6}{\fs16}Wendy's 云狄斯 美国第二大汉堡包快餐连锁店

146
00:05:34,603 --> 00:05:36,820
就是这个意思
Exactly.

147
00:05:37,288 --> 00:05:40,172
好了 吾儿
And now, my son...

148
00:05:40,174 --> 00:05:43,309
时辰已至 吾将赠与你
it is time for me to bestow on you...

149
00:05:43,311 --> 00:05:45,695
我们就不能像正常人那样面对面交流吗
Can we just talk face-to-face like normal people?

150
00:05:45,697 --> 00:05:47,697
泰德 你就
Ted, just...

151
00:05:47,699 --> 00:05:49,015
配合一下
just...

152
00:05:49,017 --> 00:05:51,367
好吗
okay?

153
00:05:51,369 --> 00:05:53,069
吾儿
My son,

154
00:05:53,071 --> 00:05:56,355
时辰已至 吾将赠与你
it is time for me to bestow on you...

155
00:05:59,693 --> 00:06:00,660
把门关上
Close the door.

156
00:06:00,662 --> 00:06:01,628
不 这也
No. This is...

157
00:06:01,630 --> 00:06:03,195
我的天啊 你就不能好好的
Oh, my God, can you just be cool?

158
00:06:03,197 --> 00:06:04,864
哪怕一次 求你了
Once? Please?

159
00:06:04,866 --> 00:06:06,382
就这一次
Just once?

160
00:06:06,384 --> 00:06:08,551
配合一下会死吗
Can you just once be cool?

161
00:06:08,553 --> 00:06:09,836
就一次
Once?

162
00:06:09,838 --> 00:06:11,537
求你了
Please?

163
00:06:17,027 --> 00:06:18,594
吾儿
My son...

164
00:06:18,596 --> 00:06:19,979
许多年来
for many years

165
00:06:19,981 --> 00:06:24,600
这套公寓都是我巴尼超人的孤独堡垒
this apartment has been my Fortress of Barnitude.

166
00:06:24,602 --> 00:06:26,736
但现在是时候让我
But now the time has come

167
00:06:26,738 --> 00:06:28,354
把它传下去了
for me to pass it on.

168
00:06:29,073 --> 00:06:32,058
不久 这个地方就会变成
Soon, this place will become

169
00:06:32,060 --> 00:06:35,394
你的"泰德超人的孤独堡垒"
your "Fortress of Soli-Ted."

170
00:06:35,396 --> 00:06:36,729
巴尼 哪怕你用
Barney, I wouldn't

171
00:06:36,731 --> 00:06:39,198
普瑞来 阿莫西林和圣水刷洗这里的每一个角落
live here even if you scrubbed every inch of this place

172
00:06:39,200 --> 00:06:41,484
我也不会住进来
with Purell, amoxicillin and holy water.

173
00:06:39,200 --> 00:06:41,484
{\a6}Purell 普瑞来 美国洗手液品牌

174
00:06:43,171 --> 00:06:44,537
好吧
Fine.

175
00:06:44,539 --> 00:06:46,405
但我觉得我们都同意
But I think we can both agree,

176
00:06:46,407 --> 00:06:49,008
如果能用乔•艾尔摄像机能让我的
it would be totally awesome to see 

177
00:06:49,010 --> 00:06:51,961
那玩意儿漂浮在空中绝对是好棒的
my deal floating around all huge-like on the big Jor-El cam.

178
00:06:51,963 --> 00:06:53,763
等一下
Hold on.

179
00:06:53,765 --> 00:06:56,632
现在堡垒里有点冷
Now, it's a little cold here in the Fortress,

180
00:06:56,634 --> 00:06:57,633
所以别因为这个
so don't judge...

181
00:06:57,635 --> 00:06:58,751
泰德 等等
Ted, wait.

182
00:06:58,753 --> 00:07:00,386
你做了什么
What did you...

183
00:07:00,388 --> 00:07:02,772
你把... 好了 这样不好玩
That's... okay, that's not funny.

184
00:07:02,774 --> 00:07:03,773
泰德 开门
Ted, open the...

185
00:07:03,775 --> 00:07:06,025
呃 墙壁在向我逼近
Uh... walls closing in.

186
00:07:06,027 --> 00:07:07,694
我没法呼吸了
I can't... can't breathe.

187
00:07:09,280 --> 00:07:10,262
必须
Must...

188
00:07:10,264 --> 00:07:12,365
展示那玩意
show deal...

189
00:07:12,367 --> 00:07:14,317
用乔•艾尔摄像机
on Jor-El cam...

190
00:07:14,319 --> 00:07:15,601
我...
I...

191
00:07:17,055 --> 00:07:18,905
这样看来我只好永远保留这套公寓了 晚安
Oh, well, guess I'm keeping this place forever, good night.

192
00:07:18,907 --> 00:07:20,606
等等 给我等一下 这样就完了
Wait a... wait a minute, that's it?

193
00:07:20,608 --> 00:07:22,492
泰德没兴趣买你的公寓
Ted wasn't interested in buying your apartment,

194
00:07:22,494 --> 00:07:24,160
你就放弃了吗
so you just gave up?

195
00:07:24,162 --> 00:07:26,445
巴尼 我抛弃了自己
Barney, I gave up my

196
00:07:26,447 --> 00:07:27,830
位于曼哈顿上西区的
beautiful two-bedroom apartment

197
00:07:27,832 --> 00:07:29,716
不用交房租的两室公寓
on the Upper West Side that was rent-free

198
00:07:29,718 --> 00:07:32,618
房东还亲自手洗我的高档衣服
and the landlord hand-washed all my delicates.

199
00:07:32,620 --> 00:07:34,921
这可能是我不用交房租的原因
Which is probably why it was rent-free.

200
00:07:34,923 --> 00:07:36,506
重点是
The point is,

201
00:07:36,508 --> 00:07:37,957
我所有内衣都要重新买
I need to buy all new underwear,

202
00:07:37,959 --> 00:07:40,893
你也答应我们一起换个新地方住
and you agreed that we would find a new place together.

203
00:07:40,895 --> 00:07:42,128
天啊 巴尼
Oh, God, Barney,

204
00:07:42,130 --> 00:07:45,131
恋爱是需要互相信任和妥协的
relationships are about trust and compromise.

205
00:07:45,133 --> 00:07:46,315
你不能只是
You can't just...

206
00:07:46,317 --> 00:07:47,600
啊 你死定了
Oh, you are so dead.

207
00:07:47,602 --> 00:07:49,152
别让我找到方法出来
If I ever figure a way out of here,

208
00:07:49,154 --> 00:07:50,770
我会让你生不如死的
I will make your life a living...

209
00:07:52,139 --> 00:07:53,973
我和莉莉真的很需要出去约个会
Lily and I really need this night out.

210
00:07:53,975 --> 00:07:55,992
丰盛精致的晚餐和芭蕾表演
A big fancy dinner and the ballet.

211
00:07:55,994 --> 00:07:57,827
谢谢你能帮忙照顾孩子
Thank you so much for babysitting.

212
00:07:57,829 --> 00:07:59,996
嘿 一小时三刀呢 谢谢你才对
Hey, three bucks an hour, thank you.

213
00:08:03,984 --> 00:08:05,484
喂 宝贝
Oh, hey, baby.

214
00:08:05,486 --> 00:08:06,819
我正要出门
Yeah, I'm just on my way out.

215
00:08:06,821 --> 00:08:08,704
如果你早到了
If you get there before...

216
00:08:08,706 --> 00:08:10,173
别这样 不是吧
Come on, really?

217
00:08:11,491 --> 00:08:13,593
之后见
I'll see you later.

218
00:08:13,595 --> 00:08:15,445
船长吗
Captain?

219
00:08:15,447 --> 00:08:16,796
真遗憾 兄弟 不过 
I'm sorry, dude. But, hey,

220
00:08:16,798 --> 00:08:18,014
你可以这样想
look at it this way:

221
00:08:18,016 --> 00:08:19,766
至少你不用去看芭蕾表演了啊
now you don't have to go to the ballet.

222
00:08:19,768 --> 00:08:21,267
把你脑袋从菊花里拔出来使一下好吗 泰德
Get your head out of your ass, Ted.

223
00:08:21,269 --> 00:08:22,469
根本就没有什么芭蕾表演
There was no ballet.

224
00:08:22,471 --> 00:08:24,691
我们就打算溜进你公寓来一炮
We were gonna sneak into your apartment and bang.

225
00:08:25,672 --> 00:08:27,273
好吧 知道有什么可以
Well, you know what might

226
00:08:27,275 --> 00:08:29,308
让我们忘掉这些烦心事吗
take both our minds off that?

227
00:08:29,310 --> 00:08:31,360
稍稍看一集
A little, uh...

228
00:08:31,362 --> 00:08:33,179
伍德沃斯庄园
Woodworthy Manor.

229
00:08:35,032 --> 00:08:36,315
不 这不行
No, I-I-I can't.

230
00:08:36,317 --> 00:08:37,450
我答应过莉莉
I-I promised Lily

231
00:08:37,452 --> 00:08:38,785
要等着她一起看的
that I would wait and watch it with her.

232
00:08:38,787 --> 00:08:40,319
要是我先看了 就好像背叛了她一样
And I feel like I'd be cheating on her.

233
00:08:40,321 --> 00:08:42,455
好吧好吧 我懂的
Sure, sure, sure, sure, I get all that.

234
00:08:42,457 --> 00:08:44,457
只不过
It's just, um...

235
00:08:44,459 --> 00:08:47,243
你要知道 今晚他们终于要找出那个
You know, tonight they're gonna finally reveal

236
00:08:47,245 --> 00:08:49,378
而陷害扫烟囱工说他偷了庄园主人
who framed the chimney sweep

237
00:08:49,380 --> 00:08:52,799
斯塔德夏尔的鹅莓的凶手了
for stealing Lord Stoutshire's gooseberries.

238
00:08:54,168 --> 00:08:55,334
还要角逐出
And reveal the winner of

239
00:08:55,336 --> 00:08:57,587
当地园艺大赛的冠军
the local gardening competition.

240
00:08:57,589 --> 00:08:58,888
我完全猜不透他们怎样才能
I don't know how they're going to pack

241
00:08:58,890 --> 00:09:00,756
把这么多剧情集中到一集里面
all that action into one episode.

242
00:09:06,815 --> 00:09:08,981
啊哦
Oops.

243
00:09:10,717 --> 00:09:11,884
不行啊 泰德
No, Ted, you know

244
00:09:11,886 --> 00:09:14,320
-我答应了莉莉  -嘘 别说话
-I promised Lily, I... -Shh, shh, shh.

245
00:09:14,322 --> 00:09:16,322
顺其自然吧
Just let it happen.

246
00:09:16,324 --> 00:09:18,741
这周晚些时候 巴尼回家时发现
Later that week, Barney came home to discover

247
00:09:18,743 --> 00:09:21,577
罗宾给他准备了一个小惊喜
that Robin had a little surprise waiting for him.

248
00:09:26,500 --> 00:09:28,668
-含羞草吗  -是啊
-Mimosas? -Mm-hmm.

249
00:09:26,500 --> 00:09:28,668
{\a6}Mimosas 因为颜色像含羞草而命名的鸡尾酒

250
00:09:28,670 --> 00:09:31,704
刚烤的饼干的香味
Freshly-baked cookie smell?

251
00:09:31,706 --> 00:09:34,240
还有穿红色运动衣的中年妇女
A middle-aged woman in a red blazer?

252
00:09:34,242 --> 00:09:36,575
我明白了
I see what this is.

253
00:09:36,577 --> 00:09:39,045
你总算同意我纵酒狂欢啦
You finally green-lit my orgy idea!

254
00:09:39,047 --> 00:09:40,246
真好
Okay.

255
00:09:40,248 --> 00:09:42,048
这是场家庭招待会 巴尼
It's an open house, Barney.

256
00:09:42,050 --> 00:09:44,550
跟你的堡垒说再见吧
Say good-bye to your fortress.

257
00:09:44,552 --> 00:09:46,769
要不是因为我们要狂欢
If we weren't about to have an orgy,

258
00:09:46,771 --> 00:09:48,587
我肯定会对你发火的
I'd be so mad at you right now.

259
00:09:53,143 --> 00:09:54,583
如果你们跟随我到卧室
If you'll follow me into the bedroom,

260
00:09:54,644 --> 00:09:56,593
会看到很棒的实木家具哦
I'll show you some beautiful woodwork.

261
00:09:56,595 --> 00:09:59,070
我现在太生气 都懒得吐槽 曾有多少无知少女
I am way too upset right now to point out how many women

262
00:09:59,072 --> 00:10:00,771
在卧室里见过很棒的"实木家具"
have seen some beautiful woodwork in there.

263
00:09:59,322 --> 00:10:00,771
{\a6}也指小鸡鸡

264
00:10:00,773 --> 00:10:02,289
愤怒自我击掌
Angry self five!

265
00:10:02,291 --> 00:10:03,290
啊
Rah!

266
00:10:03,292 --> 00:10:04,492
罗宾
Robin,

267
00:10:04,494 --> 00:10:05,893
我不允许你卖掉公寓
I did not agree to this.

268
00:10:05,895 --> 00:10:06,994
你必须允许
Yes, you did.

269
00:10:06,996 --> 00:10:08,996
我搬出我的公寓
That is why I gave up my apartment.

270
00:10:08,998 --> 00:10:11,782
不是为了住进一个病菌滋生
Not so I could live in a disease-riddled bang pad

271
00:10:11,784 --> 00:10:13,834
上门荡妇阴魂不散的淫窝
haunted by the ghosts of your ex-skanks.

272
00:10:15,337 --> 00:10:17,938
浴室是意大利大理石的哟
The bathrooms are Italian marble.

273
00:10:19,141 --> 00:10:20,774
你好啊 老兄
Hello, old bean.

274
00:10:20,776 --> 00:10:22,209
今晚棒极了 对吧
Jolly good evening, isn't it?

275
00:10:22,211 --> 00:10:23,277
你们在这儿干嘛
What are you doing here?

276
00:10:23,279 --> 00:10:25,796
而且你说话怎么跟麦当娜似的
And why do you sound like Madonna?

277
00:10:25,798 --> 00:10:27,097
罗宾让我们都来转转
Uh, Robin asked us all to come here

278
00:10:27,099 --> 00:10:29,600
假装我们是很喜欢这公寓的潜在买主
and pretend that we are prospective buyers who love this apartment.

279
00:10:29,602 --> 00:10:31,352
我受到伍德沃斯庄园中
And inspired by a character

280
00:10:31,354 --> 00:10:33,637
一个角色的启发 决定扮演
on Woodworthy Manor, I've decided to play

281
00:10:33,639 --> 00:10:35,356
埃姆斯布瑞•波斯尔思韦特
Emsbry Postlethwaite,

282
00:10:35,358 --> 00:10:39,276
一位帅气迷人内心却厌恶自己生活的板球运动员
a handsome cricket player who secretly hates his life.

283
00:10:39,278 --> 00:10:40,945
你没必要当什么板球运动员
You don't have to be a cricket player.

284
00:10:40,947 --> 00:10:42,530
跟埃姆斯布瑞的爸爸说去吧
Tell that to Emsbry's father.

285
00:10:42,532 --> 00:10:43,864
抱歉
Sorry!

286
00:10:43,866 --> 00:10:45,416
我来了
Oh...

287
00:10:45,418 --> 00:10:48,202
我去看了些地铁流浪汉的涂鸦作品
I was checking out some mole people's graffiti art

288
00:10:48,204 --> 00:10:50,171
我的披肩还被地铁勾住了
and my cape got caught on the F train.

289
00:10:50,173 --> 00:10:51,172
来
Oh.

290
00:10:51,174 --> 00:10:52,423
亲亲
Bisou bisou.

291
00:10:53,291 --> 00:10:55,659
哇 好可爱的宝宝
Oh, what a cute baby.

292
00:10:55,661 --> 00:10:56,710
他叫什么名字啊
What's his name?

293
00:10:56,712 --> 00:10:57,828
马尔文
Marvin.

294
00:10:57,830 --> 00:10:58,779
为了纪念我父亲
For my father.

295
00:10:58,781 --> 00:11:00,497
噢 这好贴心啊
Oh, that's so sweet.

296
00:11:00,499 --> 00:11:03,217
你们俩已经在这一带看很多公寓了吗
Have you two been looking at a lot of places in this neighborhood?

297
00:11:03,219 --> 00:11:04,518
噢 事实上他们不是...
Oh, actually they're not...

298
00:11:04,520 --> 00:11:06,887
是 我们看过了
Yes, we have.

299
00:11:06,889 --> 00:11:08,338
什么
What?

300
00:11:08,340 --> 00:11:12,226
我跟我丈夫埃姆斯布瑞爱死这一片地区了
My husband Emsbry and I just love this area.

301
00:11:12,228 --> 00:11:14,845
我是一位帅气迷人内心却厌恶自己生活的板球运动员
I'm a cricket player who secretly hates his life.

302
00:11:15,731 --> 00:11:17,648
你在干什么啊
What are you doing?

303
00:11:17,650 --> 00:11:19,817
鉴于你再一次迟到了
Well, you were late yet again,

304
00:11:19,819 --> 00:11:21,702
我决定和泰德做一次角色扮演
and so I'm gonna do this little scene study with Ted.

305
00:11:21,704 --> 00:11:24,121
你问为什么 因为他随时在我身边
Why? Because he's there for me.

306
00:11:25,874 --> 00:11:27,658
假装你结婚了
Pretending you're married?

307
00:11:27,660 --> 00:11:30,494
这离你要证明的观点也太远了吧
That's going a little far to prove your point, isn't it?

308
00:11:30,496 --> 00:11:32,963
打扰一下 但是你说同性恋情侣们结婚
Excuse me, but I think it's offensive to suggest

309
00:11:32,965 --> 00:11:35,916
只是为了证明某种观点也太无礼了吧
the only reason gay people get married is to prove a point.

310
00:11:35,918 --> 00:11:38,201
不×5
No, no, no, no, no.

311
00:11:38,203 --> 00:11:39,753
我不是那个意思
I didn't... that's not what I...

312
00:11:39,755 --> 00:11:41,171
谢谢你 姐们 看来需要找人来给
Thank you, sister-- somebody needs

313
00:11:41,173 --> 00:11:44,008
这位女士的思想安一块倒车镜
to get this lady's mind a rearview mirror

314
00:11:44,010 --> 00:11:46,877
因为她的思维在倒退
because she is thinking in reverse. Mm-hmm.

315
00:11:49,898 --> 00:11:51,565
恨就一个字 我只说一次
Hate is a four-letter word.

316
00:11:51,567 --> 00:11:53,550
我没有 我投票给了...
I didn't... I voted for...

317
00:11:57,072 --> 00:11:58,739
噢 这是安全系统的一部分吗
Oh, is this part of a security system?

318
00:11:58,741 --> 00:11:59,940
算是吧
Sort of.

319
00:11:59,942 --> 00:12:02,225
它和门口的擦鞋垫是连起来的 你看
It's connected to the welcome mat. You see...

320
00:12:02,227 --> 00:12:04,111
假设你带回家的小妞
Let's say the young lady you're bringing home

321
00:12:04,113 --> 00:12:05,412
穿的冬装
is dressed for winter.

322
00:12:05,414 --> 00:12:06,664
在这个面板里面
Under those layers,

323
00:12:06,666 --> 00:12:08,065
可能有个不幸的消息等着你
an unwelcome surprise could await you.

324
00:12:08,067 --> 00:12:10,251
在擦鞋垫下面我藏了一个
The scale with body fat calculator

325
00:12:10,253 --> 00:12:12,453
人体脂肪测量秤
I've hidden under the welcome mat

326
00:12:12,455 --> 00:12:15,072
可以确保我不会睡让我后悔的妞
makes sure you never have banger's remorse.

327
00:12:15,074 --> 00:12:17,124
肥妞快走
The Heavy Set Go

328
00:12:17,126 --> 00:12:18,709
斯丁森出品 专利申请中
by Stinson, patent pending.

329
00:12:18,711 --> 00:12:21,629
因为卧室里只有一种丰满的东西是你想要的
'Cause there's only one kind of chubby you want in the bedroom.

330
00:12:21,631 --> 00:12:23,080
我说的对吧 大家
Am I right, people?

331
00:12:23,082 --> 00:12:26,267
这家伙知道我在说什么
This guy knows what I'm talking about.

332
00:12:26,269 --> 00:12:30,387
不是我想教你和埃姆斯布瑞怎么养"你们的"孩子
I don't want to tell you and Emsbry how to raise your child,

333
00:12:30,389 --> 00:12:33,023
但如果你一直让他打盹的话
but I think if you keep letting him nap,

334
00:12:33,025 --> 00:12:34,141
他会整夜睡不着的
he's gonna be up all night.

335
00:12:34,143 --> 00:12:36,277
真是搞笑 听起来好像你最近有
Funny, you sound like someone who's been

336
00:12:36,279 --> 00:12:38,145
陪着他入睡一样
around for his bedtime lately.

337
00:12:38,147 --> 00:12:40,731
嗯 有人能给这位女士一家店面
Uh, can somebody get this lady a storefront

338
00:12:40,733 --> 00:12:43,433
好让她专注于自己的事情吗
'cause she needs to mind her own business, mm-kay?

339
00:12:44,570 --> 00:12:45,986
你能歇会儿吗
Would you stop it?

340
00:12:45,988 --> 00:12:48,539
噢 对 对 因为这是你的抉择
Oh, right, right, because it's a choice.

341
00:12:49,991 --> 00:12:51,792
你们知道什么不用抉择吗
You know what's not a choice?

342
00:12:51,794 --> 00:12:53,294
充满基情地享用这个厨房
Being gay for this kitchen.

343
00:12:54,329 --> 00:12:56,413
打开方式有点不太对 重点是
That came out wrong-- the point is,

344
00:12:56,415 --> 00:12:58,666
看看这个超赞的公寓吧
let's focus on this awesome apartment.

345
00:12:58,668 --> 00:13:00,134
你说得对
You're right.

346
00:13:00,136 --> 00:13:02,970
看看这个传说中的等离子电视吧
Look at that fabulous plasma television.

347
00:13:02,972 --> 00:13:06,223
我的前夫 那个从不支持我事业的家伙
My ex-husband, who never supported my career,

348
00:13:06,225 --> 00:13:10,894
会爱死用这个来看维京人
would love to watch the Vikings never win a Super Bowl

349
00:13:10,896 --> 00:13:12,680
在历史上从来没赢过的超级碗比赛
in franchise history on that thing.

350
00:13:12,682 --> 00:13:14,932
-岂有此理  -别让她戳中了你的怒点
-How dare you. -Don't let her push your buttons.

351
00:13:15,633 --> 00:13:17,318
对
Right.

352
00:13:18,320 --> 00:13:21,105
我才不在意什么橄榄球赛呢
I don't care about football.

353
00:13:21,107 --> 00:13:22,690
我更算得上是个
I'm more of a...

354
00:13:22,692 --> 00:13:24,307
伍德沃斯庄园剧迷
Woodworthy Manor fan.

355
00:13:25,360 --> 00:13:27,911
我非常享受那一夜看剧的美好时光
I very much enjoyed watching it the other night.

356
00:13:28,698 --> 00:13:29,997
和埃姆斯布瑞一起
With Emsbry.

357
00:13:29,999 --> 00:13:31,148
你不会吧
Oh, you didn't.

358
00:13:31,150 --> 00:13:32,700
是 我们看了
Yeah, oh, yeah.

359
00:13:32,702 --> 00:13:34,501
我知道是谁故意水淹了
I know who deliberately overwatered

360
00:13:34,503 --> 00:13:36,337
琪尔斯布瑞夫人那获过奖的玫瑰
Lady Chillsbury's prize-winning roses.

361
00:13:36,339 --> 00:13:38,872
他们一整季都在为那个真相做铺垫
They have been building to that reveal all season,

362
00:13:38,874 --> 00:13:40,791
马修 你敢再往下说
Marshall, don't you tell me...

363
00:13:40,793 --> 00:13:43,427
是帕尔森•斯莫尔斯比
It was Parson Smallsby.

364
00:13:46,264 --> 00:13:48,849
哇 风景不错
Wow, great view.

365
00:13:48,851 --> 00:13:49,850
而且是可定制的哟
And customizable.

366
00:13:49,852 --> 00:13:50,884
假设你承诺给一个女孩
Let's say you promised a girl

367
00:13:50,886 --> 00:13:52,002
一场惊喜旅行
a surprise trip

368
00:13:52,004 --> 00:13:54,171
到地球上最浪漫的地方
to the most romantic place on Earth.

369
00:13:54,173 --> 00:13:56,357
不准偷看哦
No peeking.

370
00:13:56,359 --> 00:13:58,642
哇 我们一定到了很远的地方
Wow, we must've gone far.

371
00:13:58,644 --> 00:14:02,162
在你的私人飞机上待了快有六个小时了
We were on your private jet for, like, six hours.

372
00:14:02,164 --> 00:14:03,480
是啊
Well,

373
00:14:03,482 --> 00:14:05,149
你一定不是戴着耳塞乘着公交
You definitely weren't on a bus to Delaware

374
00:14:05,151 --> 00:14:07,350
来回了一趟特拉华州 我只能告诉你这么多
and back wearing earplugs, I'll tell you that much.

375
00:14:07,352 --> 00:14:09,453
看到眼前的美景时你一定会觉得
And I think you'll agree it was worth the wait

376
00:14:09,455 --> 00:14:11,354
一切等待都是值得的
once you see the view.

377
00:14:11,356 --> 00:14:13,207
亲爱的 我们到啦
Et voila ma cherie.

378
00:14:15,994 --> 00:14:18,361
噢 我的天哪
Oh, my God.

379
00:14:18,363 --> 00:14:20,414
你带我飞到了维加斯
You flew me to Vegas?

380
00:14:20,416 --> 00:14:22,916
这是 这是巴黎
It's, um... it's Par...

381
00:14:22,918 --> 00:14:24,885
算了 管用就行 无所谓啦
Well, hey, whatever works, whatever...

382
00:14:24,887 --> 00:14:27,054
风景之屋
The Room With a Screw

383
00:14:27,056 --> 00:14:28,839
斯丁森出品 专利申请中
by Stinson, patent pending.

384
00:14:29,674 --> 00:14:30,674
我看懂你的这些把戏了
I know what you're trying to do.

385
00:14:30,676 --> 00:14:31,759
你就是想把这些人都吓跑
You're trying to drive people away.

386
00:14:31,761 --> 00:14:33,010
不 我才没有呢 我只是
No, I'm not-- I'm just trying

387
00:14:33,012 --> 00:14:34,678
卖弄下这套公寓独一无二的特征
to show off all of its one-of-a-kind features.

388
00:14:34,680 --> 00:14:37,380
看 看 我这儿还有 威尼斯
See, see, there's also, uh, Venice.

389
00:14:38,433 --> 00:14:41,151
尼亚加拉大瀑布
Niagara Falls,

390
00:14:41,153 --> 00:14:43,720
非洲之旅
African safari.

391
00:14:43,722 --> 00:14:44,688
哦
Oh...

392
00:14:44,690 --> 00:14:46,023
还有我的最爱
and my favorite...

393
00:14:48,943 --> 00:14:50,244
怎么样
Huh?

394
00:14:50,246 --> 00:14:52,079
让女孩以为自己在乎的人都已化为灰烬
Nothing gets a girl to go from "On the fence"

395
00:14:52,081 --> 00:14:54,864
没有什么比这更快的方法
to "On all fours" Faster than thinking

396
00:14:54,866 --> 00:14:56,950
让她从"犹豫不决"转变到"坚定不移"了
everyone she's ever held dear is a glowing pile of ash.

397
00:14:56,952 --> 00:14:58,919
蘑菇云击掌
Mushroom cloud five.

398
00:15:03,792 --> 00:15:06,260
我喜欢你的口音
I love you accent.

399
00:15:06,262 --> 00:15:07,678
谢谢
Thank you.

400
00:15:07,680 --> 00:15:09,079
我练了整整一早上了
I practiced it all morning.

401
00:15:10,099 --> 00:15:11,414
你真可爱
You are adorable.

402
00:15:12,468 --> 00:15:14,584
那个马修真是个幸运的男人
That Marshall's a lucky man.

403
00:15:14,586 --> 00:15:16,186
哦 你真是招人喜欢
Well, aren't you ducky?

404
00:15:16,188 --> 00:15:18,088
说真的 如果你是直男
Seriously if you were straight,

405
00:15:18,090 --> 00:15:20,257
我一定为你倾倒
I'd be all over you.

406
00:15:21,292 --> 00:15:22,559
哼
Huh.

407
00:15:23,728 --> 00:15:25,112
这是什么
What's this?

408
00:15:25,114 --> 00:15:25,979
哦 天呐
Oh, God.

409
00:15:25,981 --> 00:15:27,781
史上最好的东西
Only the best thing ever.

410
00:15:27,783 --> 00:15:30,284
假设你和一个女生过了愉快的一夜 
Let's say you had a wonderful night with a girl, but now

411
00:15:30,286 --> 00:15:33,770
她有点像吃完避孕药一样 磨叽着不走
she's turning into a bit of a morning-after pill.

412
00:15:41,830 --> 00:15:43,780
看到了吧 我们要延长坡道
See? We need to extend the chute

413
00:15:43,782 --> 00:15:46,049
再加一个着陆点
and add a landing spot.

414
00:15:46,051 --> 00:15:48,669
你还说用假人测试是浪费时间
And you said testing it with a dummy was a waste of time.

415
00:15:48,671 --> 00:15:52,723
不 我说的是"打扮这假人"是浪费时间
No, I said "Dressing the dummy" Was a waste of time.

416
00:15:52,725 --> 00:15:54,508
贱人山的求生通道
The Escape From Bitch Mountain

417
00:15:54,510 --> 00:15:56,193
斯丁森出品 专利申请中
by Stinson, patent pending.

418
00:15:56,195 --> 00:15:57,594
他开玩笑呢 这只是 你知道
He's kidding, it's just, you know,

419
00:15:57,596 --> 00:15:58,762
以防失火
in case of fire.

420
00:15:58,764 --> 00:16:00,630
不是的 但是很高兴你正好提到了火
No, but I'm glad you mentioned fire.

421
00:16:00,632 --> 00:16:03,100
看到那些烟雾探测器了吗
See those smoke detectors?

422
00:16:04,135 --> 00:16:05,352
念出这些话
Say these words.

423
00:16:06,938 --> 00:16:09,306
"我想要更进一步的承诺"
"I'm looking for a deeper commitment."

424
00:16:10,693 --> 00:16:14,361
"我太累了""我们来抱抱吧"也会激活它
It's also triggered by "I'm too tired," "Let's snuggle,"

425
00:16:14,363 --> 00:16:15,696
还有"我月经晚了一周"
and "I'm a week late."

426
00:16:15,698 --> 00:16:17,314
巴尼 我身上都湿了
Barney, I'm getting wet.

427
00:16:17,316 --> 00:16:21,151
说这句就能把它关掉
And that turns it off.

428
00:16:21,153 --> 00:16:22,485
好吧 别说了
Look, just stop talking.

429
00:16:22,487 --> 00:16:24,037
我们已经做好决定了
We've made up our minds.

430
00:16:24,039 --> 00:16:25,789
哦 好吧 谢谢你们来参观
Oh, well, thanks for taking a look.

431
00:16:25,791 --> 00:16:26,874
我来送你们出去
I'll walk you out.

432
00:16:26,876 --> 00:16:28,709
我们买了
We'll take it.

433
00:16:28,711 --> 00:16:31,211
只要你们不用紫外光灯 住在这里一定会超幸福的
If you never get a black light, you'll be so happy here.

434
00:16:28,711 --> 00:16:31,211
{\a6}紫外光灯会照出残留"小蝌蚪"的痕迹

435
00:16:31,213 --> 00:16:33,130
太好了 太好了
Yes, yes!

436
00:16:38,603 --> 00:16:40,837
天堂里的烦恼吗
Trouble in paradise?

437
00:16:38,603 --> 00:16:40,837
{\a6}《天堂里的烦恼》婚外恋电影

438
00:16:47,511 --> 00:16:50,013
我们有个孩子
We have a child together.

439
00:16:56,351 --> 00:16:59,306
真不敢相信你居然没等我一起看伍德沃斯庄园
I can't believe you watched Woodworthy Manor without me.

440
00:16:59,360 --> 00:17:02,078
真不敢相信你居然生我的气
I can't believe that you're mad at me.

441
00:17:02,080 --> 00:17:05,031
我老婆和基友都把我抛弃了
I've been abandoned by my wife and my gay companion.

442
00:17:05,033 --> 00:17:07,533
如果我打羽毛球时候把一只眼睛弄瞎了
If I get blinded in one eye by a badminton shuttlecock,

443
00:17:07,535 --> 00:17:09,035
那我就也成了艾斯特布鲁克庄主了
you might as well call me Lord Esterbrooke.

444
00:17:10,038 --> 00:17:11,153
你背着我看了最新一集吗
You watched the new one without me?

445
00:17:11,155 --> 00:17:13,923
被人背叛很不爽吧 埃姆斯布瑞
Betrayal stings, doesn't it, Emsbry?

446
00:17:15,292 --> 00:17:16,425
嘿
Hey.

447
00:17:16,427 --> 00:17:17,476
嘿 听着
Hey. Listen.

448
00:17:17,478 --> 00:17:18,761
不 我先说
No, me first.

449
00:17:19,630 --> 00:17:20,630
我考虑了一下
I've been thinking

450
00:17:20,632 --> 00:17:22,098
想明白了一些事
and I realized something.

451
00:17:22,100 --> 00:17:26,168
孤独堡垒是超人独处的地方
The Fortress of Solitude is where Superman went to be alone.

452
00:17:26,170 --> 00:17:28,521
我永远都不想再一个人了
And I never want to be alone again.

453
00:17:28,523 --> 00:17:31,557
谢谢 巴尼 那真是
Thank you, Barney, that really...

454
00:17:31,559 --> 00:17:33,609
然后我想起了超人第二部
But then I remembered in Superman II,

455
00:17:33,611 --> 00:17:36,362
超人为了露易丝•莱恩放弃了他的所有能力
Superman gave up all his powers to be with Lois Lane,

456
00:17:36,364 --> 00:17:38,231
在那之后 老实说他就是个废人
and he was honestly kind of a vag after that.

457
00:17:38,233 --> 00:17:40,015
哥们 能不能停一下
Oh, buddy, just quit while...

458
00:17:40,017 --> 00:17:41,234
然后 超人第三部
Now, Superman III was

459
00:17:41,236 --> 00:17:42,568
简直就是一部灾难
a complete train wreck totally.

460
00:17:42,570 --> 00:17:43,619
你想说什么
What's your point?

461
00:17:44,622 --> 00:17:46,188
想说 我爱你
that I love you.

462
00:17:46,190 --> 00:17:48,190
还有
And...

463
00:17:48,192 --> 00:17:50,710
我要为你放弃我的公寓
I'm giving up my apartment for you.

464
00:17:50,712 --> 00:17:54,964
还有超人系列电影的水平参差不齐
And that the Superman films are uneven.

465
00:17:56,416 --> 00:17:58,868
我真的很感动 巴尼 但是
I really appreciate that, Barney, but...

466
00:18:00,204 --> 00:18:02,922
恭喜啊 你们入手了这间超赞的公寓
Congrats. You guys are getting a fantastic apartment.

467
00:18:02,924 --> 00:18:06,392
我知道这里的一些地方有一点点奇怪
I mean, I know some of the features are a little weird.

468
00:18:06,394 --> 00:18:07,927
一点点吗
A little?

469
00:18:08,645 --> 00:18:09,679
我们会把这里都扒光
We're gonna rip this thing

470
00:18:09,681 --> 00:18:11,013
拆成毛坯房
down to the studs.

471
00:18:11,015 --> 00:18:12,765
我明白
I get it.

472
00:18:12,767 --> 00:18:15,434
但是 我是说 还是有些值得保留的地方
But, I mean, some things might be worth saving.

473
00:18:15,436 --> 00:18:17,687
我可没看出来 没有
I don't see any. No.

474
00:18:17,689 --> 00:18:19,989
你没看出来
You don't see any?

475
00:18:20,691 --> 00:18:22,024
当然这里的一些东西是有些吓人
Sure some of the stuff in here is creepy,

476
00:18:22,026 --> 00:18:24,360
但也非常有才啊
but it's also brilliant.

477
00:18:24,362 --> 00:18:27,663
我是说 很多天才都有些古怪
I mean, a lot of geniuses were kind of pervy.

478
00:18:27,665 --> 00:18:29,015
看看托马斯•爱迪生
Look at Thomas Edison

479
00:18:29,017 --> 00:18:31,167
不然你以为灯泡怎么会是胸部的形状呢
why do you think that lightbulbs are boob-shaped?

480
00:18:31,169 --> 00:18:33,786
好吧 我们要把这个地方彻底拆掉
Yeah, we're taking a wrecking ball to this place

481
00:18:33,788 --> 00:18:37,406
建成个真正适合人类的地方
and turning it into something actually fit for humans.

482
00:18:39,460 --> 00:18:40,793
失陪一下
Excuse me.

483
00:18:47,402 --> 00:18:48,768
出去
Get out!

484
00:18:48,770 --> 00:18:51,938
巴尼超人的孤独堡垒不卖了
The Fortress of Barnitude is no longer for sale.

485
00:18:51,940 --> 00:18:54,390
还有你的老公一下午一直盯着我的屁股看
Also your husband has been staring at my ass

486
00:18:54,392 --> 00:18:58,027
所以别装高风亮节了
all afternoon so don't act all high-and-mighty.

487
00:18:58,029 --> 00:18:59,762
你拒绝了他们
You turned them down?

488
00:18:59,764 --> 00:19:03,399
是啊 如果我要求你改变太多
Yeah. If I ask you to change too many things about yourself,

489
00:19:03,401 --> 00:19:06,535
你就不是我爱上的那个人了
you're not gonna be the man I fell in love with.

490
00:19:06,537 --> 00:19:09,572
所以 我接受并欣赏你
Turns out, I accept and appreciate

491
00:19:09,574 --> 00:19:14,076
包括你最猥琐 最可怕 最反社会的阴暗面
even the grossest, creepiest, most sociopathic parts of you.

492
00:19:15,246 --> 00:19:18,714
某人刚才好像已经把结婚誓言写好了哦
Sounds like somebody just wrote her vows.

493
00:19:22,953 --> 00:19:24,286
是船长
It's the Captain.

494
00:19:25,455 --> 00:19:26,555
啊嗬
Ahoy.

495
00:19:26,557 --> 00:19:28,290
中央公园的动物园里有一匹斑马
There's a zebra at the Central Park Zoo

496
00:19:28,292 --> 00:19:30,593
有着对摄影非常敏锐的蹄子
who's got quite a keen hoof at photography.

497
00:19:30,595 --> 00:19:32,795
说来好笑 他竟然对颜色很在行 现在
Ironically, he's great with color. Now...

498
00:19:32,797 --> 00:19:36,015
船长 我会去看看的 但不是今晚
Captain, I'll check it out, just not tonight.

499
00:19:36,017 --> 00:19:38,901
我需要些时间陪陪我的丈夫
I need to spend some time with my husband.

500
00:19:38,903 --> 00:19:41,303
你确定吗
You sure?

501
00:19:41,305 --> 00:19:43,806
我知道 我这样忙于工作 你挺不容易的
I know it's been tough, me working this much,

502
00:19:43,808 --> 00:19:47,976
我估计自己对艺术家气派的追求也有点过火了
and I guess I went a little overboard with the whole artsy thing.

503
00:19:47,978 --> 00:19:49,245
我知道
I know.

504
00:19:49,247 --> 00:19:50,413
你那披肩
The cape.

505
00:19:50,415 --> 00:19:51,530
我的披肩怎么了
What about my cape?

506
00:19:51,532 --> 00:19:52,648
我很喜欢
I love it.

507
00:19:52,650 --> 00:19:54,834
而且我知道 你热爱这份工作
And I... I know that you love this job.

508
00:19:54,836 --> 00:19:56,452
我应该更支持你的 我只是想你了
I should be more supportive-- I just miss you.

509
00:19:56,454 --> 00:19:58,337
我也想你
I miss you, too.

510
00:19:58,339 --> 00:19:59,822
嗨 伙计们
Hey, guys.

511
00:19:59,824 --> 00:20:01,957
-嗨  -嗨
-Hey. -Hey.

512
00:20:01,959 --> 00:20:04,010
你们都好幸运
You guys are all so lucky.

513
00:20:04,012 --> 00:20:06,762
我什么时候才能找到真爱呢
When am I gonna find something real?

514
00:20:06,764 --> 00:20:10,049
埃姆斯布瑞 想不想试试和女人在一起是什么感觉
Well, Emsbry, ready to see what it's like to be with a woman?

515
00:20:10,051 --> 00:20:14,270
万事总有第一次嘛
I suppose there's a first time for everything.

516
00:20:15,022 --> 00:20:17,056
-去吧  -吾儿
-Go ahead. -My son.

517
00:20:26,796 --> 00:20:29,881
你们确定我俩会喜欢伍德沃斯庄园吗
Are you guys sure we're gonna like this Woodworthy Manor show?

518
00:20:30,050 --> 00:20:31,983
是啊 听起来有点无聊
Yeah, it sounds kind of boring.

519
00:20:33,219 --> 00:20:34,386
有点无聊
Kind of boring?

520
00:20:34,388 --> 00:20:38,056
快点坐下吧 但相信我吧 绝对精彩得让你坐不住
Grab a seat guys, but trust me, you're only gonna need the edge.

521
00:20:38,908 --> 00:20:42,279
好了 先讲一段背景故事
Ah-ha, all right, now, a little backstory.

522
00:20:42,281 --> 00:20:45,866
斯塔德夏尔小姐的槌球及踝靴事业已经发展壮大了
Lady Stoutshire has developed a serious case of croquet ankle

523
00:20:45,868 --> 00:20:49,920
厨子布特布拉什夫人找不到足够的栗子
and the cook Mrs. Bootbrush can't find enough chestnuts

524
00:20:49,922 --> 00:20:52,005
来喂圣克里斯宾节的鹅
for a proper St. Crispin's Day goose.

525
00:20:52,007 --> 00:20:53,423
一起看吧
Let's watch.

526
00:21:04,936 --> 00:21:06,353
我爱你
I love you.

527
00:21:06,355 --> 00:21:07,354
我手腕摔坏了
My wrist is broken.

528
00:21:07,356 --> 00:21:09,389
-那也值了  -嗷
-Worth it. -Ow.

529
00:21:09,391 --> 00:21:11,391
HIMYM字幕组 谢谢观看

